<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369986" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode3B1D5563-8BD3-4BC3-A2C8-7178AF0ECEA5">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">30000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode98F452E0-FADD-4335-8459-87D3F59B902F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode36AFFF32-9D84-4BF8-8C50-CAB16C3EEEA6">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">8000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeE1044F87-CDC0-4CEA-AAC5-97126E82D375">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN Tennessee Board of Regents, Office of Academic Affairs AND Tennessee Technology University This Agreement is made this fifteenth day of June, 2009, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as the "TBR", and Tennessee Technology University, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A.    The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: 1.   Continue overall development of the community college education and workforce web site with emphasis on development of the individual nontraditional student page and the development of a community college “score card” report. 2.   Develop an integrated marketing campaign to market the community college education and workforce website to the state’s stakeholders, including potential students, other state-funded entities, and business and industry. 3.   Provide additional video production and editing services. 4.   Continue to provide limited technical support for the web portal previously developed to facilitate the grant process required under the Carl D. Perkins Career and Technical Education Act of 2006 for the community colleges. B.    The following tasks will be performed by the Contractor: 1. The Contractor will in support of the community college web site for the academic affairs workforce development office develop an integrated marketing campaign to increase traffic directed toward the website is to include, but not restricted to: a.   print campaign material, b.   electronic media, c.   the utilization of direct mail, and d.   tradeshow material. ($8,000) 2.   Develop a targeted integrated marketing campaign toward the Tennessee Career Centers, operated by the Tennessee Department of Labor. The intent is to increase the visibility of community colleges in the centers to their clients. ($3,000) 3.   Collect and prepare additional video vignettes for the community college websites to emphasize how the workforce units of the colleges seek to serve all aspects of business and industry within their service area. ($2,000) 4.   Enhance the “individual” section of the community college website to include, but not be limited to, additional information targeted toward: a.   military personnel b.   single parents and displaced homemakers c.   under represented genders in nontraditional occupations d.   English as a second language learners e.   displaced workers, and f.    general information on financial aid. ($4,000) 5. Develop a “dashboard” reporting mechanism, highlighting a graphic interface of Tennessee Board of Regents’ Community College data. The information presented would include, but not be limited to: a.   general community college data, b.   data related to the Carl D. Perkins Career and Technical Education Act of 2006 (e.g. annual consolidated annual report (CAR) and federal agreed upon performance levels (FAUPL)), and c. data related to the non-credit workforce development units of the colleges. ($10,000) 6. Provide technical support for the Perkins IV data system web portal. ($3,000) B. The TBR agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1.   Compensation to the Contractor will be based upon successful completion, as agreed upon by the two parties, of each task within the scope of work. 2.   Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, provided that payments shall be made only upon submittal of invoices by the Contractor, and after performance of the portion of the services which the invoiced amount represents. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Agreement. 4. In no event shall the liability of the TBR under this contract exceed $ 30,000 . Funds are dependent upon federal funding. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement. 1.   If the Contractor is an individual, the Contractor warrants that within the past six months he/she has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2.   The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitmentor recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3.   Contractor agrees to complete a TBR Annual Title VI Survey or cooperate with a TBR Title VI compliance audit if it received Federal funds under this Agreement. 4.   The term of this contract shall be from June 15, 2009 to September 30, 2010. 5.   This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 45 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 6.   If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this Agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this Agreement, the TBR shall have the right to immediately terminate this Agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the TBR for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Agreement by the Contractor. 7.   This Agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 8.   The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the TBR under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the TBR or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 9.   The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Tennessee Board of Regents. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 10.  The Contractor shall submit to the TBR periodic progress reports if requested by the TBR. 11.  This Agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or designee, and the Chancellor or designee for the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 12.  Payment to the Contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be in the amount of actual cost or per diem, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the Tennessee Board of Regents policies, as they may be from time to time amended. 13.  Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference as Attachment A. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. 14. Voluntary Buyout Program. The Contractor acknowledges and understands that, for a period of two years beginning August 16, 2008, restrictions are imposed on former state employees who received a State of Tennessee Voluntary Buyout Program (VBP) severance payment with regard to contracts with state agencies that participated in the VBP. a.   The State will not contract with either a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or an entity in which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or the spouse of such an individual holds a controlling financial interest. b.   The State may contract with an entity with which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment is an employee or an independent contractor. Nothwithstanding the foregoing, the Contractor understands and agrees that there may be unique business circumstances under which a return to work by a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment as an employee or an independent contractor of a State contractor would not be appropriate, and in such cases the State may refuse Contractor personnel. Inasmuch, it shall be the responsibility of the State to review Contractor personnel to identify any such issues. c. With reference to either subsection a. or b. above, a Contractor may a written request for a waiver of the VBP restrictions regarding a former state employee and a contract with a state agency that participated in the VBP. Any such request must be submitted to the State in the form of the VBP Contracting Restriction Waiver Request format available from the State and the Internet at: www.state.tn.us/finance/rds/ocr/waiver.html. The determination on such a request shall be at the sole discretion of the head of the state agency that is a Party to this Contract, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration, and the Commissioner of Human Resources. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. Tennessee Technology University BY: rancis Otuonye, Ph.D. TITLE^SSOC" VP f°r Research/Graduate Studies DATE:    S'lll[bcl______________ Tennessee Board of Regents BY: TITLE:                         j DATE:   S ~^7    _______</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8FBEF412-FBEA-43AC-825C-E5D609927EDF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1750</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1756</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode36AFFF32-9D84-4BF8-8C50-CAB16C3EEEA6"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode86009C63-5507-4100-AF2E-FF9FAEC53FB3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1750</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1751</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode36AFFF32-9D84-4BF8-8C50-CAB16C3EEEA6"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode09A8D367-7747-471E-B28B-600C88F22BC5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1751</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1756</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode36AFFF32-9D84-4BF8-8C50-CAB16C3EEEA6"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">8000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF32967AF-97DC-4CE9-96A9-1762C44EC1AE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2620</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2621</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode98F452E0-FADD-4335-8459-87D3F59B902F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode75D3DA19-B1D4-466F-A9B2-D2156D234DA9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2620</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2626</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode98F452E0-FADD-4335-8459-87D3F59B902F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode681A3220-8277-4876-BA5B-BD8A52498983">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2621</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2626</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode98F452E0-FADD-4335-8459-87D3F59B902F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4596229F-C6F5-4698-91A8-71BDF5FB4BE7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3886</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3894</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3B1D5563-8BD3-4BC3-A2C8-7178AF0ECEA5"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9C2D9300-1210-4999-9C7A-FD0749147F13">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3886</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3887</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3B1D5563-8BD3-4BC3-A2C8-7178AF0ECEA5"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode732F86A2-874C-48E3-9856-465C8481EB22">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3888</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3894</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3B1D5563-8BD3-4BC3-A2C8-7178AF0ECEA5"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">30000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>