<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369974" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode521807F6-55F4-41A3-B055-0C5BFA04323F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">S US</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">30000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode6A4E87FF-E271-473E-A4F8-9C6A136A2A6A">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">dollars</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">30000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeDF4C513D-94AA-4A23-B915-B4E5483011AF">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Memorandum of Agreement for the International Business Leadership Experience (IBLE) Program between Middle Tennessee State University and Chung Yuan Christian University Purpose The College of Business of Chung Yuan Christian University and the Jennings A. Jones College of Business at Middle Tennessee State University hereby agree to achieve the common goals of enhancing the program’s participating students’ foreign language skills, international perspective, and international business understanding by doing the following things: 1. promoting the collaborative study among the participating students; 2. enhancing collaborative business experience by encouraging research; 3. recognizing international business practices for the participating students by field trips; and, 4. providing the program in English to enhance the English language capabilities of the participating students from Chung Yuan Christian University. Program Implementation for MTSU Students at CYCU Up to fifteen MTSU students may come annually to CYCU for a three week study led by an MTSU professor. CYCU will provide classroom and living facilities for the students and the professor at no cost to the students or professor. MTSU will be responsible for the academic course content for the MTSU students. The MTSU students and professor will pay their food costs. CYCU will provide: 1.  one or more lectures in English on Chinese culture (3 clock hours); 2.   five field trips to appropriate businesses, industries, and/or factories in northern Taiwan; 3.  two field trips to cultural and scenic sites in northern Taiwan on weekends; 4.  thirty thousand dollars (S30,000 US) annually for scholarships; 5.   technical and administrative assistance; and, 6.  orientation to campus and surrounding community. Parity from Middle Tennessee State University The Jennings A. Jones College of Business at MTSU will provide tuition support for two academic semesters for up to five undergraduate or graduate students from the College of Business of Chung Yuan Christian University to study at MTSU. The five students will pay their tuition to the home institution while studying at MTSU. The quota of students can be accumulated from one year to the other if it cannot be used up in a year. In order to qualify, a student from Chung Yuan Christian University must do the following: 1.  submit an appropriate application for admission to MTSU and receive his/her acceptance; 2.  take the Test of English as a Foreign Language (TOEFL) and achieve a minimum score of 550 (paper based test) or 213 (computerized test) or 80 (internet-based test); and, 3.  enroll in twelve undergraduate semester hours or nine graduate semester hours in a business program each semester during the academic year while studying at MTSU. Students from Chung Yuan Christian University will pay the tuition to their home institution for the two semesters while studying at MTSU and they will pay to MTSU all applicable fees including, but not limited to, the Business fee, the technology fee and the international student fee while they participate in the MTSU academic program. While they are in the United States, it will be necessary for them to purchase MTSU Student Health Insurance. Costs associated with travel, books, materials, and extracurricular activities will be paid by participating CYCU students. They are also responsible for their housing and food costs. If campus housing and meals are desired, prospective students must meet applicable MTSU deadlines. MTSU will send an official transcript to CYCU within eight weeks of the end of the term following an official request made by the student. f j o.......; Student Responsibilities Students participating in the IBLE Program shall abide by all applicable rules and regulations of the home and host university and by all applicable laws, rules and regulations of the home and host countries. In case of violation, either university has the right to terminate the student’s participation in the exchange and the host university has the right to expel the student in question. Non-discrimination No person on the grounds of handicap, race, color, creed, religion, sex, age, veteran status or national origin will be excluded from participation in, or be denied benefits of, or otherwise be subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Agreement. Term The term of this Agreement shall commence on the date of full execution and shall not exceed a period of five (5) years. Cancellation This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other at least ninety (90) days before the effective date of termination. Notices Notices and communications hereunder shall be deemed made if given by registered mail or by reputable international courier service. Notices shall be deemed to have been given on the date shown on the receipt for registered mail or on the date of delivery shown in the business records of the international courier service at the address given below, or such other address as may hereafter be designated by notice in writing to the following contact person: MTSU John W. Cothem Senior Vice President 1301 East Main Street Murfreesboro, Tn 37132 CYCU Wan-Lee Cheng, President Chung Yuan Christian University 200 Chung Pei Rd., Chung-Li 32023 Taiwan (R.O.C.) Liaisons The following are contacts for the program of study under this Agreement: MTSU Wen Jang Jih Professor, Computer Information Systems Box 45 Murfreesboro, Tn 37132 CYCU Chien-Song Chyang, Vice President Chung Yuan Christian University 200 Chung Pei Rd., Chung-Li 32023 Taiwan (R.O.C.) The following are contacts for student application and admission process under this Agreement: The following are contacts for student application and admission process under this Agreement: MTSU Rhonda Waller, Director MT Abroad Middle Tennessee State University Box 127 Murfreesboro, Tn 37132 CYCU Jyhtong Teng, Director of International Affairs Chung Yuan Christian University 200 Chung Pei Rd., Chung-Li 32023 Taiwan (R.O.C.) Indemnification Neither party shall be responsible for personal injury or property damage or other loss except that resulting from its own negligence or the negligence of its employees or others for whom the party is legally responsible. Nothing in this Agreement shall be construed as creating an obligation to indemnify the other party against that party’s own negligence. Governing Law and Jurisdiction This Agreement shall be governed as to the formation, interpretation, and validity thereof by the laws of the State of Tennessee, without regard to the principles of conflicts of laws. Any and all claims against MTSU for personal injury or property damage resulting from the negligence of MTSU in performing any responsibilities specifically required under the terms of the Agreement shall be submitted to the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee. Damages recoverable against MTSU shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Claims Commission pursuant to T.C.A. Section 9-8-301, et seq. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, each of the parties, by its duly authorized representative, has entered into this agreement as of the date of the effective date. •Sulney A. McPhee, Middle Tennessee State University Date Date APPROVED Date</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF16E4AC3-2B8F-455E-9DC1-3DB42DA9A626">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1619</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1642</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6A4E87FF-E271-473E-A4F8-9C6A136A2A6A"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode530E72C8-4C80-424C-80D0-E56BE75BB552">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1619</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1634</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6A4E87FF-E271-473E-A4F8-9C6A136A2A6A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">30000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBAEF1633-05C5-468E-B63B-50FA34A706B2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1635</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1642</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6A4E87FF-E271-473E-A4F8-9C6A136A2A6A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">dollars</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCEEF92D5-10CF-4574-90B1-5AAFCFE66B9D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1644</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1645</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode521807F6-55F4-41A3-B055-0C5BFA04323F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">S US</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode880FE6A9-9F41-4E49-A751-43FAF4E21020">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1644</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1654</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode521807F6-55F4-41A3-B055-0C5BFA04323F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode06A9C2C5-F149-4630-8B0B-DC44F73A3BBB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1645</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1651</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode521807F6-55F4-41A3-B055-0C5BFA04323F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">30000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5712D04E-A9D6-4631-BEC4-DBAEF503B217">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1652</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1654</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode521807F6-55F4-41A3-B055-0C5BFA04323F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">S US</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>