<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369899" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0912AFD-CFD6-4124-882E-6545AD8413EA">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">7500</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode462772AD-22DF-4FB7-8EF4-6A352C725756">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">) 0 3^15 AGREEMENT BETWEEN THE UNIVERSITY OF TENNESEE AND TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGY CENTER AT JACKSON This agreement, by and between The University of Tennessee, acting through its Martin campus, hereinafter referred to as UTM or University, and Tennessee Technology Center at Jackson, hereinafter referred to as TTCJ. Witnesseth'. In consideration of the mutual promises contained herein and the Statement of Understanding, Attachment 1, herewith that terminates the prior contract, the parties have agreed to and do hereby enter into this agreement according to the provisions established herein for UTM to offer selected courses on the TTCJ campus. 1.  TTCJ will: a.  Provide UTM the use of approximately three classrooms per semester with adequate secure storage space for mobile technology and equipment in support of classroom instruction. b.  Provide the classrooms on weeknights, Monday through Thursday, 3:30-10pm each fall, spring, and summer semesters. The three classroom space requirements are as follows: 1) The interactive video classroom (25 student capacity). 2) The TTC conference room (15 student capacity), when available, or another classroom with minimum 15 student capacity. 3) A classroom that will accommodate a minimum of 25 students. c.  Invoice UTM for two semi-annual payments no later than three weeks after the beginning of each UTM fall and spring academic semesters. Each semi-annual invoice will be $2,500 for a maximum annual combined invoice amount not to exceed $5,000. d.  Provide UTM the use of copier and printing services at existing TTCJ rates, if needed or available. TTC agrees to submit original itemized invoices to UTM, no more often than monthly, for these usages and services, if required. 2. UTM will: a.  Provide semi-annual payments to TTCJ no later than thirty days after receipt of an original invoice. Each semi-annual payment will be $2,500. Maximum payment for UTM’s combined fall, spring, and summer administrative/classroom space usage of TTCJ facilities will not exceed $5,000. b. Provide TTCJ with spring semester classroom academic space needs by November 1, annually. Provide TTCJ fall and summer classroom space needs by March 30, annually. c.  Provide necessary equipment in support of academic requirements for all UTM degree programs. 3. Classroom space made available at TCCJ to UTM is subject to the needs of the Tennessee Board of Regents’ (TBR) institutions, which will have priority over UTM in requesting space. Space needs will be projected on an academic year basis. Tennessee Board of Regents’ institutions will have an obligation of requesting academic year space by May 1, annually. Summer school needs will be treated separately. Tennessee Board of Regents’ institutions will have an obligation of requesting summer space needs by March 15, annually. In the event TTCJ is unable to provide UTM classroom space needs due to TBR ATTACHMENT 1 STATEMENT OF UNDERSTANDING Between UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE MARTIN And TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGY CENTER AT JACKSON WHEREAS, the Tennessee Technology Center at Jackson (TTCJ) has provided the University of Tennessee at Martin (UTM) substantial office space, classrooms, and support services in accordance with UTM Contract #95586/Tennessee Board of Regents Contract #100036, WHEREAS, the University of Tennessee at Martin is moving its primary operation to Jackson State Community College in January 2008 and will vacate the office space and reduce the need for classroom space and other services at TTCJ, WHEREAS, the Tennessee Technology Center at Jackson would like to regain the use of office space and classroom space currently contracted to UTM, WHEREAS, the University of Tennessee at Martin desires to offer only select classes at the Tennessee Technology Center at Jackson, IT IS MUTUALLY AGREED that UTM Contract #95586/TBR Contract #100036 be terminated, effective December 31, 2007, and this agreement hereto attached be executed to clearly outline the relationship and responsibilities of each party. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signature: Date: FEB 2 5 2008 institutions’ needs, UTM has the option to terminate the agreement at the completion of the ongoing semester, without further payment due to TTCJ. 4.  Each user is responsible for paying their respective line charges, and abiding by existing UT/TBR distance learning usage policies. 5. All items purchased by UTM will remain the property of UTM. 6. This agreement becomes effective January I, 2008 through July 2, 2009. It may be terminated at any time by mutual consent, or by either party upon one year prior notice. In the event this agreement is terminated during a semester, ongoing UTM courses will be allowed to continue until completed, and all other stipulations of this agreement will remain in effect until all services and payments are completed by both parties. 7.  Since this agreement is for a term extending beyond a single fiscal year of the University, in the event the University does not receive appropriate funds for the payment required under this agreement of any fiscal period, this agreement shall be deemed terminated at such time at no penalty to the University. 8. In no event shall the maximum liability of the University exceed $7,500. 9. TTCJ and UTM will each maintain documentation for all charges against the other under this contract. The books, records and documents of each, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained in accordance with generally accepted principles of accounting for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice, by the other, or their duly appointed representatives. 10. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto, and supersedes all previous agreements between UTM and TTCJ. 11. No person will be excluded from participation in, or be denied benefits of, or otherwise be subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Agreement, or in the employment practices of TTCJ on the ground of handicap, race, color, religion, sex, or national origin. 12. TTCJ and UTM are self-insured under the provisions of the Tennessee Claims Commission Act, T.C.A. Sections 9-8-301, et scq.. and UTM’s liability to TTCJ, and to third parties, for the negligence of UTM and its employees is subject to the provisions of that Act. Accordingly, any liability of UTM for any damages, losses, or costs arising out of, or related to, acts performed by UTM under this agreement is y the provisions of said Act. Charles M. ?accole Vice Pres. &amp; Treasurer Director, lennessee 1 ecnnology Center at Jackson Date ----\ -- Vice Chancellor, Tennessee'Board ot4xegents Revised December 20. 2007 x           - &lt;=&gt; 7 Date</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEE369A6E-C4D7-4571-9F1B-041184249A47">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5297</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5303</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0912AFD-CFD6-4124-882E-6545AD8413EA"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6390F8A0-C056-4A5F-AFBE-26F83954848A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5297</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5298</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0912AFD-CFD6-4124-882E-6545AD8413EA"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode76D1F96D-CB9A-47DF-BCE6-54F35524C0A1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5298</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5303</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0912AFD-CFD6-4124-882E-6545AD8413EA"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">7500</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>