<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369911" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE5E4021A-47A1-49F0-9876-CE7913FCBB07">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">dollars</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4150</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode5481DE1F-8F98-427E-9E46-A97384C86040">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4150</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode2BB6FB51-C86D-4124-832D-1089666CBE82">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4150</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode5586E7CA-AFB7-49F5-A1D2-3F840EDB5C50">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">CONTRACT BETWEEN, TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS AND UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH AUSTRALIA This Contract, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as the “Board” and University of South Australia , hereinafter referred to as the “Contractor,” is for the provision of a Quality Assessment Review of the Office of System-wide Internal Audit, as further defined in the "SCOPE OF SERVICES." The Contractor is a body corporate pursuant to the University of South Australia Act. The Contractor’s registered address is: North Terrace, Adelaide, South Australia, Australia A. SCOPE OF SERVICES: The Contractor will perform a Quality Assessment Review (QAR) of the Tennessee Board of Regents, Office of System-wide Internal Audit, and a sample of Board institutions’ offices of Internal Audit. The objectives of the review are to assess the internal audit activity’s conformance with the Institute of Internal Auditor’s International Standards for the Professional Practice of Internal Auditing, evaluate the internal audit activity’s effectiveness in carrying out its mission as set forth in its charter and identify opportunities to enhance its management and work processes, as well as its value to the Board. The review will be a validation review of the system's quality self-assessment performed using the Institute of Internal Auditor’s Quality Assessment Manual. B. CONTRACT TERM: This Contract shall be effective for the period commencing on April 28, 2008 and ending on September 15, 2008. The Board shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. C. PAYMENT TERMS AMD CONDITIONS: C.1. Maximum Liability. In no event shall the maximum liability of the Board under this Contract exceed four thousand, one hundred fifty dollars ($4,150). The Service Rates in Section C.3 include, but are not limited to, all applicable taxes, fees, overheads, and all other direct and indirect costs incurred or to be incurred by the Contractor. The maximum liability represents available funds for payment to the Contractor and does not guarantee payment of any such funds to the Contractor under this Contract unless the Board requests work and the Contractor performs said work. C.2. Compensation Firm. The Service Rates and the Maximum Liability of the Board under this Contract are firm for the duration of the Contract and are not subject to escalation for any reason unless amended. C.3. Payment Methodology. The Contractor shall be compensated based on the Service Rates herein for units of service authorized by the Board in a total amount not to exceed the Contract Maximum Liability established in Section C.1. The Contractor’s compensation shall be contingent upon the satisfactory completion of units of service or project milestones defined in Section A. The Contractor shall be compensated based upon the following Service Rates: SERVICE UNIT/MILESTONE                            AMOUNT Completion of QAR and Validation Report                          $4,150.00 The Contractor shall submit an invoice, in form and substance acceptable to the Board with all of the necessary supporting documentation when services are completed. C.4. Travel Compensation. The Contractor shall not be compensated or reimbursed for the direct cost of travel, meals, and lodging. C.5. Payment of Invoice. The payment of an invoice by the Board shall not prejudice the Board's right to object to or question any invoice or matter in relation thereto. D. STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS: D.1. Required Approvals. The Board is not bound bv this Contract until it is approved bv the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee Institution laws and regulations. D.2. Modification and Amendment. This Contract mav be modified onlv bv a written amendment executed bv all parties hereto and approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee Institution laws and regulations. D.3. Ethnicity. This Contract shall not be executed until the Contractor has completed the Minority/Ethnicity Form. D.4. Termination for Convenience. The Board mav terminate this Contract without cause for anv reason. Said termination shall not be deemed a Breach of Contract by the Board. The Board shall give the Contractor at least 30 days written notice before the effective termination date. The Contractor shall be entitled to receive compensation for satisfactory, authorized service completed as of the termination date, but in no event shall the Board be liable to the Contractor for compensation for any service which has not been rendered. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to any actual general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. D.5. Termination for Cause. If the Contractor fails to prooerlv perform its obliqations under this Contract in a timely or proper manner, or if the Contractor violates any terms of this Contract, the Board shall have the right to immediately terminate the Contract and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for completed services. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the Board for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Contract by the Contractor. D.6. Conflicts of Interest. The Contractor warrants that no part of the total Contract Amount shall be paid directly or indirectly to an employee or official of the State of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as an officer, agent, employee, subcontractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this Contract. D.7. Nondiscrimination. The Contractor herebv aqrees. warrants, and assures that no person shall be excluded from participation in, be denied benefits of, or be otherwise subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Contract or in the employment practices of the Contractor on the grounds of disability, age, race, color, religion, sex, veteran status, national origin, or any other classification protected by Federal, or Tennessee constitutional or statutory law. The Contractor shall, upon request, show proof of such nondiscrimination and shall post in conspicuous places, available to all employees and applicants, notices of nondiscrimination. D.8. Records. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Board under this Contract. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this contract, shall be maintained for a period of not less than three (3) full years from the date of the final payment and shall be subject to audit at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice by the Board, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. D.9. Monitoring. The Contractor's activities conducted and records maintained pursuant to this Contract shall be subject to monitoring and evaluation by the Board, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. D.10. Proqress Reports. The Contractor shall submit a report at the conclusion of the review. D.11. Strict Performance. Failure bv anv partv to this Contract to insist in anv one or more cases upon the strict performance of any of the terms, covenants, conditions, or provisions of this Contract shall not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of any such term, covenant, condition, or provision. No term or condition of this Contract shall be held to be waived, modified, or deleted except by a written amendment signed by the parties hereto. D.12. Independent Contractor. The parties hereto, in the performance of this Contract, shall not act as employees, partners, joint venturers, or associates of one another. It is expressly acknowledged by the parties hereto that the parties are independent contracting entities and that nothing in this Contract shall be construed to create an employer/employee relationship or to allow either to exercise control or direction over the manner or method by which the other transacts its business affairs or provides its usual services. The employees or agents of one party shall not be deemed or construed to be the employees or agents of the other party for any purpose whatsoever. The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of the Board, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance and to pay all applicable taxes incident to this Contract. D.13. Board Liability. The Board shall have no liability except as specifically provided in this Contract. D.14. Force Maieure. The obligations of the parties to this contract are subiect to prevention bv causes bevond the parties’ control that could not be avoided by the exercise of due care including, but not limited to, acts of God, riots, wars, epidemics or any other similar cause. D.15. Board and Federal Compliance. The Contractor shall comply with all applicable State and Federal laws and regulations, including Board policies and guidelines in the performance of this Contract. D.16. Governinq Law. This Contract shall be aoverned bv and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee. The Contractor agrees that it will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Tennessee Claims Commission in actions that may arise under this Contract. The Contractor acknowledges and agrees that any rights or claims against the Board or its employees hereunder, and any remedies arising therefrom, shall be subject to and limited to those rights and remedies, if any, available under Tennessee Code Annotated, Sections 9-8-101 through 9-8-407. D.17. Completeness. This Contract is complete and contains the entire understandina between the parties relating to the subject matter contained herein, including all the terms and conditions of the parties’ agreement. This Contract supersedes any and all prior understandings, representations, negotiations, and agreements between the parties relating hereto, whether written or oral. D.18. Severability. If any terms and conditions of this Contract are held to be invalid or unenforceable as a matter of law, the other terms and conditions hereof shall not be affected thereby and shall remain in full force and effect. To this end, the terms and conditions of this Contract are declared severable. D.19. Headings. Section headings of this Contract are for reference purposes only and shall not be construed as part of this Contract. E. SPECIAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS: E.1. Communications and Contacts. The Board: Tammy Gourley, Director of System-wide Internal AuditTennessee Board of Regents1415 Murfreesboro Road, Suite 308Nashville, Tennessee 37207 Telephone: (615)366-4407 Facsimile: (615)366-2242 The Contractor: Phillip John Armanas, Manager: Audit and Risk Management University of South Australia Level 2, 101 Currie Street Adelaide, South Australia 5000 Telephone: +61 883021799 Facsimile: +61 883021053 All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications shall be sent in a manner that verifies proof of delivery. Any communication by facsimile transmission shall also be sent by United States mail or Australian Post on the same date of the facsimile transmission. All communications which relate to any changes to the contract shall not be considered effective until agreed to, in writing, by both parties. E.2. Subject to Funds Availability. The Contract is subject to the appropriation and availability of Board. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, the Board reserves the right to terminate the Contract upon written notice to the Contractor. Said termination shall not be deemed a breach of Contract by the Board. Upon receipt of the written notice, the Contractor shall cease all work associated with the Contract. Should such an event occur, the Contractor shall be entitled to compensation for all satisfactory and authorized services completed as of the termination date. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to recover from the Board any actual, general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. E.3. Breach. A party shall be deemed to have breached the Contract if any of the following, including but not limited to, occurs: — failure to perform in accordance with any term or provision of the Contract; — partial performance of any term or provision of the Contract; — any act prohibited or restricted by the Contract, or — violation of any warranty. For purposes of this Contract, these items shall hereinafter be referred to as a “Breach.” a.      Contractor Breach— Board shall notify Contractor in writing of a Breach. (1) In event of a Breach by Contractor, the Board shall have available the remedy of Actual Damages and any other remedy available at law or equity. b.      Board Breach— In the event of a Breach of contract by the Board, the Contractor shall notify the Board in writing within 30 days of any Breach of contract by the Board. The notice shall contain a description of the Breach. In the event of Breach by the Board, the Contractor may avail itself of any remedy at law in the Claims Commission; provided, however, failure by the Contractor to give the Board written notice and opportunity to cure as described herein operates as a waiver of the Board’s Breach. Failure by the Contractor to file a claim before the appropriate forum in Tennessee with jurisdiction to hear such claim within one (1) year of the written notice of Breach shall operate as a waiver of said claim in its entirety. It is agreed by the parties this provision establishes a contractual period of limitations for any claim brought by the Contractor. E.4. Board Ownership of Work Products. The Board shall have all ownership right, title, and interest, including ownership of copyright, in all work products created, designed, developed, derived, documented, installed, or delivered to the Board under this Contract. The Board shall have unlimited rights to use, disclose, reproduce, or publish, for any purpose whatsoever, all said work products. The Contractor shall furnish such information and data upon request of the Board, in accordance with the Contract and applicable Institution law. E.5. Printing Authorization. The Contractor agrees that no publication coming within the jurisdiction of Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 12-7-101, ef. seq., shall be printed unless a printing authorization number has been obtained and affixed as required by Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 12-7-103 (d). E.6. Board Furnished Property. The Contractor shall be responsible for the correct use, maintenance, and protection of all articles of nonexpendable, tangible, personal property furnished by the Board for the Contractor’s temporary use under this Contract. Upon termination of this Contract, all property furnished shall be returned to the Board in good order and condition as when received, reasonable use and wear thereof excepted. Should the property be destroyed, lost, or stolen, the Contractor shall be responsible to the Board for the residual value of the property at the time of loss. E.7. Incorporation of Additional Documents. Included in this Contract by reference are the following documents: a.     The Contract document and its attachments b.      All Clarifications and addenda In the event of a discrepancy or ambiguity regarding the Contractor’s duties, responsibilities, and performance under this Contract, these documents shall govern in order of precedence detailed above. E.8. Lobbying. The Contractor certifies, to the best of its knowledge and belief, that: No federally appropriated funds have been paid or will be paid, by or on behalf of the Contractor, to any person for influencing or attempting to influence an officer or employee of any agency, a Member of Congress in connection with the awarding of any federal contract, the making of any federal grant, the making of any federal loan, and entering into any cooperative agreement, and the extension, continuation, renewal, amendment, or modification of any federal contract, grant, loan, or cooperative agreement. If any funds other than federally appropriated funds have been paid or will be paid to any person for influencing or attempting to influence an officer or employee of any agency, a Member of Congress, an officer or employee of Congress, or an employee of a Member of Congress in connection with this contract, grant, loan, or cooperative agreement, the Contractor shall complete and submit Standard Form-LLL, “Disclosure Form to Report Lobbying," in accordance with its instructions. The Contractor shall require that the language of this certification be included in the award documents for all sub-awards at all tiers (including sub-grants, subcontracts, and contracts under grants, loans, and cooperative agreements) and that all sub-recipients of federally appropriated funds shall certify and disclose accordingly. E.9. Prohibited Advertising. The Contractor shall not refer to this Contract or the Contractor’s relationship with the Board hereunder in commercial advertising in such a manner as to state or imply that the Contractor or the Contractor's services are endorsed. E.10. Indemnity. The Contractor agrees to indemnify the Board as well as its officers, agents, and employees from and against any and all claims, liabilities, losses, and causes of action which may arise, accrue, or result to any person, firm, corporation, or other entity which may be injured or damaged as a result of acts, omissions, or negligence on the part of the Contractor, its employees, or any person acting for or on its or their behalf relating to this Contract. The Contractor further agrees it shall be liable for the reasonable cost of attorneys for the Board in the event such service is necessitated to enforce the terms of this Contract or otherwise enforce the obligations of the Contractor to the Board. In the event of any such suit or claim, the Contractor shall give the Board immediate notice thereof and shall provide all assistance required by the Board in the Board’s defense. The Board shall give the Contractor written notice of any such claim or suit, and the Contractor shall have full right and obligation to conduct the Contractor’s own defense thereof. Nothing contained herein shall be deemed to accord to the Contractor, through its attorney(s), the right to represent the Board in any legal matter, such rights being governed by Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 8-6-106. E.11. Debarment and Suspension. The Contractor certifies, to the best of its knowledge and belief, that it and its principals: a.      are not presently debarred, suspended, proposed for debarment, declared ineligible, or voluntarily excluded from covered transactions by any Federal or Board department or agency; b.      have not within a three (3) year period preceding this Contract been convicted of, or had a civil judgment rendered against them from commission of fraud, or a criminal offence in connection with obtaining attempting to obtain, or performing a public (Federal, State, or Local) transaction or grant under a public transaction; violation of Federal or State antitrust statutes or commission of embezzlement, theft, forgery, bribery, falsification, or destruction of records, making false Statements, or receiving stolen property; c.      are not presently indicted for or otherwise criminally or civilly charged by a government entity (Federal, State, or Local) with commission of any of the offenses detailed in section b. of this certification; and d.      have not within a three (3) year period preceding this Contract had one or more public transactions (Federal, State, or Local) terminated for cause or default. E.13. Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated as Attachment A. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. IN WITNESS WHEREOF: UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH AUSTRALIA: _______________i____^&lt;7-. ■:____*---------■--------------------------------------------------------- Warren Einarson, Director: Planning and Assurance Services Date APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS: Charles W. Manning, Chancellor Date </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEFE4910D-F136-417A-9C54-C1C28072D006">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1774</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1814</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE5E4021A-47A1-49F0-9876-CE7913FCBB07"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5D762CF8-E6D5-4BB8-9C96-AA05FF46B645">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1774</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1806</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE5E4021A-47A1-49F0-9876-CE7913FCBB07"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4150</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF6FCBC6A-E3D5-4C94-9D5F-BDAB9B11873E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1807</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1814</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE5E4021A-47A1-49F0-9876-CE7913FCBB07"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">dollars</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeACCD30C1-DB03-49BF-9A52-B57DD9C12D0D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1816</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1817</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5481DE1F-8F98-427E-9E46-A97384C86040"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1303B4B9-1114-41F3-ABDF-7699D256BBF6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1816</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1822</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5481DE1F-8F98-427E-9E46-A97384C86040"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8BFA54BB-29DC-4392-8FF4-BB38238B02A9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1817</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1822</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5481DE1F-8F98-427E-9E46-A97384C86040"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4150</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC5B40FBA-CAE2-45D9-AB97-F8C22A18BED6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3037</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3038</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2BB6FB51-C86D-4124-832D-1089666CBE82"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9DA0ACA4-B737-40AE-8C34-3AB6AAFE9B55">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3037</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3046</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2BB6FB51-C86D-4124-832D-1089666CBE82"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4DDFDCD6-3CED-46CB-8AB8-179D0C8B9AF3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3038</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3046</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2BB6FB51-C86D-4124-832D-1089666CBE82"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4150</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>