<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369883" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeFE312049-4A45-495B-A65C-D6E4536FD764">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Dollar</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode62E648F0-4145-4DB9-BA09-06E0DE4AC267">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode2BA742DC-283D-4CA5-9DB6-6FFD0733EF2F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">18000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8B27AD57-CE1C-4616-AC6D-F90AC1955DE6">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">11</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeBB730908-5BA7-4E4D-A5D1-FD99B9D40C51">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">INTERDEPARTMENTAL CONTRACT BETWEEN THE TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS AND NASHVILLE STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE This Contract, by and between the TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS, hereinafter referred to as the “TBR” and NASHVILLE STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE, hereinafter referred to as the “Contractor”, is for the provision of student assistants, as further defined in the "SCOPE OF SERVICES." A. SCOPE OF SERVICES: A. 1. THE CONTRACTOR SHALL a.   Provide student resources to augment the Tennessee Board of Regents, Office of Facilities Development. b.   Advise and enroll students in the Cooperative Education program at all times to allow participation in this work plan. c.   Select students at the college to receive work related experiences who are actively engaged in a course of study related to the functions of architecture and building construction or computer science education/business education, and who have at least one year remaining in planned studies. d.   Provide the TBR with quarterly reimbursement requests. e.   Replace students working under this contract at the request of the TBR under the following conditions: (1)   Causes relating to performance of duties. (2)   Causes relating to conduct which may affect a student employee’s ability to successfully fulfill the requirements of his/her assigned job. f.   Provide the TBR with assistance in collecting TBR provided employee identification and/or security cards at such time as the student is no longer a participant under this contract. A. 2.    THE TBR SHALL: a.   Provide students an average of not less than fifteen (15) hours nor more than thirty (30) hours of work per week during the academic year, except with mutual consent with the TBR, Contractor and student. During extended holiday periods and summer vacations, students can work 37.5 hours per week upon approval by the TBR. b.   Provide a written job description including the name of the department where the student is to be assigned, an overview of the job tasks and number of work periods projected on a form. c.   Assist the students in completing a “Cooperative Education Learning Agreement” for each work semester. d.   Maintain and furnish the Contractor TBR pay period student time and attendance information. e.   Submit to the Contractor, each semester, a written evaluation of the student performance on a form supplied by the Contractor. f.    Both parties will endeavor to resolve unforeseen difficulties in the best interest of the TBR, the Contractor and the student. B.  CONTRACT TERM: B.1. Contract Term. This Contract shall be effective for the period commencing on September 15, 2007 and ending on June 30, 2008. The TBR shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. C. PAYMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS: C.1. Maximum Liability. In no event shall the maximum liability of the TBR under this Contract exceed Eighteen Thousand Dollars ($18,000), including up to $500 in travel compensation. This amount shall constitute the maximum compensation due the Contractor for the service and all of the Contractor's obligations hereunder regardless of the difficulty, hours worked, or materials or equipment required. The Contract Amount includes, but is not limited to, all applicable taxes, fees, overhead, profit, and all other direct and indirect costs incurred or to be incurred by the Contractor. C.2. Compensation Firm. The maximum liability of the TBR under this contract is firm for the duration of the Contract and is not subject to escalation for any reason unless amended. C.3. Payment Methodology. The Contractor shall be compensated based on the Unit Rates in a total amount not to exceed the Contract maximum Liability established in Section C.1. The Contractor shall be compensated based upon the following Unit Rate: JOB TITLE                    HOURLY RATE Coop Student                              $11.00 The Contractor shall submit invoices for completed work, in a form and substance acceptable to the TBR with all of the necessary supporting documentation, prior to any payment. Such invoices shall, at a minimum, include the name of each individual, the individual’s job title, the number of hours worked during the period, the hourly rate, the total compensation requested for the individual, and the total amount due the Contractor for the period invoiced. The student worker will be paid One Dollar ($1.00) per hour less than the Contractor Unit Rate. The One Dollar ($1.00) per hour will be used to pay matching FICA, Medicare, and cover administrative costs. C.4. Travel Compensation. Compensation to the Contractor for travel, meals, or lodging shall be in the amount of actual costs, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the "State Comprehensive Travel Regulations," as they are amended from time to time. This amount shall not exceed Five Hundred Dollars ($500.00) during the period of the Contract. C.5. Payment of Invoice. The payment of the invoice by the TBR shall not prejudice the TBR's right to object to or question any invoice or matter in relation thereto. Such payment by the TBR shall neither be construed as acceptance of any part of the work or service provided nor as an approval of any of the amounts invoiced therein. C.6. Invoice Reductions. The Contractor’s invoice shall be subject to reduction for amounts included in any invoice or payment theretofore made which are determined by the TBR, on the basis of audits conducted in accordance with the terms of this contract, not to constitute proper remuneration for compensable services. C. 7.     Deductions. The TBR reserves the right to deduct from amounts which are or shall become due and payable to the Contractor under this or any contract between the parties any amounts which are or shall become due and payable to the TBR by the Contractor. D. STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS: D.1. Required Approvals. The TBR is not bound by this Contract until it is approved by the appropriate State officials in accordance with applicable State laws and regulations. D.2. Modification and Amendment. This Contract may be modified only by a written amendment executed by all parties hereto and approved by the appropriate State officials in accordance with applicable State laws and regulations. D.3. Termination. Either party may terminate this contract upon giving thirty (30) days written notice to the other party. Such termination shall have no effect on students currently enrolled in the cooperative education program. E. SPECIAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS: E.1. Communications and Contacts. All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications required or contemplated by this Contract shall be in writing and shall be made by facsimile transmission, by overnight courier service, or by first class mail, postage prepaid, addressed to the respective party at the appropriate facsimile number or address as set forth below or to such other party, facsimile number, or address as may be hereafter specified by written notice. The TBR: Jerry W. Preston, Executive Director Office of Facilities Development Tennessee Board of Regents 1415 Murfreesboro Road Nashville, TN 37217 Telephone:    615-366-4434         Fax: 615-366-3992 The Contractor: Debra Bauer, Vice President of Finance and Administrative Services Nashville State Technical Community College 120 White Bridge Road, Nashville, TN 37209-4515 Telephone:    615-353-3300         Fax: 615-353-3499 All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications shall be considered effectively given as of the day of receipt. E.2. Subject to Funds Availability: This Contract is subject to the appropriation and availability of State and/or Federal funds. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, the TBR reserves the right to terminate the Contract upon written notice to the Contractor. Upon receipt of the written notice, the Contractor shall cease all work associated with the Contract on or before the effective termination date specified. Should such an event occur, the Contractor shall be entitled to compensation for all satisfactory and authorized services completed as of the effective termination date. IN WITNESS WHEREOF: NASHVILLE STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE: Debra Bauer, Vice President, Finance and Administrative Services Date:        6 ' George H Van Allen, President Date: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS: Charles W. Manning, Chancellorz^Qgp/^ Date:</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeFBEE6994-8925-4323-88BC-4B2AC73FBFEF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2970</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2977</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2BA742DC-283D-4CA5-9DB6-6FFD0733EF2F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode162A4EB1-E560-434B-9225-E8B16F2C79CE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2970</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2971</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2BA742DC-283D-4CA5-9DB6-6FFD0733EF2F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode13855694-7619-4EEB-BAD7-C7049E739265">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2971</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2977</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2BA742DC-283D-4CA5-9DB6-6FFD0733EF2F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">18000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode643F9058-D35C-4224-95F6-13B4DEDED7F8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3943</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3949</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8B27AD57-CE1C-4616-AC6D-F90AC1955DE6"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode228AD3AC-C133-4BC3-8D5A-4959F613D2B4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3943</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3944</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8B27AD57-CE1C-4616-AC6D-F90AC1955DE6"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode486EC579-7B27-4D04-897B-2338EFA1AFAB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3944</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3949</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8B27AD57-CE1C-4616-AC6D-F90AC1955DE6"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">11</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA032C053-A747-4D03-A4DB-8DC2FA04B2AF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4440</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4450</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeFE312049-4A45-495B-A65C-D6E4536FD764"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode12214FAF-7484-4F9E-B030-7998F48D65D0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4440</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4443</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeFE312049-4A45-495B-A65C-D6E4536FD764"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD0456FA1-95AB-4AB4-959F-DBE38766522F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4444</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4450</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeFE312049-4A45-495B-A65C-D6E4536FD764"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Dollar</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3EF55EE8-9AC6-4EBF-BCE4-3933D9438DFE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4452</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4453</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode62E648F0-4145-4DB9-BA09-06E0DE4AC267"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDB67DECF-F46E-40DA-B48F-163A79856B67">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4452</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4457</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode62E648F0-4145-4DB9-BA09-06E0DE4AC267"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6C09947C-C4DD-4413-82CD-600C23976FF3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4453</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4457</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode62E648F0-4145-4DB9-BA09-06E0DE4AC267"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>