<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369834" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4C63B543-F6ED-4691-AAA5-C5A37A6E8B44">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">6000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeBD36825A-5A14-4D29-8505-62CF37AA0B52">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode40E87E4E-2012-492E-82FD-813CF2CF2800">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">CLINICAL AFFILIATION AGREEMENT BETWEEN THE TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS (TBR), on behalf of its 6 universities as listed below AUSTIN PEAY STATE UNIVERSITY EAST TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS AND DIALYSIS CLINIC INC. This Agreement is made this 1st day of September, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as "Institution" and Dialysis Clinic, Inc. hereinafter referred to as "Affiliate". Whereas, it is to the mutual benefit of the parties to provide clinical experience for students enrolled in certain programs of the Institution, the parties have agreed to the terms and provisions set forth below: I.   Purpose - the purpose of this Agreement shall be to provide clinical experience to students enrolled in the Master of Science in Nursing Regents Online Degree Program of the TBR. A.  Consideration for this Agreement shall consist of the mutual promises contained herein, the parties agreeing that monetary compensation shall neither be expected nor received by either party. B.  The clinical experience shall be provided at the Affiliate's Facility located at 100 Academy Street, Dickson, TN 37055 hereinafter referred to as "Facility". C. The specific experience to be provided students is described as follows: Provide clinical experiences for students enrolled in the Master of Science in Nursing Regents Online Degree Program. II.  Terms and Conditions - pursuant to the above-stated purpose, the parties agree as follows: A. Term - the term of this Agreement shall be (from one to five years) commencing September 1, 2006 and ending August 31,2011. to perform services in lieu of staff employees. 8.  The Affiliate shall provide emergency medical treatment to students (and faculty, if applicable) if needed for illness or injuries suffered during clinical experience. Such treatment shall be at the expense of the individual treated. 9.  The Affiliate shall maintain all applicable accreditation requirements and certify such compliance to the Institution or other entity as requested by the Institution. The Affiliate shall also permit authorities responsible for accreditation of the Institution's curriculum to inspect the Affiliate's clinical facilities and services as necessary. 10. The Institution shall provide health records of students (and faculty, if applicable) upon request by the Affiliate. 11. The Institution shall notify the Affiliate if a student (or faculty, if applicable) is/are unable for any reason to report for clinical training. 12. The Affiliate requires written evidence of professional liability insurance coverage from individual students and faculty and staff (if applicable) participating in the experience. The minimum amount of coverage per individual shall be $1,000,000/$6,000,000.. The coverage shall extend through the term of the student's and faculty or staff’s (if applicable) participation. 13. The State of Tennessee is self-insured and does not carry or maintain commercial general liability insurance or medical, professional or hospital liability insurance. Any and all claims against the State of Tennessee, including the Institution or its employees, shall be heard and determined by the Tennessee Claims Commission in the manner prescribed by law. Damages recoverable against the Institution shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Claims Commission pursuant to T.C.A. Section 9-8-301 et seq. E. Mutual responsibilities - the parties shall cooperate to fulfill the following mutual responsibilities: 1. Each party shall comply with all federal, state and municipal laws, advice, rules and regulations which are applicable to the performance of this Agreement, which shall include but not be limited to: HIPAA Requirements: To the extent required by federal law, the parties agree to comply with the Health Insurance Portability and background check done prior to the student’s initial clinical placement if the student maintains continuous enrollment in the health care program and if the results of the background check are archived by the background check agency. Institution shall inform students or faculty/staff members excluded from clinical placement on the basis of a criminal background check of any review or appeal process available pursuant to the Fair Credit Reporting Act or any other law or policy, if any. 3.  Students shall be treated as trainees who have no expectation of receiving compensation or future employment from the Affiliate or the Institution. 4.   Any courtesy appointments to faculty or staff by either the I nstitution or the Affiliate shall be without entitlement of the individual to compensation or benefits from the appointing party. 5.   The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of I972, and Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 6.  The confidentiality of patient records and student records shall be maintained at all times. F. Miscellaneous Terms - The following terms shall apply in the interpretation and performance of this Agreement: 1. Neither party shall be responsible for personal injury or property CLINICAL AFFILIATION AGREEMENT ADDENDUM THIS CLINICAL AFFILIATION AGREEMENT ADDENDUM (this “Addendum”) is entered into as of this 1st day of September, 2006, by and between Dialysis Clinic, Inc., a Tennessee non-profit corporation (“DCI”), and The Tennessee Board of Regents (“TBR”). RECITALS: WHEREAS, DCI and TBR have entered into that certain Clinical Affiliation Agreement, dated as of September 1, 2006 (the “Agreement”), wherein the parties agreed to certain responsibilities and obligations respecting clinical training of TBR’s Master of Science in Nursing Regents Online Degree Program students (each a “Student” and collectively, the “Students”) at DCI’s dialysis clinic located at 100 Academy Street, Dickson, Tennessee 37055 (the “Facility”); and WHEREAS, the parties desire to further define their respective responsibilities and obligations respecting such clinical training; NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration of the foregoing and the mutual covenants set forth below, the parties agree as follows: 1.     TBR shall ensure that the Students have received CPR training and training concerning universal precautions and Blood Borne Pathogens. TBR shall provide proof of this training to DCI. TBR shall further ensure that the Students use universal precautions when they are in the treatment area or in any location in which there is a risk of exposure to patient fluids. 2.     TBR understands and shall inform its students, faculty members, employees and agents of TBR that DCI accepts no responsibility for any injury sustained by any Student, faculty member, employee or agent of TBR while on or about DCI premises. This provision will survive the expiration or earlier termination of the Agreement. 3.     TBR shall ensure that the Students understand that they are not entitled to wages for their activities during the period of affiliation with DCI and are not agents, employees, or representatives of DCI and will not hold themselves out as agents of DCI at any time while they are assigned to train at the Facility. 4.     TBR shall ensure that the Students will only observe the treatment provided by DCI staff and will not provide direct patient care. 5.     The parties recognize that DCI’s information concerning its patients is confidential and that DCI is under an obligation to maintain the confidentiality of such patient information in accordance with Federal and state law. In light of the foregoing, TBR specifically covenants and agrees that, for the purposes of this Addendum, it shall not access, use or disclose any Protected Health Information of DCI other than as permitted under the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (“HIPAA”) and its implementing regulations. As used in this Addendum, “Protected Health Information” means any information, whether oral or recorded in any form or medium: (i) that relates to the past, present or future physical or mental condition of an individual; the provision of health care to an individual; or the past, present or future payment for the provision of health care to an individual, and (ii) that identifies the individual or with respect to which there is a reasonable basis to believe the information can be used to identify the individual, and as further described under 45 C.F.R. § 160.103. 6.     TBR shall notify the Students of their obligation to comply with DCI’s policies and procedures governing the confidentiality of medical records and the use and disclosure of Protected Health Information. Solely for the purpose of defining the Students’ duties and obligations regarding use and disclosure of DCI’s Protected Health Information, the Students shall be considered members of the DCI “workforce”, as that term is defined under 45 C.F.R. § 163.103, when engaged in activities pursuant to the Agreement or this Addendum. However, the Students are not, and shall not for any other purpose be considered, employees or agents of DCI. TBR further agrees that prior to receiving training at DCI, each Student shall be required to sign the Confidentiality Agreement attached hereto as Exhibit A and incorporated herein by reference. 7.     The parties acknowledge that Federal and state laws relating to the privacy and security of patient information are evolving rapidly and that changes to this Agreement may be required to ensure compliance with such developments. The parties specifically agree to take such actions as may be necessary to implement the standards and requirements of HIPAA and other Federal and state laws relating to the security or confidentiality of patient information. 8.     Except as so supplemented and/or amended, the terms of the Agreement shall continue unchanged and shall apply with full force and effect to govern the matters addressed in this Addendum and the Agreement. In the event of any conflict between the terms of this Addendum and the Agreement, the terms of this Addendum shall control. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties hereto have executed this Addendum effective as of the date first set forth above. DIALYSIS CLINIC, INC. James Perry, President, or Ed Attrill, Secretary/Treasurer Date:      / 6? - 6      ____________________ Date Date Student Signature Student Name Printed Witness Signature Witness Name Printed</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEE5448B9-F478-49CD-83DD-DF08AEDD53AE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2854</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2864</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeBD36825A-5A14-4D29-8505-62CF37AA0B52"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9F4C2437-5F5A-45FF-A1BA-764E25617E2A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2854</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2855</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeBD36825A-5A14-4D29-8505-62CF37AA0B52"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD7C7F106-4708-4526-8997-C5E70D884186">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2855</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2864</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeBD36825A-5A14-4D29-8505-62CF37AA0B52"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEC94A97B-A3A9-4715-BE5E-A0405EFA21FA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2865</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2875</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4C63B543-F6ED-4691-AAA5-C5A37A6E8B44"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBD038ED2-508D-479D-99EC-926982440C3E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2865</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2866</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4C63B543-F6ED-4691-AAA5-C5A37A6E8B44"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode68CD08CE-0CC3-4C7D-A88C-32ADBDFA1D1F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2866</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2875</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4C63B543-F6ED-4691-AAA5-C5A37A6E8B44"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">6000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>