<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369755" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8470AF0E-93BB-4CC0-828F-049A3A598421">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">150000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode3C4A72C6-EB1D-4A64-8A0C-7B701FBFF770">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Areawide Public Utility Contract For Electric, Energy Management Services, and Services Provided under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority Contract No. GS-00P-16-BSD-1205 between the United States of America and COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY Franchised areas in the Chicago, Illinois metropolitan area and Northern Illinois Negotiated Areawide Contract No. GS-00P-16-BSD-1205 between the United States of America And COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY TABLE OF CONTENTS Article Page Preamble and Whereas Clauses 3 1. Definitions 3 2. Scope and Duration of Contract 6 3. Existing Contracts 6 4 Authorization Procedure and Service Disconnections 6 5. Rates, Charges, and Public Regulation 7 6. Bills and Billing Data 8 7. Payments for Services 8 8. Contractor-Owned Meters 8 9. Equipment and Facilities 9 10. Liability 9 11. Access to Premises 10 12. Parties of Interest 10 13. Representations and Certifications 10 14. Supplemental Clauses 11 15. Small Business Subcontracting Plan 15 16. Notices 16 17. Reporting 16 18. Utility Energy Services Contracts 16 19. Miscellaneous 18 Signatures 19 Certificate 20 Authorization for Electric Service Exhibit A Authorization for Energy Management Service Exhibit B Authorization for Services Provided under the Appropriate  Regulatory Authority Exhibit C NEGOTIATED AREAWIDE CONTRACT No. GS-00P-16-BSD-1205 BETWEEN THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA AND COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY THIS AREA WIDE CONTRACT FOR Electric, Energy Management Services and Services Provided Under The Appropriate Regulatory Authority is executed this 5th day of February, 2016, between the UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, acting through the Administrator of General Services (hereinafter referred to as the "Government"! pursuant to the authority contained in Section 201(a) of the Federal Property and Administrative Services Act of 1949, as amended, 40 U.S.C. 501(b)(1), and, COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY, a corporation organized and existing under the laws of the Slate of Illinois, and having its principal office and place of business at One Financial Place, 440 S. LaSalle Street - 33rd Floor, Chicago, Illinois 60605 (hereinafter referred to as the "Contractor"): WHEREAS, the Contractor is an electric utility company that is regulated by the Illinois Commerce Commission and the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (hereinafter referred to collectively as the “Commission”); WHEREAS, the Contractor now has on file with the Commission all of its effective tariffs, rate schedules, riders, rules and regulatory terms and conditions of service, as applicable; and WHEREAS, with some exceptions, the Government is generally required by Chapter 1 of Title 48 of the Federal Acquisition Regulation (FAR), 48 CFR 41,204, to enter into a bilateral contract for Electric, Energy Management Services and/or Services Provided Under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority at each Federal facility where the value of the Services provided is expected to exceed $ 150,000 annually; and WHEREAS, where the Government has an areawide contract in effect with a particular utility, then such service is normally to be procured thereunder; and WHEREAS, the Government is now purchasing such electric and energy management services from the Contractor under the Areawide Public Utilities Contract No. GS-OOP-05-BSD-0361 that expires on January 10,2016, or under some other service arrangement; and WHEREAS, the Contractor and the Government mutually desire that this Areawide Contract be used by the agencies of the Government in obtaining electric, energy management services and/or services provided under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority from the Contractor and to facilitate partnering arrangements as encouraged and authorized by 10 U.S.C, 2911-2918 and 42 U.S.C. 8256; and NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration of the premises and mutual covenants herein contained, the parties hereby agree as follows: ARTICLE 1. DEFINITIONS. 1.1. As used in this Aieawide Contract, the following terms have the meaning as prescribed below: (a) 11 Areawide Contract" means this master contract entered into between the Government and Contractor to cover the Service acquisitions of all Federal agencies in the franchised certificated service territory from Contractor for a period not to exceed ten (10) years. (b) "Agency" means any Federal department, agency, or independent establishment in the executive branch of the Government, any establishment in the legislative or judicial branches of the Federal Government, or any wholly/mixed ownership Government corporation, as defined in the Government Corporation Control Act, a list of which Agencies may be found at ADM 4800.2E on the General Services Administration website. (c) "Ordering Agency" means any Agency that enters into a bilaterally executed Authorization for procurement of Electric and/or Services Provided under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority, or otherwise is authorized to and obtains Services under this Areawide Contract. (d) "Authorization" means an order form used to acquire Services under this Areawide Contract (see Exhibit "A" AUTHORIZATION FOR ELECTRIC SERVICE, Exhibit «B” AUTHORIZAION for ENERGY MANAGEMENT SERVCE AND Exhibit "C" AUTHORIZATION FOR THE PROVISION OF SERVICES PROVIDED UNDER THE APPROPRIATE REGULATORY AUTHORITY AND annexed hereto; (e) "Termination Authorization" means an order form used to discontinue or disconnect Services under this Areawide Contract (see Exhibit "A" AUTHORIZATION FOR ELECTRIC SERVICE, Exhibit “B” AUTHORIZAION for ENERGY MANAGEMENT SERVCE AND Exhibit "C" AUTHORIZATION FOR THE PROVISION OF SERVICES PROVIDED UNDER THE APPROPRIATE REGULATORY AUTHORITY AND); (f) "Servients!" means Electric Service, Energy Management Services, ECM, and/or Services Provided Under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority that are generally available from the Contractor pursuant to Contractor’s Tariffs or the Contractor's Terms and Conditions, whichever is applicable. (g) "Electric Service" means regulated electric commodities, transmission, distribution, and/or related services. (h) “Energy Conservation Measure (ECM)” means any specific energy related or waler service intended to provide energy savings and/or demand reduction in Federal facilities (Reference Article 18 herein). (i) "Energy Management Service (EMS)" means any project or service (including any ECM)lhat is intended to reduce and/or manage energy demand or water use in a facility as well as energy audits and any ancillary services necessary to ensure the proper operation of the energy conservation measure. Such measures include, but are not limited to, operating and maintenance and commissioning services (Energy Conservation Measure and Demand Side Management Measure are considered equivalent terms.) To be considered an EMS measure, the measure must satisfy all of the following requirements: 1. The EMS measure must produce measurable energy reductions or measurable amounts of controlled energy and/or water use; 2. The EMS measure must be directly related to the use of energy or directly control the use of energy or water; 3. The preponderance of work covered by the EMS measure (measured in dollars) must be for items 1 and 2 above; and 4. The EMS measure must be an improvement to real property or any action that is necessary to ensure the functionality of the EMS measure. (j) “Contractor’s Tariffs” means utility service tariffs, and includes rate schedules, riders, rules, regulations, and regulated terms and conditions of service as may be modified, amended or supplemented by the Contractor from time to time and, approved by the Commission, (k) "Contractor's Terms and Conditions" for this Areawide Contract, means the terms, conditions, policies, procedures, payment terms and prices established by the Contractor for those services that are provided pursuant to this Contract, and as such, may be modified, amended, or supplemented by (he Contractor from time to time, but are not required to be approved by the Commission and/or not specifically subject to Commission approval before they take effect. (l) "Connection Charge" means a Contractor’s charge for facilities on the Contractor’s side of the delivery point which facilities (1) are required to make connections with the nearest point of supply and (2) are in accordance with the Contractor’s Tariffs and the Commission’s rules and regulations, installed, owned, maintained and operated by the Contractor. (m) "Class of Service" or "Service Classification" means those categories of service established in the Contractor’s Tariff as filed with the Commission. (n) “Extension Fee” means a Contractor’s charge for facilities on the Contrator’s side of the delivery point which facilities (1) are required to make connections with the nearest point of supply and (2) are, in accordance with the Terms of Service, installed, owned, maintained and operated by the Contractor. (o) “Hazardous Materials” means i.    those substances defined as "hazardous substances" pursuant to Section 101(14) of the Comprehensive Environmental Response, Compensation and Liability Act of 1980, as amended by the Superfund Amendments and Re authorization Act of 1986 (42 U.S.C. Sections 9601 et seq.); ii.    those substances designated as a “hazardous substance” pursuant to Section 311(b)(2)(A) or as a "toxic pollutant” pursuant to Section 307(a)(1) of the Clean Water Act (33 U.S.C. Sections 1251 et seq.); iii.    those substances defined as “hazardous materials” pursuant to Section 103 of the Hazardous Materials Transportation Act (49 U.S.C. Sections 1801 et seq.); iv.    those substances regulated as a “chemical substance or mixture” or as an “imminently hazardous chemical substance or mixture” pursuant to Section 6 or 7 of the Toxic Substances Control Act (15 U.S.C. Sections 2601 etseq.); v.    those substances defined as “contaminants” pursuant to Section 1401 of the Safe Drinking Water Act (42 U.S.C. Sections 300f et seq.), if present in excess of permissible levels; vi.    those substances regulated pursuant to the Oil Pollution Act of 1990 (33 U.S.C. Sections 2701 et seq.); vii.    those substances defined as a “pesticide” pursuant to Section 2(u) of the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act as amended by the Federal Environmental Pesticide Control Act of 1972 and by the Federal Pesticide Act of 1978 (7 U.S.C. Sections 136 et seq.); viii.    those substances defined as a “source”, "special nuclear” or “by-product” material pursuant to Section 11 of the Atomic Energy Act of 1954 (42 U.S.C. Section 2014 et seq.); ix.    those substances defined as “residual radioactive material” in Section 101 of the Uranium Mill Tailings Radiation Control Act of 1978 (42 U.S.C. Sections 7901 et seq.); x.    those substances defined as “toxic materials” or “harmful physical agents” pursuant to Section 6 of the Occupational Safety and Health Act (29 U.S.C. Section 651 et seq.); xi.    those substances defined as “hazardeus air pollutants” pursuant to Section 112(a)(6), or “regulated substance” pursuant to Section 112(a)(2)(B) of the Clean Air Act (42 U.S.C. Sections 7401 et seq.); xii.    those substances defined as “extremely hazardous substances” pursuant to Section 302(a)(2) of the Emergency Planning &amp; Community Right-to-Know Act of 1986 (42 U.S.C. Sections 11001 et seq.); xiii.    those other hazardous substances, toxic pollutants, hazardous materials, chemical substances or mixtures, imminently hazardous chemical substances or mixtures, contaminants, pesticides, source materials, special nuclear materials, by-product materials, residual radioactive materials, toxic materials, harmful physical agents, air pollutants, regulated substances, or extremely hazardous substances defined in any regulations promulgated pursuant to any environmental Law, and xiv.    all other contaminants, toxins, pollutants, hazardous substances, substances, materials and contaminants, polluted, toxic and hazardous materials, the use, disposition, possession or control of which is regulated by one or more Laws. (p)  "Hazardous Wastes” means those substances defined as “hazardous waste” pursuant to Section 1004(5) of the Resource, Conservation and Recovery Act (42 U.S.C. Section 6901 et seq.), and those other hazardous wastes defined in any regulations promulgated pursuant to any environmental Law. (q) UESC means a Utility Energy Service Contract, as authorized by the Energy Policy Act of 1992, P.L. 102-486 (codified as 42 U.S.C. 8256) as an established-source contract between a federal agency and its serving utility for energy- and water-efficiency improvements and demand-reduction services. 1.2. This Article is hereby expanded to include the additional definitions contained in FAR Clause 52.202-1, Definitions (MAY 2001), 48 C.F.R. 52.202-1, which are incorporated herein by reference. ARTICLE 2. SCOPE AND DURATION OF CONTRACT.  2.1. This Arcawidc Contract shall be in effect on and after the 5lh day of February, 2016 (“Effective Date”), and shall continue for a period of ten (10) years (“Term”), except that the Government, pursuant to the clause contained in FAR 52.249-2 (48 C.F.R. 52.249-2), incorporated into this Areawide Contract under Article 14.1-34, or the Contractor, upon sixty (60) days written notice to the Government, and without liability to the Government or any Ordering Agency, may terminate this Areawide Contract, in whole or in part, when it is in their respective interest to do so, provided, however, that neither the stated duration of this Areawide Contract nor any other termination of it, in whole or in part, pursuant to such incorporated clause, this Article 2.1, or otherwise, shall be construed to affect any obligation for any payment, charge, rate, or other matter that may be imposed pursuant to the Contractor’s Tariffs, rates, rules, regulations, riders, practices, or terms and conditions of Service as may be modified, amended, or supplemented by the Contractor and approved from time to time by the Commission. 2.2. Authorizations may be executed under this Areawide Public Utility Contract at any time during the term of this Contract. The Areawide Public Utility Contract shall be for a term of ten (10) years. The term of any Authorization executed under this contract may be for a term of up to ten (10) years, which term may extend beyond the term of this Areawide Public Utility Contract. Authorizations executed pursuant to the authority under 42 U.S.C. Section 8256 may be for a term of up to 25 years, as long as the other requirements of this Section are met, and the term may extend beyond the term of the Areawide Public Utility Contract. Termination, modification or expiration of the Areawide Public Utility Contract shall not affect in any way any Authorizations previously entered into under this Contract. 2.3. The provisions of this Area wide Contract shall not apply to the Contractor's Service to any Agency until both the Ordering Agency and the Contractor execute a written Authorization for Electric, Energy Management Services and/or Services provided under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority. Upon bilateral execution of an Authorization, the Contractor agrees to furnish to the Ordering Agency, and the Ordering Agency agrees to purchase from the Contractor, the above noted Services for the installation^) or facilities named in the Authorization pursuant to the terms of this Areawide Contract. 2.4. Nothing in this Areawide Contract shall be construed as precluding the Ordering Agency and the Contractor from entering into an Authorization for negotiated rates or Service of a special nature, provided such negotiated rates or Service are in accordance with the rules and regulations of the Commission, if applicable. 2.5. This Areawide Contract may be used by an Ordering Agency to obtain electric services that are offered by Contractor, as further described in 40 U.S.C. Section 591, to the extent it is applicable, (quoted here in relevant part): “A department, agency, or instrumentality of the Federal Government may not use amounts appropriated or made available by any law to purchase electricity in a manner inconsistent with State law governing the provision of electric utility service...”. 2.6. To facilitate an Ordering Agency obtaining services under Contractor's standard agreements for utility service, an Exhibit “C” has been included in this Areawide Contract. This Exhibit “C” is designed so it also can be used by an Ordering Agency when a change requested by the Ordering Agency to Contractor’s standard terms and conditions for utility service has been approved by the Appropriate Regulatory Authority. ARTICLE 3. EXISTING CONTRACTS. 3.1. The parties agree that an Agency currently acquiring Service from the Contractor under a separate written contract may continue to do so until that contract expires or until such lime as the Agency and the Contractor mutually agree to terminate that separate written contract and have such Service provided pursuant to this Areawide Contract by executing an appropriate Authorization or Authorizations. 3.2. Existing special rates and services of a special nature currently provided under a separate written contract may be continued under the Authorizations described in Article 3.1 if requested by the Ordering Agency and agreed upon by the Contractor. ARTICLE 4. AUTHORIZATION PROCEDURE AND SERVICE DISCONNECTION. 4.1. To obtain or change Service under this Areawide Contract, the Ordering Agency shall complete the appropriate Authorization and forward it to the Contractor. Upon the request of the Ordering Agency, the Contractor shall endeavor to provide reasonable assistance to the Ordering Agency in selecting the service classification which may be most favorable to the Ordering Agency. Upon execution of an Authorization by both the Contractor and the Ordering Agency, the dale of initiation or change in Service shall be effective as of the date specified in the Authorization. An executed copy of the Authorization shall be transmitted by the Ordering Agency to GSA at the address provided in Article 16.1. 4.2. During the Term of this Areawide Contract, effective Authorizations need not be amended, modified, or changed by an Ordering Agency to reflect changes in: accounting and appropriation data, the Contractor’s Tariff, the Contractor's cost of purchased fuel, or the estimated annual cost of Service. Such changes are considered internal to the party involved. Where changes are required in effective Authorizations because of a change in the Service requirements of an Ordering Agency, an amended Authorization shall be mutually agreed upon and executed. 4.3. An Ordering Agency or the Contractor may discontinue Service provided pursuant to this Areawide Contract to a particular Federal facility or installation by delivering a written Termination Authorization to the other. Such discontinuance of Service by an Ordering Agency or the Contractor shall be in accordance with the terms of this Area wide Contract and the Contractor’s Tariffs. 4.4. In the event the Areawide Contract is not renewed at the expiration of the contract term, any active authorizations for services shall be controlled by the Contract terms and conditions in effect at the time of award. ARTICLE 5. RATES, CHARGES, AND PUBLIC REGULATION. 5.1. A complete listing of all Contractor’s Tariffs, as amended, supplemented, modified and revised from time to lime, is available to the Government and any Ordering Agency electronically at the Contractor’s website accessible via http://www.comed.com. 5.2. Subject to the provisions of Article 2.3, all Electric, Energy Management Services and/or Services Provided Under The Appropriate Regulatory Authority purchased under this Areawide Contract, as well as any other action under this Areawide Contract shall be in accordance with, and subject to, the Contractor's Tariffs, Contractor’s Terms and Conditions, and any other terms and conditions set forth in an Authorization, except to the extent that same are preempted by Federal law. Throughout the Term of the Areawide Contract, the Government shall have full access to the Contractor's currently effective Tariffs. In the event the Contractor's Tariffs become inaccessible via the internet or the Ordering Agency does not have access to the internet, the Contractor agrees to provide newly effective or amended Tariffs in accordance with the Contractor’s Tariff distribution practices, policies and procedures applicable to all customers. 5.3. If, during the Term of this Area wide Contract, the Commission approves a change in rales for services specified in Authorizations in effect hereunder, the Contractor agrees to continue to furnish, and the Ordering Agency agrees to continue to pay for, those Services at the newly approved rates from and after the date such rates are made effective. As provided in Article 4.2, modification of any Authorization hereunder is not necessary to implement higher or lower rates. 5.4. The Contractor hereby represents and warrants to the Government that the Service rates available to any Ordering Agency hereunder shall at all times not exceed those available to any other customer served under the same Service Classification for the same or comparable service, under like conditions of use. Nothing herein shall require the Contractor to apply service rates that are inapplicable to the Ordering Agency. 5.5. Reasonable written notice via an Authorization shall be given by the Ordering Agency to the Contractor, at the address provided in Article 16.2, of any material changes proposed in the volume or characteristic of utility services required hy the Ordering Agency. 5.6. To the extent required by the Contractor’s Tariffs, the Commission’s rules and regulations, or the Contractor’s policies and practices applicable to all customers, and in accordance therewith, any necessary extension, alteration, relocation, or reinforcement of the Contractor’s transmission or distribution lines, related special facilities, Service arrangements, demand side management services (including any rebates to which the Ordering Agency may be entitled), energy audit services, or other Services required or requested by an Ordering Agency shall be provided and, as applicable, billed for, by the Contractor. To the extent available from the Contractor, the Contractor shall provide and, as applicable, bill for such technical assistance on or concerning an Ordering Agency’s equipment (such as the inspection or repair of such equipment) as may be requested by such Ordering Agency. The charges for such technical assistance shall be calculated at the time the technical assistance is rendered, as mutually agreed upon by the Contractor and the Agency, and shall comply with Contractor's Tariffs, if applicable. The Authorization or any other agreement used to obtain and provide the matters, Services, or technical assistance described in this Article 5.6 shall contain information descriptive of the matters, Services, or technical assistance required or requested, including the amount of (or method to determine) any payment to be made by the Ordering Agency to the Contractor for the provision of said matters. Services, or technical assistance, 5.7. Any charges for matters or Services referenced in Article 5.6 hereof which are not established by the Contractor’s Tariffs shall be subject to audit by the Ordering Agency prior to payment provided, however, that notwithstanding such right to audit, payment for the matters and Services referenced in Article 5,6 thereof shall not be unreasonably withheld or denied. The Contractor further warrants and represents to the Government that charges for the matters or Services referenced in Article 5.6 hereof will not exceed the charges billed to other customers of the Contractor served under the same Service Classification for like matters or Services provided under similar circumstances. 5.8. The requirements of the Disputes clause at FAR 52.233-1 are supplemented to provide that matters involving the interpretation of Contractor’s Tariffs) are subject to the jurisdiction and regulation of the utility rate commission havingjurisdiction. ARTICLE 6. BILLS AND BILLING DATA. 6.1 The Electric, Energy Management Services and/or Services provided under the Appropriate Regulatory Authority supplied hereunder shall be billed to the Ordering Agency at the address specified in each Authorization. Bills shall be submitted in original only, unless otherwise specified in the Authorization. All bills shall contain such data as is required by the Commission to substantiate the billing and such other reasonable and available data as may be requested by the Ordering Agency, provided that such other data are contained in bills provided to other customers of the Contractor served under the same Service Classification as the Ordering Agency. ARTICLE 7. PAYMENTS FOR SERVICES. 7.1. Payments hereunder shall not be paid in advance of Services rendered. The Ordering Agency shall effect payment of all bills for regulated Services rendered under this Areawide Contract in accordance with the terms of the Contractor's Tariff, Contractor’s Standard Terms and Conditions, and any other payment terms and conditions set forth in an Authorization.. Changes in the Contractor’s Tariff provisions for the payment of bills shall supersede the provisions of this paragraph to the extent of the applicability of such changes. 7.2. The Ordering Agency will make invoice payments for Services not subject to the direct oversight of the Commission in accordance with the provisions of the FAR Subpart 52.232-25 (Article 14.1-16). The interest rate for late payments made pursuant to this clause shall be computed in accordance with the Office of Management and Budget prompt payment regulations at 5 C.F.R. 1315. 7.3. Payments hereunder shall not normally be made in advance of services rendered in accordance with 48 C.F.R. Subpart 32.4, unless required by the Contractor’s Tariff or Contractor’s Terms and Conditions. The applicability of this provision is limited to connection charge and line extension payments specifically cited in the Contractor's Tariff. 7.4. Each payment made by Treasury check to the Contractor shall include the Contractor's billing stub(s), or a Government or Ordering Agency payment document, that clearly and correctly lists ail of the Contractor's account numbers to which the payment applies and the dollar amount applicable to each account. If payment is by Electronic Funds Transfer either through the Automated Clearing House (ACH) or the Federal Reserve Wire Transfer System, the provisions of FAR Subpart 52.232-34 shall apply (See Article 14), ARTICLE 8. CONTRACTOR-OWNED METERS. 8.1. Metering equipment of standard manufacture suitable to measure all utility services supplied by the Contractor hereunder shall be furnished, installed, calibrated and maintained by the Contractor in accordance with Contractor’s Tariffs and the Commission’s regulations. In the event any meter fails to register or registers incorrectly, as determined by the regulations of the Commission, billing adjustments shall be made in accordance with such regulations. 8.2. The Contractor, so far as possible, shall read all meters monthly in accordance with the Contractor's Tariff and the Commission’s regulations. 8.3. Meters shall be inspected upon installation in accordance with Contractor’s Tariffs and the Commission’s regulations. Subsequent inspection, periodic testing, repair, and replacement of meters shall be done in such place and manner as provided by the Commission’s regulations. Upon notice that a meter is failing to register correctly, the Contractor shall lake immediate steps to effect replacement or repair in accordance with Commission regulations. Ordering Agencies shall have the right to request a meter lest in accordance with lhe procedures prescribed in the Commission's regulations. The tests and applicable meter accuracy standards are those set forth in the Commission's regulations. The expense of meter tests shall be bome by lhe party designated as responsible therefore m the Commission's regulations. 8.4. For the purposes of this Article 8, references to meters shall apply only to Contractor-owned metering devices installed and maintained by the Contractor in accordance with Commission guidelines for utility service(s). References to meters under this Article shall not apply to meters that are to be installed by the Contractor at lhe request of an Ordering Agency, to be owned by lhe Government as a part of an Authorization for Energy Management Service or other Service. ARTICLE 9. EQUIPMENT AND FACILITIES. 9.1. Subject to lhe provisions of Article 5.6 hereof, lhe responsibility for owning, furnishing, installing, and maintaining all equipment and facilities (other than meters) required to supply service at lhe delivery point(s) specified in an Authorization shall be determined in accordance with lhe Contractor's regulated Tariffs and lhe Commission’s regulations. The Ordering Agency shall provide, free of charge to the Contractor, mutually agreeable locations on its premises for the installation of meters and such other equipment furnished and owned by lhe Contractor and necessary to supply Service hereunder. The Contractor shall, at all times during the Term of this Areawide Contract, operate and maintain such equipment or facilities as for which it has responsibility in accordance with this Article 9.1, in accordance with Contractor’s Tariffs and lhe Commission’s regulations. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in FAR 52.241-5 (Contractor’s Facilities (FEB 1995)), to lhe extent required by the Contractor’s Tariffs and lhe Commission's rules and regulations, and in accordance thereof, such equipment and facilities as for which the Contractor has responsibility in accordance with this Article 9.1 shall be removed, or any underground equipment or facilities for which the Contractor has responsibility in accordance with this Article 9.1, such underground equipment or facilities may be abandoned, and in both cases, the Agency's premises restored, by lhe Contractor within a reasonable time after discontinuance of service to lhe Ordering Agency. 9.2. All necessary rights-of-way, easements and such other rights necessary to permit the Contractor to perform under this Areawide Contract shall be obtained and lhe expense for same bome in accordance with the Contractor’s Tariffs and the Commission’s rules and regulations. 9 J. Prior to lhe Contractor commencing construction on lhe property of the Ordering Agency, the Ordering Agency shall, at its own expense, provide the Contractor with copies of maps and other records of existing Government-owned on-site utilities and other potential obstructions, as deemed necessary by the Contractor. In addition, the Ordering Agency, at its own expense, shall locate and field-mark existing Government-owned on-site underground utilities prior to lhe Contractor commencing construction. As an option, the Ordering Agency may request lhe Contractor to provide these services within the scope of the Authorization, at an additional expense, if mutually agreed to by both parties. The Ordering Agency shall, at its own expense, identify and remove or otherwise render safe any and all unexploded ordinance on lhe property of the Ordering Agency prior to lhe Contractor commencing construction. ARTICLE 10. LIABILITY. 10.1. If the Government and/or an Ordering Agency has limited or res trie led the Contractor's right of access under Article 11 and thereby interfered with lhe Contractor's ability to supply service or to correct dangerous situations which are a threat to public safety, Contractor shall be excused from any contractual or service obligations that are impacted by lhe Government’s limitation or restriction on access and lhe Government shall be responsible for any liability resulting from such restricted or limited access to lhe extent permitted by law and authorized by appropriations. This Article (10.1) shall not be construed to limit the Government's liability under applicable law. 10.2. The Contractor's liability to the Government and to any Ordering Agency for any failure to supply Service, for any interruptions in Service, and for any irregular or defective Service shall be determined in accordance with lhe Contractor’s Tariffs or Contractor’s Terms and Conditions. 10.3. Except as provided above, and in accordance with the Contractor's Tariff and Terms and Conditions of Service, the Government shall not be liable for damage or injury to any person or property, including death, occasioned solely by the Contractor's, its employees' or agents' negligent installation, use, operation or intentional misuse of the Contractor’s equipment or facilities. 10.4. In accordance with the Contractor’s Tariff and/or Terms and Conditions of Service, neither the Contractor nor its employees or agents, shall be liable for damage or injury to any person or property, including death, occasioned solely by the negligent installation, use, operation or intentional misuse of Contractor's equipment or facilities by the Government, its employees or agents. 10.5. The Contractor shall not be liable for incidents arising out of or in any way connected with the violation or compliance with any local, slate or federal environmental law or regulation resulting from pre-existing conditions at a Government job site, release or spill of any pre-existing Hazardous Materials or Hazardous Waste, or out of the management and disposal of any pre-existing contaminated soils or ground water, hazardous or non-hazardous, removed from the ground as a result of work performed by the Contractor. 10.6. The Government agrees to accept full responsibility for and bear ail costs associated with pre-existing environmental liability. Responsibility for testing, abatement, remediation, and/or disposal of Hazardous Material, including, but not limited to, contaminated soil, contaminated groundwater and contaminated surface water and storm water resulting from contact with pre-existing hazardous materials, lead paint, asbestos, polychlorinated biphenyls, fuel oil, or underground fuel oil tanks, shall remain with the Government. Where there is reason to suspect that Hazardous Material is present at the work site, or where Hazardous Material is encountered during the course of work being performed, the Contractor shall stop work, notify the Contracting Officer and Activity personnel, and request (hat the Government test the work site for such Hazardous Material and appropriately abate and dispose of such Hazardous Material. Once the work site has been cleared of all Hazardous Material, the Contractor shall resume work in that area. ARTICLE 11. ACCESS TO PREMISES. 11.1. The Contractor and its employees, agents, representatives and independent contractors shall have access to the premises served at all reasonable times during the Term of any Authorization t executed under this Areawide Contract and for a reasonable period of time following its expiration or termination, whichever occurs latest, to perform certain work, which shall include but not be limited to the following: for the purpose of reading meters, making installations, repairs, or removals of the Contractor's equipment, or for any other proper purposes hereunder provided, however, (hat proper military or other governmental authority may limit or restrict such right of access in any manner considered by such authority to be reasonably necessary or advisable. However, any such limitation or restriction shall not be to the extent to prohibit the Contractor’s ability to complete all work incident to the termination or expiration of this Areawide Contract. ARTICLE 12. PARTIES OF INTEREST. 12.1. This Areawide Contract shall be binding upon and inure to the benefit of the successors, legal representatives, and assignees of the respective parties hereto. 12.2. When the Contractor becomes aware that a change in ownership (“change in ownership” for purposes of this Areawide Contract being defined as a sale of more than fifty percent of the outstanding voting stock of the Contractor) or company name has occurred, or is certain to occur, the Contractor shall notify the Contracting Officer at the address provided in Article 16.1 not later than thirty (30) days after the effectiveness of any such ownership or name change. In the event (he Contractor fails to make the notification required by this Article 12,2, the Government cannot guarantee the timely payment of outstanding invoices in accordance with the provisions of Article 7.1; however, the Government shall he responsible for all payments related to the Services provided hy the Contractor hereunder. ARTICLE 13. REPRESENTATIONS AND CERTIFICATIONS. 13.1. This Areawide Contract incorporates by reference the representations and certifications made by the Contractor which shall be filed annually electronically at www.sam.gov. 13.2. Contractor represents that the following persons are currently authorized to negotiate and execute on its behalf with the U.S. Government in connection with this Areawide Contract: (List names, titles, email address and telephone numbers of the authorized negotiators): 1. Fidel Marquez, Jr. SVP Governmental and External Affairs 312-394-4951 Fidel.marquez@comed.com 2. Miguel Ortega Director External Affairs 630-437-2139 Miguel.ortega@comed.com 3. Thomas O’Neil SVP Regulatory &amp; Energy Policy &amp; general Counsel 312-394-7205 Thomas.oneill@comed.com Contractor reserves the right to amend the above-list of persons at any time by delivering written notice to the Government at the address provided in Article 16.1. ARTICLE 14. SUPPLEMENTAL CLAUSES. 14.1. 52.252-2 Clauses Incorporated by Reference. (FEB 1998) This Area wide Contract incorporates one or more clauses by reference, with the same force and effect as if they were given in full text. Upon request, the Contracting Officer will make their full text available. The offeror is cautioned that the listed provisions and clauses may include blocks that must be completed by the contractor and/or submitted with its documentation. In lieu of submitting the full text of those provisions and clauses, the contractor may identify the provision and/or clause by paragraph identifier and provide the appropriate information with its documentation. Also, the full text of a clause may be accessed electronically at this/these address (es): http//: www.amet.gov FAR REF Federal Acquisition Regulation 1.        52.203-3 2.        52.203-5 3.        52.203-6 4.       52.203-7 5.       52.203-8 6.       52.203-10 7.        52.203-11 8       52.203-12 9.       52.204-4 10.      52.204-5 11.      52.204-9 GRATUITIES (APR 1984) COVENANT AGAINST CONTINGENT FEES (MAY 2014) RESTRICTIONS ON SUBCONTRACTOR SALES TO THE GOVERNMENT (SEPT 2006) ANTI-KICKBACK PROCEDURES (MAY 2014) CANCELLATION, RESCISSION, AND RECOVERY OF FUNDS FOR ILLEGAL OR IMPROPER ACTIVITY (MAY2014) PRICE OR FEE ADJUSTMENT FOR ILLEGAL OR IMPROPER ACTIVITY (MAY 2014) CERTIFICATION AND DISCLOSURE REGARDING PAYMENTS TO INFLUENCE CERTAIN FEDERAL TRANSACTIONS (SEPT 2007) LIMITATION ON PAYMENTS TO INFLUENCE CERTAIN FEDERAL TRANSACTIONS (OCT 2010) PRINTED OR COPIED DOUBLE-SIDED ON RECYCLED PAPER (MAY 2011) WOMEN-OWNED BUSINESS (OTHER THAN SMALL BUSINESS) (MAY 1999) PERSONAL IDENTITY VERIFICATION OF CONTRACTOR PERSONNEL (JAN 2011)/,2 12.      52.204-7 13.      52.209-6 14.      52.215-2 15.      52.215-10 16.      52.215-12 17      52.215-14 18.      52.215-20 19.      52.219-8 20.      52.219-9 21.      52.219-16 22.      52.222-3 23.      52.222-21 24.      52.222-26 25.      52.222-35 26.      52.222-36 27.      52.222-37 28.      52.222-38 29.      52.222-50 30.      52.222-54 31.       52.223-1 32.      52.223-5 33.      52.223-6 34.      52.223-9 35.      52.223-15 36.      52.223-17 37.      52.225-13 38.      52.232-11 39.      52.232-17 40.      52.232-18 41.      52.232.19 42.      52.232-23 43.      52.232-25 44.      52.232-33 45.      52.232-35 46.      52.232-36 47.      52.232-37 48.      52.233-1 49.      52.233-4 50.      52.236-9 51.      52.237-2 52.      52.241-2 53.      52.241-3 54.      52.241-4 55.      52.241-5 56.      52.241-6 57.      52.241-7 58.      52.241-8 59.      52.241-9 60.      52.241-9 61.      52.241-10 62.      52.241-12 63.      52.242-13 64.      52.243-1 65.      52.244-5 CENTRAL CONTRACTOR REGISTRATION (JUL 2013) PROTECTING THE GOVERNMENT’S INTEREST WHEN SUBCONTRACTING WITH CONTRACTORS DEBARRED, SUSPENDED, OR PROPOSED FOR DEBARMENT (OCT 2015) AUDIT AND RECORDS—NEGOTIATION (OCT 2010)/ PRICE REDUCTION FOR DEFECTIVE COST OR PRICING DATA (AUG 2011)/ SUBCONTRACTOR COST OR PRICING DATA (OCT 2010)7 INTEGRITY OF UNIT PRICES (OCT 2010)7 REQUIREMENTS FOR COST OR PRICING DATA OR INFORMATION OTHER THAN COST OR PRICING DATA (OCT 2010)7 UTILIZATION OF SMALL BUSINESS CONCERNS (OCT 2014) SMALL BUSINESS SUBCONTRACTING PLAN (OCT 2015) LIQUIDATED DAMAGES—SUBCONTRACTING PLAN (JAN 1999) CONVICT LABOR (JUNE 2003) PROHIBITION OF SEGREGATED FACILITIES (APR 2015) EQUAL OPPORTUNITY (APR 2015) EQUAL OPPORTUNITY FOR VETERANS (OCT 2015) AFFIRMATIVE ACTION FOR WORKERS WITH DISABILITIES (JUL 2014) EMPLOYMENT REPORTS ON VETERANS (OCT 2015) COMPLIANCE WITH VETERANS’ EMPLOYMENT REPORTING REQUIREMENTS (SEPT 2010) COMBATING TRAFFICKING IN PERSONS (MAR 2015) EMPLOYMENT ELIGIBILITY VERIFICATION (OCT 2015) RECOVERED MATERIAL CERTIFICATION (MAY 2008)7 POLLUTION PREVENTION AND R1GHT-TO-KNOW INFORMATION (MAY 20H) DRUG-FREE WORKPLACE (MAY 2001) ESTIMATE OF PERCENTAGE OF RECOVERED MATERIAL CONTENT FOR EPA- DESIGNATED ITEMS (MAY 2008)1,3 ENERGY EFFICIENCY IN ENERGY-CONSUMING PRODUCTS (DEC 2007) I AFFIRMATIVE PROCUREMENT OF EP A-DESIGNATED ITEMS IN SERVICE AND CONSTRUCTION CONTRACTS (MAY 2008)7 RESTRICTIONS ON CERTAIN FOREIGN PURCHASES (JUNE 2008) EXTRAS (APR 1984) INTEREST (MAY 2014) AVAILABILITY OF FUNDS (APR 1984) AVAILABILITY OF FUNDS FOR THE NEXT FISCAL YEAR (APR 1984) 4 ASSIGNMENT OF CLAIMS (MAY 2014) PROMPT PAYMENT (JUL 2013) 7 PAYMENT BY ELECTRONIC FUNDS TRANSFER—CENTRAL CONTRACTOR REGISTRATION (JUL 2013) DESIGNATION OF OFFICE FOR GOVERNMENT RECEIPT OF ELECTRONIC FUNDS TRANSFER INFORMATION (JUL 2013) 1,2 PAYMENT BY THIRD PARTY (MAY 2014) 2 MULTIPLE PAYMENT ARRANGEMENTS (MAY 1999) DISPUTES (MAY 2014) APPLICABLE LAW FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT CLAIM (OCT 2004) PROTECTION OF EXISTING VEGETATION, STRUCTURES, EQUIPMENT, UTILITIES, AND IMPROVEMENTS (APR 1984) PROTECTION OF GOVERNMENT BUILDINGS, EQUIPMENT, AND VEGETATION (APR 1984) ORDER OF PRECEDENCE—UTILITIES (FEB 1995) SCOPE AND DURATION OF CONTRACT (FEB 1995) 4 CHANGE IN CLASS OF SERVICE (FEB 1995) CONTRACTOR’S FACILITIES (FEB 1995) SERVICE PROVISIONS (FEB 1995) 4 CHANGE IN RATES OR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SERVICE FOR REGULATED SERVICES (FEB 1995) CHANGE IN RATES OR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SERVICE FOR UNREGULATED SERVICES (FEB 1995) 1,3 CONNECTION CHARGE (FEB 1995)2,3 CONNECTION CHARGE (ALT I) (FEB 1995) 2,3 TERMINATION LIABILITY (FEB 1995)2,3 NONREFUNDABLE NONRECURRING SERVICE CHARGE (FEB 1995) 2,3 BANKRUPTCY (JULY 1995) CHANGES—FIXED PRICE (AUG 1987) COMPETITION IN SUBCONTRACTING (DEC 1996) 7 66.      52.244-6 67.      52.246-25 68.      52.248-1 69.      52.249-4 70.      52.249-8 71.      552.241-70 72.      552.241-71 SUBCONTRACTS FOR COMMERCIAL ITEMS (OCT 2015) LIMITATION OF LIABILITY—SERVICES (FEB 1997) VALUE ENGINEERING (ALT I) (OCT 2010) / TERMINATION FOR CONVENIENCE OF THE GOVERNMENT (SERVICES) (SHORT FORM) (APR 1984) DEFAULT (FIXED-PRICE SUPPLY AND SERVICE) (APR 1984) 1 AVAILABILITY OF FUNDS FOR THE NEXT FISCAL YEAR OR QUARTER (SEPT 2010) DISPUTES (UTILITY CONTRACTS) (AUG 2010) 1 INDICATES THAT THE CLAUSE APPLIES TO THE ENERGY MANAGEMENT AUTHORIZATION AND ONLY TO THE EXTENT THAT THE CONTRACTING OFFICER OF THE DELIVERY ORDER DETERMINES THAT THE CLAUSE IS NECESSARY FOR EFFICIENT CONTRACT ADMINISTRATION. 2 INDICATES THAT THE CLAUSE APPLIES TO THE ELECTRIC SERVICE AUTHORIZATION AND ONLY TO THE EXTENT THAT THE CONTRACTING OFFICER OF THE DELIVERY ORDER DETERMINES THAT THE CLAUSE IS NECESSARY FOR EFFICIENT CONTRACT ADMINISTRATION. 3 THE REFERENCED CLAUSE SHOULD BE INCLUDED IN FULL TEXT TN THE AUTHORIZATION FOR ELECTRIC SERVICE. 4 INDICATES THAT TI-IE CLAUSE HAS BEEN INCLUDED WITHIN THE TEXT OF THE AREAWIDE CONTRACT ON A "SUBSTANTIALLY THE SAME" BASIS AS REQUIRED BY SUBPART 41.501(A) OF THE FEDERAL ACQUISITION REGULATIONS Clauses marked with an asterisk (*) are only applicable if checked on an Authorization, and only to the work ordered on that Authorization. 14.2    Unregulated Services. Pursuant to this Areawide Contract, the Contractor may provide energy related services that are not subject to rate and tariff regulations by the Commission under a pre-approved alternative (FAR 52.241-8) that demonstrates the Contractor will provide these services under terms and conditions that are competitive and otherwise in the best interests of the Ordering Agency. If, as demonstrated by the Ordering Agency, the conditions for use of this preapproved alternative cannot be satisfied, then the Ordering Agency should consider the requirement of the Competition in Contracting Act of 1984 and the extent to which a competitive acquisition process is required to select and award a contract for these unregulated services. If an Authorization under this Areawide Contract is utilized, the prices and terms and conditions for unregulated services offered by the Contractor shall be negotiated subject to the requirements of FAR 41.5, subject to the general requirements of FAR 52.241-8. 14.3 Repeal ofCIauses During Term of Areawide Contract. If, during the Term of this Areawide Contract, any of the clauses contained m this Article are repealed, revoked, or dissolved by the Government, then such clauses shall no longer be part of this Areawide Contract as of the date of such repeal, revocation, or dissolution. The elimination of these clauses by reason of such repeal, revocation, or dissolution shall not affect the continuing validity and effectiveness of the remainder of this Areawide Contract or other clauses referenced in this Article. The parties’ conduct thereafter shall be modified accordingly and reflect the repeal, revocation, or dissolution as related to their respective rights and obligations hereunder. 14.4 Clauses Incorporated in Full Text. 1. 52.222-40 Notification of Employee Rights Under the National Labor Relations Act. As prescribed in 22,1605. insert the following clause: NOTIFICATION OF EMPLOYEE RIGHTS UNDER THE NATIONAL LABOR RELATIONS ACT (DEC 2010) (a) During the term of this contract, the Contractor shall post an employee notice, of such size and in such form, and containing such content as prescribed by the Secretary of Labor, in conspicuous places in and about its plants and offices where employees covered by the National Labor Relations Act engage in activities relating to the performance of the contract, including all places where notices to employees are customarily posted both physically and electronically, in the languages employees speak, in accordance with 29 CFR 471,2 (d) and (f). (1) Physical posting of the employee notice shall be in conspicuous places in and about the Contractor’s plants and offices so that the notice is prominent and readily seen by employees who are covered by the National Labor Relations Act and engage in activities related to the performance of the contract, (2) If the Contractor customarily posts notices to employees electronically, then the Contractor shall also post the required notice electronically by displaying prominently, on any website that is maintained by the Contractor and is customarily used for notices to employees about terms and conditions of employment, a link to the Department of Labor’s website that contains the full text of the poster. The link to the Department’s website, as referenced in (b)(3) of this section, must read, “Important Notice about Employee Rights to Organize and Bargain Collectively with Their Employers." (b) This required employee notice, printed by the Department of Labor, may be— (1) Obtained from the Division of Interpretations and Standards, Office of Labor-Management Standards, U.S. Department of Labor, 200 Constitution Avenue, NW, Room N-5609, Washington, DC 20210, (202) 693-0123, or from any field office of the Office of Labor-Manage me nt Standards or Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs; (2) Provided by the Federal contracting agency if requested; (3) Downloaded from the Office of Labor-Management Standards Web site at www .dol.gov/olms/regs/complianc eEO 13496.him; or (4) Reproduced and used as exact duplicate copies of the Department of Labor’s official poster. (c) The required text of the employee notice referred to in this clause is located at Appendix A, Subpart A, 29 CFR Part 471. (d) The Contractor shall comply with all provisions of the employee notice and related rules, regulations, and orders of the Secretary of Labor. (e) In the event that the Contractor does not comply with the requirements set forth in paragraphs (a) through (d) of this clause, this contract may be terminated or suspended in whole or in part, and the Contractor may be suspended or debarred in accordance with 29 CFR 471.14 and subpart 9.4. Such other sanctions or remedies may be imposed as are provided by 29 CFR part 471, which implements Executive Order 13496 or as otherwise provided by law. (f) Subcontracts. (1) The Contractor shall include the substance of this Clause, including this paragraph (f), in every subcontract that exceeds $10,000 and will be performed wholly or partially in the United States, unless exempted by the rules, regulations, or orders of the Secretary of Labor issued pursuant to section 3 of Executive Order 13496 of January 30, 2009, so that such provisions will be binding upon each subcontractor. (2) The Contractor shall not procure supplies or services in a way designed to avoid the applicability of Executive Order 13496 or this clause. (3) The Contractor shall take such action with respect to any such subcontract as may be directed by the Secretary of Labor as a means of enforcing such provisions, including the imposition of sanctions for noncompliance. (4) However, if the Contractor becomes involved in litigation with a subcontractor, or is threatened with such involvement, as a result of such direction, the Contractor may request the United States, through the Secretary of Labor, to enter into such litigation to protect the interests of the United Slates. (End of clause) 2. 52.241-7 Change in Rates or Terms and Conditions ofService for Regulated Services (FEB 1995) The items included in Contractor’s Tariff are available to the government and any Ordering Agency electronically at tire Contractor’s website, http://www.comed.com. In addition, the government and any Ordering Agency may register at the website maintained by each of the respective Regulatory Commissions for each docket opened regarding Contractor for automatic electronic notifications pertaining to that docket. Contractor shall comply with the Commission's regulatory requirements applicable to notifications to Contractor customers for changes to Contractors TarifF. (End of clause) 3. 52.252-1 Solicitation Provisions Incorporated by Reference (FEB 1998) As prescribed in 52.107(a). insert the following provision: Solicitation Provisions Incorporated by Reference (Feb 1998) (See Article 14.1) 4. The requirements of the Disputes clause at Federal Acquisition Regulation (FAR) 52.233-1 are supplemented to provide that matters involving the interpretation of tariffed retail rates, tariff rate schedules, and tariffed terms provided under this Areawide contract are subject to the jurisdiction and regulation of the utility rate commission having jurisdiction. 5. 52,216-1     Type of Contract As prescribed in 16.105, complete and insert the following provision: Type of Contract (Apr 1984) For ECMs, the Government contemplates award of a Fixed Price contract resulting from this solicitation. 14.4 State Taxes. The contract price includes all State and local taxes levied on or measured by the contract or sales price of the services or completed supplies furnished under this contract The Government agrees either to pay the amount of the stale or local taxes to the Contractor or provide evidence necessary to sustain an exemption from such taxes. ARTICLE 15. SMALL BUSINESS SUBCONTRACTING PLAN. 15.1. Attached hereto and made a part hereof by reference is a SUBCONTRACTING PLAN FOR SMALL BUSINESS CONCERNS, SMALL BUSINESS CONCERNS OWNED AND CONTROLLED BY SOCIALLY &amp; ECONOMICALLY DISADVANTAGED INDIVIDUALS, HUB ZONE BUSINESS CONCERNS, WOMAN OWNED SMALL BUSINESS CONCERNS, VETERAN-OWNED SMALL BUSINESSES CONCERNS AND DISABLED VETERAN-OWNED BUSINESSES negotiated between the Contractor and the Government, which is applicable on a company wide basis pursuant to the requirements of Section 211 of P.L, 95-507, as amended (15 U.S.C. 637(d)). The Contractor expressly understands that this subcontracting plan is an annual plan and hereby agrees to submit a new subcontracting plan by November 30th of each year during the Term of this Areawide Contract 15.2. Information and announcements concerning current developments in the GSA Small Business Subcontracting Program are available on the GSA Energy Division web site accessible via http://www.gsa.gov/energy. ARTICLE 16. NOTICES. 16.1. Unless specifically provided otherwise, all notices required to be provided to the Government under this Areawide Contract shall be mailed to: U. S. General Services Administration, PBS, Office of Facilities Management and Services Program; Director, Energy Division, 1800 F Street, NW Room 5116, Washington, DC 20405. 16.2. All inquiries and notices to the Contractor regarding this Areawide Contract shall be mailed to: Miguel Ortega (Telephone Number: (630)437-2139 ), (E-mail: Miguel.ortega@comed.com) or to such other person as the Contractor may hereafter designate in writing. 16.3. The Ordering Agency shall provide GSA with a copy of all fully executed Exhibits including any applicable attachments at the address provided in Article 16.1. ARTICLE 17. REPORTING. The Contractor shall provide, as prescribed and directed by the Contracting Officer, an annual report on Subcontracting Plan Achievements, in accordance with the approved subcontracting plan for small business concerns and small business concerns owned and controlled by socially and economically disadvantaged individuals by October 30 of each year during the Term of this Areawide Contract. The report shall be submitted electronically utilizing the Small Business Administration's Electronic Subcontracting Reporting System. The website address of system can be found at http ://www. esra.gov. ARTICLE 18. EXHIBIT “B” AUTHORIZATION FOR ENERGY MANAGEMENT SERVICES (UTILITY ENERGY SERVICES CONTRACTS) 18.1. Measurement and verification: Energy Conservation Measures (ECM) will not be normally considered unless a net overall energy or water usage or cost reduction can be demonstrated and verified. Verification standards for energy projects are established in the North-American Energy Measurement and Verification Protocol (NEMVP), published by the Department of Energy’s Federal Energy Management Program (FEMP), or as agreed in the Authorization. 18.2.  Unless otherwise provided by law or the terms and conditions of an Authorization, the following provisions shall apply: (a) Payment for energy conservation measures, when authorized as Energy Management Service (EMS), shall be equal to the direct cost of capital or financing amortized over a negotiated payment term commencing on the date of acceptance of the completed installation; (b) The payment term for Authorizations involving energy conservation measures should be calculated to enable the Ordering Agency’s payment(s) to be lower than the estimated cost savings to be realized from its implementation. In no event, however, shall this term exceed eighty percent (80%) of the useful life of the equipment/material to be installed. 183. Subcontracting; Contractor shall have the right to enter into a subcontract with a third-party Energy Service Company (“ESCO”), which shall include unregulated affiliates of Contractor, to perform the project development and project management functions under the Authorization. Contractor or any such ESCO designated by Contractor may perform any or all of the Energy Management Services requested by an Ordering Agency through subcontractors (each an “EMS Subcontractor”). EMS Subcontractors shall be competitively selected in accordance with FAR 52.244-5 (Competition in Subcontracting) (DEC 1996) (See Article 14). EMS Subcontractor selection shall be based on cost, experience, past performance and other such factors as the Contractor and the Ordering Agency may mutually deem appropriate and reasonably related to the Government’s minimum requirements. Upon request by the Government, the Contractor shall make available to the contracting officer all documents related to the selection of a subcontractor. In no event shall the Service be provided by an EMS Subcontractor listed as excluded from Federal Procurement Programs maintained by GSA pursuant to 48 C.F.R. 9.404 in accordance with 52.209-6 (Protecting the Government’s Interest when Subcontracting with Contractors Debarred, Suspended, or Proposed for Debarment (AUG 2013) (See Article 14)). 18.4. For all Authorizations involving Energy Conservation Measures, it is desirable to have a Warranty Clause that addresses the specific needs and requirements of the work being performed and equipment that is to be provided by the Contractor; however, in the absence of a Warranty Clause in the Authorization, the following language will serve as the default Clause: The Company shall pass through to the Agency all warranties on equipment installed or provided by it or its subcontractors on Government property with the following representation: COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA WILL OWN OR LEASE THE EQUIPMENT AND/OR MATERIALS BEING INSTALLED OR SUPPLIED HEREUNDER, AND, ACCORDINGLY, AGREES THAT ALL WARRANTIES SET FORTH HEREIN, OR OTHERWISE PROVIDED BY LAW IN FAVOR OF GOVERNMENT SHALL INURE ALSO TO THE BENEFIT OF THE UNITED STATES AND THAT ALL CLAIMS ARISING FROM ANY BREACH OF SUCH WARRANTIES OR AS A RESULT OF DEFECTS IN OR REPAIRS TO SUCH EQUIPMENT OR SUPPLIES MAY BE ASSERTED AGAINST COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY OR MANUFACTURER DIRECTLY BY THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA. 18.5.   The Ordering Agency shall submit to GSA a copy of all preliminary energy audit results or energy conservation measure analysis for review and compliance with Federal regulations and policy. Upon written acknowledgement from GSA of receipt of the aforementioned information, a copy of which shall be provided by the Ordering Agency to the Contractor, the Ordering Agency may negotiate Task Orders with the Contractor for the implementation of the energy conservation measures described in the preliminary documents. The Ordering Agency shall provide GSA with copies of fully executed Exhibit “B” Authorizations for any Energy Management Services resulting from confirmed/approved energy audits, including any applicable attachments, at the address provided in Article 16.1. 18.6. Contractor’s Responsibilities under this Areawide Contract: (a) The Contractor shall not provide Energy Management Service to Federal facilities unless the facility is a current customer or prospective customer of the regulated utility within the franchised service territory of the utility company providing such services. (b) The work that is to be performed under the Authorization for Energy Management Services shall be limited to work resulting in a direct reduction in energy or water usage (see Article l.l(j)) and any modification or repair that is necessary as a direct result of the installation of the ECM. 18.7.   Energy Savings and Scoring of UESC’s by the Ordering Agency (ies): For Ordering Agency facilities, UESC’s that meet the definition of “Energy Management Service" (“EMS”) prescribed in Article I.l(k) of this Areawide Contract, and whicb follow the guidance prescribed in OMB Memoranda M-12-21 and M-98-13, may be scored for budgetary purposes by the Ordering Agency (ies) on an annual basis if the UESC requires: (a)  Energy savings performance assurances or guarantees of the savings to be generated by improvements, which must cover the full cost of the Federal investment for the improvements; (b) Measurement and verification (M&amp;V) of savings through commissioning and retro-commissioning; and (c) Competition or an alternatives analysis as part of the selection process prior to entering into a UESC 18.8.   In order to assure the necessary fiscal responsibility consistent with sound program management, for Ordering Agency facilities, alternatively financed UESCs may include a plan for continued action during the contract to assure continued accomplishment of expceted performance (this is referred to as a Performance Assurance or Performance Verification Plan). The level of performance assurance (M&amp;V) and its associated costs should be worth the level of certainty of cost savings that the Ordering Agency reasonably deems to be necessary. Each alternatively financed UESC may have a performance assurance plan to accomplish this. Such plans should provide for the separate evaluation of each energy conservation measure and combination of measures in order to identify the appropriate level of needed performance assurance activity based on the technical complexity, potential savings magnitude, and specific situation. (See Overview of the Measurement and Verification for Federal Energy Projects Guidelines Version 2.2 or FEMP Fact Sheet - Performance Assurance for Multi-Year Contracts under the Utility Incentive Program for further . 1 guidance.) Inclusion of and compliance with the performance assurance plan in the specific project task order satisfies the requirements of Contractor under section 18.1 and 18.7. ARTICLE 19. MISCELLANEOUS. 19.1. Contract administration: The Ordering Agency shall assist in the day-to-day administration of the Service being provided to it under an Authorization. 19.2. Anti-Deficicncv: Unless otherwise authorized by Public Law or Federal Regulation, nothing contained herein shall be construed as binding the Government to expend, in any one fiscal year, any sum in excess of the appropriation made by Congress for that fiscal year in furtherance of the matter of any Authorization executed in accordance with this Areawide Contract or to involve the Government in an obligation for the future expenditure of monies before an appropriation is made (Anti-Deficiency Act, 31 U.S.C. 1341.A.1). 19.3. Obligation to Serve: Nothing contained in this Areawide Contract shall obligate the Contractor to take any action which it may consider to be detrimental to its obligations as a public utility. 19.4 Term of Authorizations: It is recognized that during the Term of this Areawide Contract, situations and/or requirements may arise where it may be desirable that the term of service to an Ordering Agency's facility extend beyond the Term of this Areawide Contract. In such event, the particular Authorization involved may specify a term extending beyond the Term of this Areawide Contract, provided that it is within the contracting authority of the Ordering Agency and appropriate termination liability provisions have been negotiated between the Contractor and Ordering Agency to address unamortized balances for connection charge or energy management service projects. 19.5. Indemnification: Any indemnification language contained in standard form agreements executed between the Ordering Agency and the Contractor shall be binding upon the Federal Government only to the extent authorized by opinions of the Government Accountability Office and the Federal Torts Claims Act. 19.6. Waiver of Sovereign Immunity: Any language contained in standard form agreements executed between the Ordering Agency and the Contractor shall not be construed to waive the federal government’s sovereign immunity, and may not be applicable where the federal government's sovereign immunity has not otherwise been waived by statutory law. 19.7. Davis Bacon Act: Since this Areawide Public Utility Contract does not involve the regulated utility company performing on a Federally funded or assisted contract for the construction, alteration, or repair of a public work and/or public facility, the Davis Bacon Act does not apply to the work to be performed by the regulated utility company in connection with the provision of regulated utility services. However, if a determination by the Department of Labor (DOL) differs, the regulated utility company will be solely responsible for any financial liability for any contrary determination by DOL. TN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have executed this Areawide Contract as of the day and the year first above written. UNITED STATES OF AMERICA Acting through the Administrator of General Services By: GSA, PBS, Energy Division Contracting Officer ATTEST: COMMONWEALTH EDISON COMPANY Title:.SMf; ATTEST: By:                                    _ Title:       ClJ'lK         I S </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6CA47B21-3A97-4A5D-A98C-3205F9FBD3B1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2955</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2964</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8470AF0E-93BB-4CC0-828F-049A3A598421"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5D56DB49-7F17-4504-B89B-8A37B609C57D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2955</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2956</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8470AF0E-93BB-4CC0-828F-049A3A598421"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3AA9012F-08C5-4387-8585-2512D26710EE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2957</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2964</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8470AF0E-93BB-4CC0-828F-049A3A598421"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">150000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>