<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369977" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode12C3943C-7933-4FB5-A6CF-AECB8B1E5331">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode532C8CD0-54B7-469C-9831-11A875DC3778">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode79348A90-ABE0-4AE1-8F3A-BBB403E99533">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">03-31-06 HCA HEALTH SERVICES OF TENNESSEE, d/b/a CENTENNIAL MEDICAL CENTER 2300 Patterson Street Nashville, Tennessee 37203 CONTRACT FOR STUDENT CLINICAL TRAINING AND PRACTICE For the purpose of providing clinical training and practice for students and in consideration of the mutual convenants contained herein, it is hereby agreed by and between (Facility) Centennial Medical Center, Nashville, Tennessee and (Institution) Name: Tennessee Board of Regents (TBR), on behalf of its six (6) universities as follows: Austin Peay State University, East Tennessee State University, Middle Tennessee State University, Tennessee Technological University, University of Memphis Address: Tennessee Board of Regents, 1415 Murfreesboro Pike, Suite 350, Nashville, TN 37217 Type of Program: Master of Science in Nursing, Regents Online Degree Programs to provide clinical experience for students enrolled in certain programs of the Institution. Both parties have agreed to the terms and provisions set forth below: The specific services to be provided students are described as follows: I.       Terms and Conditions: Pursuant to the above-stated purpose, the parties agree as follows: A.      Terms: 1.       This agreement will become effective on the date that it is executed by all the designated representatives of both Parties to the agreement and shall extend for a period of 12 months from that date. 2.       Renewals of the agreement may become effective with a) letter-of-intent submitted by the Institution 30 days preceding the contract expiration date, and b) agreement of both parties, provided no changes are made in the original agreement. This agreement may be renewed with written approval of all parties for a total term of up to five years. 3.       If either party desires a revision in, an amendment to, or the termination of this agreement, written notice must be provided to the other party at least 30 days prior to the designated termination date of the agreement. Students currently enrolled in the program at the Facility at the time of notice of termination, shall be given the opportunity to complete their clinical program at Facility, such completion not to exceed six (6) months. 4.       No revision in or amendment to this agreement shall be valid until such revision or amendment is in writing and is executed by all parties hereto. 5.       This agreement contains all of the agreements among the parties with respect to its subject matter and supersedes any and all other agreements, either oral or in writing, among the parties hereto with respect to the subject matter hereof. B.       Institution Specific Responsibilities: The following duties shall be the specific responsibilities of the Institution: 1.       Assume full responsibility for the planning, implementation, modification or revision of the academic educational programs in the Institution with participation (if applicable) by the clinical staffs of the Facility. The Institution is responsible for preparing its students for both the academic and clinical components of their education. 2.       Appoint a person as the Academic Coordinator of Clinical Education for the Institution to serve as the liaison for the Institution, the Facility and the students. The Institution will provide the name of this individual to the Facility. 3.       Follow channels of communication in planning experiences within the Facility by arranging schedules for students’ observation and/or practical assignments at the Facility in cooperation with the Facility liaison appointee as indicated within this Agreement. All students, faculty, employees, agents and representatives of Institution participating in the Program at the Facility shall be accountable to the Facility's Administrator. 4.       Recommend and select for assignment at the Facility only those students who have satisfactorily completed the prerequisites (education, experience, and competency appropriate for assigned responsibilities) for the Clinical Practicums. 5.       Provide written notice to the Facility at least 14 days prior to the beginning of the academic term of the number and names of students who will be assigned there for clinical experience. 6.       Provide the following information in writing: a.       Behavioral objectives for the learning experience; b.       Types of activities in which the students will participate; c.       Educational needs of the students; d.       Evaluation methodologies and materials; e.       The level of students in the program; and f.        A schedule for student orientation and clinical experience. 7.        Provide a ratio of 1 faculty to 8 students and select all of the following that apply. □  An Institution faculty member will be present and responsible for the student’s supervision during the clinical experience. □  The Institution shall provide on-site faculty at the Facility on a regular basis to be defined as one day every two weeks during the clinical experience. The Institution shall appoint a preceptor who will be present and responsible for the student’s action. □  The Institution shall appoint a Facility member preceptor who will be present and responsible for the student’s action. 8.       Assure that students participating in the program are informed of the requirement to comply and adhere to all Facility and administrative policies, procedures, and requirements. 9.       The Institution and its agents, program participants, faculty, representatives and employees agree to keep strictly confidential and hold in trust all confidential information of Facility and/or its patients and not disclose or reveal any confidential information to any third party without the express prior written consent of Facility except as required by law. Institution shall not disclose the terms of this Agreement to any person who is not a party to this Agreement, except as required by law or as authorized by Facility. Unauthorized disclosure of confidential information or of the terms of this Agreement shall be a material breach of this Agreement and shall provide Facility with the option of pursuing remedies for breach, or, notwithstanding any other provision of this Agreement, immediately terminating this Agreement upon written notice to Institution. 10.      Institution shall require each individual Program Participant to obtain and maintain, occurrence-type general and professional liability insurance coverage in amounts not less than $ 1,000,000 per occurrence and $ 3,000,000 annual aggregate per Program Participant, with insurance carriers or self insurance programs approved by Facility and covering the acts and omissions of Program Participants. If such coverage is provided on a claims-made basis, then such insurance shall continue throughout the term of this Agreement and upon the termination of this Agreement, or the expiration or cancellation of the insurance, Institution shall require each individual Program Participant to purchase, tail coverage for a period of three years after the termination of this Agreement or the expiration or cancellation of the claim-made coverage (said tail coverage shall be in amounts and type equivalent to the claims-made coverage). The State of Tennessee is self-insured including, among other things, worker compensation and unemployment compensation. Any and all claims against the State of Tennessee, including the Institution or its employees, shall be heard and determined by the Tennessee Claims Commission in the manner prescribed by law. Damages recoverable against the Institution shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Claims Commission pursuant to T.C.A. Section 9-8-301, et. seq. 11.      Be responsible for the determination of a student’s final grade. 12.      Establish a procedure for notifying the Facility if a student (or faculty, if applicable) is unable for any reason to report for a clinical assignment. 13.      Inform students that they will not submit for publication any material relating to the clinical education experience without prior written approval from the Institution and the Facility. 14.      Cooperate in the evaluation activities of the Facility. 15.      Prior to clinical rotation, the Institution shall provide the Facility the CMC Student/Subject Roster form (Attachment A), the Attestation of Satisfactory Background Investigation Report form (Attachment B) and proof of malpractice liability insurance for each student. Institution shall also provide, upon request of Facility for Facility audit purposes, documentation of the following items: a.        Licensure: All faculty have current certification, licensure, or registration if required; b.       Information on criminal background: Institution shall, in a timely manner at either Institution’s expense for its faculty or the Program Participant’s expense for students, require to have conducted a background check on each and every student assigned to the Program and every member of the staff/faculty responsible for supervision and/or instruction at Facility. If Institution has students or staff/faculty on-site at Facility prior to the execution of this Agreement, then Institution shall immediately conduct or require to have conducted a retrospective background check on such persons. The background check for students shall include, at a minimum, the following: •   Social Security Number Verification; •   Criminal Search (7 years or up to 5 criminal searches); •   Violent Sexual Offender and Predator Registry Search; •   HHS/OIG List of Excluded Individuals/Entities; •   GSA List of Parties Excluded from Federal Programs; •   U.S. Treasury, Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC), List of Specially Designated Nationals (SDN); •   Applicable State Exclusion List, if one. The background check for staff/faculty, if licensed or certified caregivers, shall include all of the above and, in addition, shall include the following: •    Education verification (highest level); •    Professional License Verification; •   Certification &amp; Designations Check; and •   Professional Disciplinary Action Search. If the background check results in any adverse information revealed by the entity conducting the background check, Institution shall notify Facility of this fact and, after redacting the individual’s name and other personally identifiable information from the report, forward to the Facility the detailed background check results. Facility shall then analyze the results in accord with Section C. 17 below. Criteria for Exclusion of Students/Faculty from Clinical Placements includes: History of Criminal Convictions •   Any felony conviction within past 7 years; •   Any Class A misdemeanor within the last 5 years; and/or •   Any Class B misdemeanor within the last 2 years. Other findings that would exclude placement include: •   Persons on the registry maintained by the Department of Health pursuant to T.C.A. 68-11-1004; •   Persons listed on the GSA/HHS/O1G list of excluded individuals; •   Persons listed on the U.S. Treasury Department’s Office of Foreign Assets Control list of Specially Designation Nationals; and •   Encumbered license in a health-related field. Warranty of Non-exclusion: Facility reserves the right to terminate this contract and/or exclude any program participant upon the finding that Institution or any program participant has been: (1) excluded, debarred or otherwise become ineligible to participate in the Federal health care programs as defined in 42 U.S.C. Section 1320a-7b(f) (the “Federal health care programs”); (ii) convicted of a criminal offense related to the provision of health care items or services but has not yet been excluded, debarred or otherwise declared ineligible to participate in the Federal health care programs; or, (iii) is under investigation or otherwise aware of any circumstances which may result in the Institution or a program participant being excluded from participation in the Federal health care programs. Institution shall immediately notify Facility of any change it becomes aware of concerning Institution or any program participant with regard to any status indicated above. Any breach of this section shall give Facility the right to terminate this Agreement immediately for cause. c.       Health Records: Compliance with applicable health screening requirements established by Facility.- All on-site faculty and students have evidence of good health as evidenced by an approved, acceptable, satisfactory physical examination and record of up-to-date immunizations (annual tuberculin skin test and/or screening or chest x-ray, Hepatitis B vaccine and Rubella immunity), if required. If rotating in Obstetrics, NICU, or Well Baby Nursery, Varicella immunity will be proven; d.       Basic Life Saving: All on-site faculty and students have completed requirements for a Basic Life Saving course as appropriate for their training and shall remain current in this requirement; e.       Infection Control: All on-site faculty and students have received training about Bloodborne Pathogens and Universal Precautions. On-site faculty and students will report for TB Mask fit-testing prior to entering negative pressure isolation rooms; and f.        Centennial Medical Center Orientation: All on-site faculty and students have received an orientation to the Centennial Medical Center and Documentation Systems. C.       Facility Specific Responsibilities: The following duties shall be the specific responsibilities of the Facility: 1.       Retain complete responsibility for patient care providing adequate supervision of students (and faculty, if applicable) at all times. 2.       Appoint a person as the Academic Coordinator of Clinical Education for the Facility to serve as the liaison for the Facility, the Institution and the students. The Facility will provide the name of this individual to the Institution. 3.       Maintain a sufficient level of staff employees to carry out regular duties. Students will not be expected nor allowed to perform services in lieu of staff employees. 4.       Facility will provide emergency care if needed for illness or injuries suffered during clinical experience. Such treatment shall be at the expense of the individual treated. 5.       Maintain all applicable accreditation requirements and certify such compliance to the Institution or other entity as requested by the Institution. The Facility shall also permit authorities responsible for accreditation of the Institution's curriculum to inspect the Facility’s clinical facilities and services as necessary. 6.       Participate in conferences with the Institution’s faculty as deemed necessary and desirable concerning the program. 7.       Provide working and/or study space for the participating students and to make clinical resources and services available as may be considered necessary to the successful operation of the program and in accordance with the policies of the Facility. 8.       Orientation options: □  Provide orientation for faculty and students; and □   The Facility shall provide orientation to the Institution’s on site faculty. This orientation shall include Facility and Documentation System orientation. The Institution’s on-site faculty shall complete student Facility and Documentation System orientation prior to placement at the Facility. The Facility shall complete student departmental orientation after placement at the Facility. 9.       Participate in periodic evaluation of the program. 10.      The Facility, as appropriate, shall note the completion of clinical skills by return demonstration. Return demonstration shall not imply certification or credentialling. 11.      Agrees to notify Institution of any incident or occurrence which could result in a liability and will fully cooperate and assist in its investigation of said incident or occurrence. 12.      Be responsible for and retain absolute control over the organization, administration, operation and financing of its services. The Facility must carry professional liability insurance for staff and general liability insurance for the Facility. 13.     Reserve the right to request the Institution to withdraw a student or faculty member from the assigned clinical education experience when his/her clinical performance is unsatisfactory or his/her behavior is disruptive or detrimental to the Facility and/or the patient. In such event, said Program Participant s participation in the Program at Facility shall immediately cease. It is understood that only Institution can dismiss the Program Participant from the Program. 14.      Provide for the student a patient caseload that is appropriate to his/her needs and level of experience and proficiency and that of sufficient size and variety to insure the best educational experience possible. 15.     Allow students to participate in non-treatment learning experiences such as Facility/unit rounds, clinics, staff conferences, inservice education program, special lectures, observations and similar activities as they become available and at the discretion of the appropriate Department Director. 16.      Notify the Institution in writing of any changes within the Facility that would alter significantly the specified clinical education experiences for the student. 17.      It shall be the responsibility of the Facility to analyze background check information containing adverse findings forwarded to it by Institution and to determine whether the person to whom the records pertain is eligible to participate in the clinical programs at its facility. If Facility determines that a student or faculty/staff member shall not participate at its facility, Facility shall so notify the Institution within 3 business days of receipt of the background check and Institution shall notify the individual concerned. Institution shall ensure that this individual does not participate in the clinical program at the Facility. D.       Student Specific Responsibilities: Institution shall inform its students that the following duties shall be the specific responsibilities of the students: 1.       Abide by existing policies, rules and regulations of the Facility when engaged in caring for patients in the Facility. 2.       Wear appropriate attire as mutually determined between the Institution and the Facility. Must wear a nametag that includes title and school affiliation at all times. 3.       Responsible for their own transportation to and from the clinical area. 4.       Remain on the Facility premises for breaks, including meals. Be responsible for own meals during clinical hours. E.       Mutual Responsibilities: The parties shall cooperate to fulfill the following mutual responsibilities: 1.       Each party shall comply with all Federal, State, and Municipal laws, advice, rules and regulations, which are applicable to the performance of this Agreement. 2.       The parties hereby acknowledge that they are independent contractors, and neither the Institution nor any of its agents, representatives, Program Participants, or employees shall be considered agents, representatives, or employees of Facility. In no event shall this Agreement be construed as establishing a partnership or joint venture or similar relationship between the parties hereto. Institution shall be liable for its own debts, obligations, acts and omissions, including the payment of all required withholding, social security and other taxes or benefits. No Program Participant shall look to Facility for any salaries, insurance or other benefits. No Program Participant or other third person is entitled to, and shall not, receive any rights under this Agreement. 3.       Any courtesy appointments to faculty or staff by either the Institution or the Facility shall be without entitlement of the individual to compensation or benefits from the appointing party. The Facility’s staff will receive no monetary compensation from the Institution for participation in the clinical education program. 4.       The parties agree to comply with Title VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, and Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246 and the related regulations to each. There shall be no discrimination on the basis of race, national origin, religion, creed, sex, age, veteran status, or handicap in either the selection of students for participation in the Program, or as to any aspect of the clinical training; provided, however, that with respect to handicap, the handicap must not be such as would, even with reasonable accommodation, in and of itself preclude the Program Participant's effective participation in the Program. 5.       The confidentiality of patient records and student records shall be maintained at all times. 6.        While enrolled in clinical experience at the Facility, students (and faculty, if applicable) will be subject to applicable policies of the Institution and the Facility. The rules, regulations and procedures will be available to the student through the appropriate Department Director. Students shall be dismissed from participation in the Institution’s program only after the appropriate policies and procedures of the Institution have been followed; however, the Facility may immediately remove from the premises any student who poses an immediate threat or danger. The Institution, the students and the Facility (staff) are expected to conduct themselves in accordance with the Code of Ethics as set forth by the State of Tennessee and the Facility. F.     HIPAA Requirements The parties agree to comply with the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996, as codified at 42 U.S.C. Section 1320d (“HIPAA”) and any current and future regulations promulgated thereunder, including, without limitation, the federal privacy regulations contained in 45 C.F.R. Parts 160 and 164 (“Federal Privacy Regulations”), the federal security standards contained in 45 C.F.R. Part 142 (“Federal Security Regulations”), and the federal standards for electronic transactions contained in 45 C.F.R. Parts 160 and 162, all collectively referred to herein as “HIPAA Requirements”. The parties agree not to use or further disclose any Protected Health Information (as defined in 45 C.F.R. Section 164.501) or Individually Identifiable Health Information (as defined in 42 U.S.C. Section 1320d), other than as permitted by the HIPAA Requirements and the terms of this Agreement. The parties agree to make their internal practices, books and records relating to the use and disclosure of Protected Health Information available to the Secretary of Health and Human Services to the extent required for determining compliance with the Federal Privacy Regulations. In addition, the parties agree to comply with any state laws and regulations that govern or pertain to the confidentiality, privacy, security of, and electronic and transaction code sets pertaining to, information related to patients. Institution shall direct its Program Participants to comply with the policies and procedures of Facility, including those governing the use and disclosure of individually identifiable health information under federal law, specifically 45 CFR parts 160 and 164. Solely for the purpose of defining the Program Participants' role in relation to the use and disclosure of Facility's protected health information, the Program Participants are defined as members of the Facility's workforce, as that term is defined by 45 CFR 160.103, when engaged in activities pursuant to this Agreement. However, the Program Participants are not and shall not be considered to be employees of Facility. G.      Miscellaneous Terms: The following terms shall apply in the interpretation and performance of this Agreement: 1.       Neither party shall be responsible for personal injury or property damage or loss except that resulting from its own negligence or the negligence of its employees or others for whom the party is legally responsible. The delay or failure of performance by either party shall not constitute default under the terms of this Agreement, nor shall it give rise to any claims against either party for damages. The sole remedy for breach of this Agreement shall be immediate termination of this Agreement. 3.       Institution may not assign or transfer any of its rights, duties or obligations under this Agreement, in whole or in part, without the prior written consent of Facility. This Agreement shall inure to the benefit of, and be binding upon, the parties hereto and their respective successors and permitted assigns. 4.       Nothing in this Agreement requires or obligates Institution to admit or cause the admittance of a patient to Facility or to use Facility’s services. None of the benefits granted pursuant to this Agreement is conditioned on any requirement or expectation that the parties make referrals to, be in a position to make or influence referrals to, or otherwise generate business for the other party. Neither party is restricted from referring any services to, or otherwise generating any business for, any other entity of their choosing. 5.       No Waiver: Any failure of a party to enforce that party's right under any provision of this Agreement shall not be construed or act as a waiver of said party's subsequent right to enforce any of the provisions contained herein. 6.       Notices: All notices hereunder by either party to the other shall be in writing, delivered personally, by certified or registered mail, return receipt requested, or by overnight courier, and shall be deemed to have been duly given when delivered personally or when deposited in the United States mail. 7.       Lori Stephens is the Coordinator for Nursing &amp; Allied for the TBR Regents Online Degree Programs and can be reached at (phone) 615-366-3936 or (email) lori.stephens@tbr.edu. 8.       Lee Ann Hanna, Director of Education, is the Coordinator for the Facility and can be reached at (phone) 615-342-3951, (fax) 615-342-3990, or (e-mail)</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode89073B46-7C71-4162-9EE9-F694ED7BC08A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6478</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6489</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode532C8CD0-54B7-469C-9831-11A875DC3778"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6ED5186C-B950-43F1-9E49-292A811EC5E3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6478</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6479</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode532C8CD0-54B7-469C-9831-11A875DC3778"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD5442836-9F2A-4720-BD5E-BF31A121F3A6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6480</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6489</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode532C8CD0-54B7-469C-9831-11A875DC3778"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF6E7BE89-EA14-41E4-B11F-85F100BE3AE0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6509</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6520</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode12C3943C-7933-4FB5-A6CF-AECB8B1E5331"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode45A7CCAE-469B-46D8-9677-27B20BD50DB2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6509</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6510</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode12C3943C-7933-4FB5-A6CF-AECB8B1E5331"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF8756E87-0E93-4EA6-A5F5-9CA1DFFD80FD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6511</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6520</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode12C3943C-7933-4FB5-A6CF-AECB8B1E5331"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>