<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369887" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeDB3C16CA-00E6-4080-9E82-D45ACCED4F95">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">DOLLARS</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode5E369750-D44A-4C81-875A-4AAEC95FC45D">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">CONTRACT BETWEEN , TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS AND PELLISSIPPI STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE This Contract, by and between TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS, hereinafter referred to as the “Institution” and PELLISSIPPI STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE, hereinafter referred to as the “Contractor," is for the provision of PERKINS REPORTING, as further defined in the "SCOPE OF SERVICES." The Contractor is a State Agency. The Contractor’s address is: 10915 HARDIN VALLEY ROAD KNOXVILLE, TN 37933 The Contractor’s place of incorporation or organization is State of Tennessee. A. SCOPE OF SERVICES: A. 1.   Tennessee Board of Regents Community Colleges are under new federal Perkins reporting requirements. Reporting requires data collection, storage, quality, and communication. The contract provides for statistical, database, reporting, and technical services necessary for institutional reporting of the Perkins requirements to the Tennessee Board of Regents and the federal government. (See attachment A - Performance Narrative and Documentation for more detail.) B.    CONTRACT TERM: B. 1.   Contract Term. This Contract shall be effective for the period commencing on SEPTEMBER 26, 2007 and ending on JUNE 30, 2008. The Institution shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. C.    PAYMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS: C.1. Maximum Liability. In no event shall the maximum liability of the Institution under this Contract exceed FIVE THOUSAND DOLLARS ($5,000), inclusive of travel expenses. The maximum liability represents available funds for payment to the Contractor and does not guarantee payment of any such funds to the Contractor under this Contract unless the Institution requests work and the Contractor performs said work. C.2. Compensation Firm. The Service Rates and the Maximum Liability of the Institution under this Contract are firm for the duration of the Contract and are not subject to escalation for any reason unless amended. C.3. Payment Methodology. The Contractor shall be compensated based on the Service Rates herein for units of service authorized by the Institution in a total amount not to exceed the Contract Maximum Liability established in Section C.1. The Contractor’s compensation shall be contingent upon the satisfactory completion of units of service or project milestones defined in Section A. The Contractor shall submit an invoice, in form and substance acceptable to the Institution with all of the necessary supporting documentation, prior to any payment. C.4. Travel Compensation. Compensation to the Contractor for travel, meals and/or lodging in connection to work performed under this Contract shall be in the amount of actual cost to the Contractor, subject to the maximum amounts and limitations specified in the State Comprehensive Travel Regulations, as they may be from time to time amended. Compensation to the contractor for travel shall be limited to 10 percent of the total contract. C.5. Payment of Invoice. The payment of the invoice by the Institution shall not prejudice the Institution's right to object to or question any invoice or matter in relation thereto. Such payment by the Institution shall neither be construed as acceptance of any part of the work or service provided nor as an approval of any of the amounts invoiced therein. C.6. Invoice Reductions. The Contractor's invoice shall be subject to reduction for amounts included in any invoice or payment theretofore made which are determined by the Institution, on the basis of audits conducted in accordance with the terms of this contract, not to constitute proper remuneration for compensable services. C. 7.   Deductions. The Institution reserves the right to deduct from amounts which are or shall become due and payable to the Contractor under this or any contract between the Contractor and the Institution any amounts which are or shall become due and payable to the Institution by the Contractor. D.    STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS: D.1. Required Approvals. The Institution is not bound by this Contract until it is approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee Institution laws and regulations. D.2. Modification and Amendment. This Contract may be modified only by a written amendment executed by all parties hereto and approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee Institution laws and regulations. D.3. Termination for Convenience. The Institution may terminate this Contract without cause for any reason. Said termination shall not be deemed a Breach of Contract by the Institution. The Institution shall give the Contractor at least ninety (90) days written notice before the effective termination date. The Contractor shall be entitled to receive compensation for satisfactory, authorized service completed as of the termination date, but in no event shall the Institution be liable to the Contractor for compensation for any service which has not been rendered. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to any actual general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. D.4. Termination for Cause. If the Contractor fails to properly perform its obligations under this Contract in a timely or proper manner, or if the Contractor violates any terms of this Contract, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate the Contract and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for completed services. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the Institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Contract by the Contractor. D.5. Subcontracting. The Contractor shall not assign this Contract or enter into a subcontract for any of the services performed under this Contract without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution. If such subcontracts are approved by the Institution, they shall contain, at a minimum, sections of this Contract pertaining to "Conflicts of Interest" and "Nondiscrimination" (sections D.6. and D.7.). Notwithstanding any use of approved subcontractors, the Contractor shall be the prime contractor and shall be responsible for all work performed. D.6. Nondiscrimination. The Contractor hereby agrees, warrants, and assures that no person shall be excluded from participation in, be denied benefits of, or be otherwise subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Contract or in the employment practices of the Contractor on the grounds of disability, age, race, color, religion, sex, veteran status, national origin, or any other classification protected by Federal, or Tennessee constitutional or statutory law. The Contractor shall, upon request, show proof of such nondiscrimination and shall post in conspicuous places, available to all employees and applicants, notices of nondiscrimination. D.7. Records. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this Contract. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this contract, shall be maintained for a period of three (3) full years from the date of the final payment and shall be subject to audit at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice by the Institution, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. The financial statements shall be prepared in accordance with generally accepted accounting principles. D.8. Monitoring. The Contractor’s activities conducted and records maintained pursuant to this Contract shall be subject to monitoring and evaluation by the Institution, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. D.9. Progress Reports. The Contractor shall annually submit brief, periodic, progress reports to the Institution as requested. D.10. Strict Performance. Failure bv anv Dartv to this Contract to insist in anv one or more cases upon the strict performance of any of the terms, covenants, conditions, or provisions of this Contract shall not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of any such term, covenant, condition, or provision. No term or condition of this Contract shall be held to be waived, modified, or deleted except by a written amendment signed by the parties hereto. D.11. Institution Liability. The Institution shall have no liability except as SDecificallv provided in this Contract. D.12. Force Maieure. The obligations of the parties to this contract are subject to Drevention bv causes bevond the parties’ control that could not be avoided by the exercise of due care including, but not limited to, acts of God, riots, wars, epidemics or any other similar cause. D.13. Institution and Federal ComDliance. The Contractor shall comDlv with all aDDlicable State and Federal laws and regulations, including Institution policies and guidelines in the performance of this Contract. D.14. Governina Law. This Contract shall be governed bv and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee. The Contractor agrees that it will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Tennessee Claims Commission in actions that may arise under this Contract. The Contractor acknowledges and agrees that any rights or claims against the Institution or its employees hereunder, and any remedies arising therefrom, shall be subject to and limited to those rights and remedies, if any, available under Tennessee Code Annotated, Sections 9-8-101 through 9-8-407. D.15. Completeness. This Contract is complete and contains the entire understanding between the Darties relating to the subject matter contained herein, including all the terms and conditions of the parties’ agreement. This Contract supersedes any and all prior understandings, representations, negotiations, and agreements between the parties relating hereto, whether written or oral. D.16. Severability. If anv terms and conditions of this Contract are held to be invalid or unenforceable as a matter of law, the other terms and conditions hereof shall not be affected thereby and shall remain in full force and effect. To this end, the terms and conditions of this Contract are declared severable. D.17. Headings. Section headings of this Contract are for reference Durooses onlv and shall not be construed as part of this Contract. E.    SPECIAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS: E. 1.    Communications and Contacts. The Institution: GREGORY J. SCHUTZ DIRECTOR OF INSTITUTIONAL EFFECTIVENESS AND ASSESSMENT TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS 1415 MURFREESBORO ROAD, SUITE 372 NASHVILLE, TN 37217 (615)366-3933 Fax: (615)366-4464 The Contractor: SHARON YARBROUGH DIRECTOR OF INSTITUTIONAL RESEARCH PELLISSIPPI STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE 10915 HARDIN VALLEY ROAD KNOXVILLE, TN 37933 (865)694-6526 All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications shall be sent in a manner that verifies proof of delivery. Any communication by facsimile transmission shall also be sent by United States mail on the same date of the facsimile transmission. All communications which relate to any changes to the contract shall not be considered effective until agreed to, in writing, by both parties. E.2. Subject to Funds Availability. The Contract is subject to the appropriation and availability of Institution and/or Federal funds. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, the Institution reserves the right to terminate the Contract upon written notice to the Contractor. Said termination shall not be deemed a breach of Contract by the Institution. Upon receipt of the written notice, the Contractor shall cease all work associated with the Contract. Should such an event occur, the Contractor shall be entitled to compensation for all satisfactory and authorized services completed as of the termination date. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to recover from the Institution any actual, general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. E.3. Institution Ownership of Work Products. The Institution shall have all ownership right, title, and interest, including ownership of copyright, in all work products created, designed, developed, derived, documented, installed, or delivered to the Institution under this Contract. The Institution shall have unlimited rights to use, disclose, reproduce, or publish, for any purpose whatsoever, all said work products. The Contractor shall furnish such information and data upon request of the Institution, in accordance with the Contract and applicable Institution law. E.4. Printing Authorization. The Contractor agrees that no publication coming within the jurisdiction of Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 12-7-101, et. seq., shall be printed unless a printing authorization number has been obtained and affixed as required by Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 12-7-103 (d). E.5. Competitive Procurements. If this Contract provides for reimbursement of the cost of goods, materials, supplies, equipment, or services. Such procurements shall be made on a competitive basis, where practical. E.6. Prohibited Advertising. The Contractor shall not refer to this Contract or the Contractor’s relationship with the Institution hereunder in commercial advertising in such a manner as to state or imply that the Contractor or the Contractor's services are endorsed. Er?:--Copyrights and Patents. The Contractor agrees to indemnify and hold harmless the Institution as well as itoofficcra, agcnto, end cmployceofrem and againot any and all claims or suite-whioh may be brought •against tho InotitutieR for infringomont of any lawo regarding patents or oopyrighto which may arioo from thc-Gentractor’o performance of thia Contract: In any 3uch action brought against the Institution, the ■ Contractor shall.satisfy and indemnify the-lnstitution for the amount-ofeny final judgment for infringement. The Contractor further agrees-it-shall be liable-for the reasonable fees of attorneys for the Institution in the event-such, service is nocossitatod to onforoo tho terms of thio Contract or otherwise enforee the ■ obligations of the Contractor to the Institution. Tho Institution shall givo tho Contraotor written notioo ef PELLISSIPPI STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE Signature -fcejliss/ Print Name a TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS: Charles W. Manning, Chancellor % Date </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCB458F71-848A-4476-A139-4BBB1B43ABA9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1498</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1519</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeDB3C16CA-00E6-4080-9E82-D45ACCED4F95"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9EEDD7D5-35CB-4AE0-8645-2975743139C1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1498</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1511</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeDB3C16CA-00E6-4080-9E82-D45ACCED4F95"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode02AFC53B-7E30-4131-9ADD-A67E7C4B5026">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1512</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1519</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeDB3C16CA-00E6-4080-9E82-D45ACCED4F95"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">DOLLARS</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>