<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369966" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEE2D672-7748-434C-B06E-15CD22B3C903">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">10.82</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0A6694B-FFAF-4687-B662-058BE169B8C0">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN DYERSBURG STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND MURRAY GUARD, INC. This Agreement is made this 17™ day of November, 2008, by and between DYERSBURG STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE, hereinafter referred to as the "Institution", and MURRAY GUARD, INC., hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: 1.     The Contractor shall furnish uniformed security officers and services for the proper protection of protected property. The specific details of the number of officers, number of days, work hours and general and personnel specifications are attached as Appendix A , Appendix B and Addendums 1 and 2. 2.     The Contractor shall furnish the unarmed security officers to provide such protection service, completely outfitted with neat, clean and properly fitted uniforms and necessary equipment. Uniforms must display a badge identifying the wearer as a security guard and the emblem or logo of the company sewn or otherwise firmly attached to the shirt and/or coat. 3.     Such security officers shall be employees of the Contractor and the Contractor shall pay all salaries and expenses of (and all Federal Social Security Taxes, Federal and State Unemployment Taxes and any similarly related taxes) such employees. The contractor further agrees to comply with all Federal, State and Local Wage and Hour Laws applicable to all security officers and other personnel furnished under this contract. 4.     The Contractor agrees to furnish and keep in full force the following minimum insurance and coverage: a. Worker’s Compensation Insurance covering all persons employed by the Contractor in the performance of the services hereunder not less than that required by the State of Tennessee. llPa^e b.    Comprehensive General Liability, Errors and Omissions, Property Care, Custody and Control and Contractual Liability Insurance covering liabilities for property damage and bodily injury to or death of persons arising out of the performance of this contract in the minimum amount of One Million Dollars ($1,000,000) per injury and per occurrence. c.     Personal Injury Liability Insurance covering false arrest, detention or imprisonment, malicious prosecution, libel, slander, defamation, violation of right of privacy, wrongful entry or eviction, or other invasion of privacy occupancy in the minimum amount of One Million Dollars ($1,000,000) per occurrence. d.     Automobile Liability Insurance covering liabilities for bodily injury and property damage in the minimum amount of One Million Dollars ($1,000,000) per occurrence. e.    Commercial Blanket Bond Coverage in the state amount of One Million Dollars ($1,000,000) to protect against direct losses of Money, Securities and other Property caused by Theft or Forgery of any identifiable Employee(s) of the Contractor, acting alone or in collusion with others. 5.     Without limiting responsibility of the contractor for the proper conduct of the security officers and the protection of the protected property, the conduct of the security officers is to be guided by a set standard of written procedures as agreed upon between the Contractor and the College, and such other special written instructions applicable to the services as may be directed by the College from time to time through its designated agents. 6.     The Contractor is responsible for the direct supervision of the security officers through its designated representative at the premises to which the contract relates and such representative will, in turn, be available at all reasonable times to report to and confer with the designated agents of the College with respect to the services to be rendered hereunder. a 7. The Contractor agrees that the security services covered by this agreement shall be performed in conformity with the College’s policies and procedures. College may require the Contractor to immediately remove any employee(s) from the property should it be determined that individuals are being assigned to duty who are unqualified for either suitability or security reasons, or who are found unfit for performing security duties during their tour of duty. The Contractor further agrees to remove from service hereunder any of its employees who may be guilty of improper conduct or are not qualified or needed to perform the work assigned. B. The Institution agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1.     $10.82 cost per man hour of security services furnished. College will not pay premium time or over-time pay for holidays, special events at off-campus locations or sporting events on campus. The number of security hours and personnel may be increased or decreased by the College as the situation demands. Temporary requirements in excel of the basic coverage are included in the scheduling detail in the attached Appendix A. The Contractor will provide special extraordinary coverage in the event of civil disorders, labor disputes, disasters, or similar situations at a special coverage rate negotiated between the parties equitable with the specific requirements of the situation. In the event of an increase in the minimum wage by any Federal, State, or Municipal Legislation enacted to become effective during the term of this Agreement, the rate for the services provided herein shall be subject for renegotiation between the parties hereto. 2.    The Contractor shall furnish the College, as requested, with daily time sheets and shift reports. Invoices are to be mailed to DSCC, Accounts Payable, 1510 Lake Road, Dyersburg, TN 38024. 3.    Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, provided that payments shall be made only upon submittal of invoices by the Contractor, and after performance of the portion of the services which the invoiced amount represents. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Agreement. If the Contractor is a non-resident alien, payment of any portion of the contract from any source will not be made by the Institution until an Individual Taxpayer Identification Number or Social Security Number has been assigned to the Contractor by the Internal Revenue Service and Immigration Naturalization Service and presented to the Institution. 4. In no event shall the liability of the Institution under this contract exceed amount referenced in section B1 and/or Appendix A and Addendums 1 and 2. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement. 1.    The Contractor warrants that no part of the total contract amount provided herein shall be paid directly or indirectly to any officer or employee of the state of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, sub-Contractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this Agreement. If the Contractor is an individual, the Contractor warrants that within the past six months he/she has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2.    The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3.    Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference as Attachment I. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. 4.    The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of this Institution, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, to pay all taxes incident hereunto, and otherwise protect and hold the Institution harmless from any and all liability not specifically provided for in this agreement. 5.    The term of this contract shall be from January 1,2009 to December 31, 2009, renewable upon mutual agreement by both parties each year thereafter for a total not to exceed five (5) years. 6.    This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 30 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 7.     If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this Agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this Agreement, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate this Agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. 5 I Is a a. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Agreement by the Contractor. 8.    This Agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 9.    The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the Institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives* 10.   The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution or Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 11.   The Contractor shall submit to the Institution monthly progress reports if requested by the Institution. 12.   This Agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or designee, the Vice Chancellor for the Tennessee Technology Centers or designee or the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 13.   This Contract shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee. 14.   Included in this Contract by reference are the following documents: a. This Contract document and its attachments, and any addenda and/or amendments to this Agreement hereafter exececuted. b. The Request for Quote 08-0100 and its associated amendments. c. The Contractor’s Proposal dated November 6, 2008. In the event of a discrepancy or ambiguity regarding the interpretation of this Contract, these documents shall govern in order of precedence as listed above. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. MURRAY GUARD, INC DATE:    December 29, 2008 BY: // TITLE:    President DYERSBURG STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE BY: TITLE: ' I           ......— ? 1 • ■ ■ ? Je DATE: / Z - Z APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS BY:           VA TITLE:                 ____________ DATE:  / 2- f- 08___________ 7 | P a g e </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode047AA472-7AD3-442F-AE46-17827CD5E869">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4596</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4602</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEE2D672-7748-434C-B06E-15CD22B3C903"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7E05B1BF-7CF2-4CED-94ED-DAE93F94A19E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4596</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4597</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEE2D672-7748-434C-B06E-15CD22B3C903"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode57A66066-3191-4C00-8436-66B4FDE31C24">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4597</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4602</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEE2D672-7748-434C-B06E-15CD22B3C903"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">10.82</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>