<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369818" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4CD1EA49-127F-4BDE-8F41-F4DBE544A7A2">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">30000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode0C2834B6-1E95-403A-88D6-952A35D67C5F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">50</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode7F58656E-624D-4A54-B45A-B8BFA82CC291">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">07-011Q AGREEMENT BETWEEN MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY AND MOTLOW STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE THIS AGREEMENT, by and between MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY, hereinafter referred to as “University,” and MOTLOW STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE, hereinafter referred to as “College.” WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The University agrees to provide the services of its Internal Audit staff for the purpose of conducting TTC Director’s Expenditures Audits, Enrollment Audits, Lead Institution Audit, Technology Access Fee Audits and Presidential Expenditure Audit as specified in Exhibit A. It is anticipated that the combined time required (including travel) to complete these audits will be approximately 600 auditor hours. Any significant increase in the number of hours required to complete the audit must be approved by the College Vice President for Business Affairs with notice of potential extended hours to be provided at the earliest possible date. All audits are to be performed on a timely basis to the extent possible and submitted to the President of the College for disposition in accordance with Tennessee Board Regents (“Board”) Guideline B 050. It shall be the sole responsibility of the College, with appropriate assistance from University, to negotiate any necessary extension of audit completion dates with Board staff. University agrees to give its beset effort toward completing audits on schedule; however, College agrees that failure by University to complete the audits in a timely manner shall not result in liability to University. B. The College agrees to compensate the University as follows: 1.  $50.00 per hour for all audits costs including travel 2. Payment to be made monthly as billed 3.  Payments to the University shall be made according to this schedule set out above, but only after receipt of invoices for services performed. The final payment shall be made only after the University has completely performed the University’s duties under this Agreement. 4. In no event shall the liability of the College under this Agreement exceed $30,000. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of the Agreement. 07-0110 1.  The term of this contract shall be from July 1, 2006 to June 30, 2007. 2. The College and University will negotiate the scheduling of any special audit request or investigation made by the College. 3. The audit working papers will be retained by the MTSU audit department and be made available to state audit upon request. 4. This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other at least thirty (30) days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the University shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation from any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 5.  The University shall maintain documentation for all charges against the College under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the university, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three (3) full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice, by the College or the Comptroller of the Treasury or their duly appointed representatives. IN WITNESSETH WHEREOF, the parties hereto have caused these presents to be executed on the dates indicated. MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY MOTLOW STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS Date:        II ~ V (p</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode534F9F61-10BA-449D-9602-12FD127AD607">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1767</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1773</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode0C2834B6-1E95-403A-88D6-952A35D67C5F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7ECDCA8E-89F0-4107-9986-38F26E37FCDE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1767</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1768</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode0C2834B6-1E95-403A-88D6-952A35D67C5F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0C6312DD-A937-491F-86E8-F3F686372DA7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1768</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1773</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode0C2834B6-1E95-403A-88D6-952A35D67C5F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">50</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC488057A-67F5-4A8B-A32C-0A45A964FFBF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2214</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2221</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4CD1EA49-127F-4BDE-8F41-F4DBE544A7A2"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEAA3514F-B917-4005-82CE-180C246D497F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2214</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2215</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4CD1EA49-127F-4BDE-8F41-F4DBE544A7A2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC31EC475-74E6-4AFD-886F-9DD43A697C1B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2215</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2221</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4CD1EA49-127F-4BDE-8F41-F4DBE544A7A2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">30000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>