<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369819" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode6B532191-F987-4472-89D8-5F95D72348FB">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3500</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode6C0E6579-A703-4C5D-9DEF-89E73329FC84">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">500</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode02FA5A80-0EC0-4724-9039-8227FC0F62A0">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS AND Terry L. James This agreement, made this 15th day of August, 2006, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as the “institution”, and Terry L. James hereinafter referred to as “contractor.” WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The contractor agrees to perform the following services: To serve as an expert consultant in the review the proposed new Master of Arts in Teaching at Austin Peay State University B. The institution agrees to compensate the contractor as follows: 1. $500 per day for a maximum of four (4) days plus travel expenditures at cost within State guidelines. 2. The above-mentioned amount will be paid upon completion of the review and receipt of the written report. 3. Payments to the contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, but only after the contractor has completely performed his duties under this agreement. 4.  In no event shall the liability of the institution under this contract exceed $3,500.00. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this agreement. 1. The contractor warrants that no part of the total amount provided herein shall be paid directly or indirectly to an officer or employee of the State of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, sub-contractor, or consultant to the contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this agreement. If the contractor is an individual, the contractor warrants that within the past six months he has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2. The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11, 246 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, handicap, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, handicap, veteran status or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3. The term of this contract shall be from August 31, 2006 to October 15, 2006. 4. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 5. The contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the institution under this agreement. The books, records, and documents of the contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 6.  The contractor shall not assign this agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the institution or Board of Regents, as appropriate. Approval shall not be given if the proposed sub-contractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 7.  The contractor shall submit to the institution a final report. 8.  This agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or his or her designee, the Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs or his or her designee, or the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 9. Compensation to the contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be in the amount of actual cost to the contractor, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the Tennessee Board of Regents policies, as they may be from time to time amended. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signature. Title: Date: Tennessee Board of Regents By: Title: _______________________________________ Chancellor, Tennessee Board of Regents Date:</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode10E7E999-5E5D-4D16-8293-AECC23810AFF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">700</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">704</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6C0E6579-A703-4C5D-9DEF-89E73329FC84"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4D4B268E-8648-4278-A638-D48C5738046C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">700</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">701</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6C0E6579-A703-4C5D-9DEF-89E73329FC84"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4C06D4F2-C14B-4064-8547-A3A3ECAC74F1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">701</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">704</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6C0E6579-A703-4C5D-9DEF-89E73329FC84"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">500</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCA1F35AC-B37D-4246-BE78-62E0613C1E2C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1165</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1174</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6B532191-F987-4472-89D8-5F95D72348FB"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode95AC8E34-2CD5-4FF9-82B2-73F9E7D90D0B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1165</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1166</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6B532191-F987-4472-89D8-5F95D72348FB"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB5EDF2CD-F535-4CB7-874F-0807FFEE988F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1166</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1174</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6B532191-F987-4472-89D8-5F95D72348FB"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3500</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>