<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369846" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode84187590-5E1D-40B4-86ED-DB109211E84E">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2110738</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode35F86C73-6D2D-4622-B4A0-22D124BE9A96">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AMENDMENT TO SUBCONTRACT BETWEEN MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY AND UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE This amendment, made this 1st day of June, 2006, by and between Middle Tennessee State University (University) and University of Tennessee (Subcontractor). WITNESSETH WHEREAS, the parties desire to modify the terms and conditions and to add or delete certain other terms and conditions to their original agreement (Contract #05- 0445) dated October 29th, 2004, the parties hereby agree as set forth below. A.     ARTICLE I - Scope of Services is replaced with the following: The Scope of Services covers the development, delivery, and evaluation for training that has been developed in consultation with members of a technical advisory committee (TAC) as part of the “Brian A. Lawsuit” and Settlement Agreement with the State. Subcontractor shall be responsible for the specific training initiatives as selected by the individual Subcontractor and as specified in Revised Attachment A dated 7-1-05. The Subcontractor shall complete development, delivery and evaluation of selected training initiatives in conformity with the plan described in Revised Attachment A dated 7-1-05. B.     The first sentence in ARTICLE II - Period of Performance is modified as follows: The period of performance for this Subcontract shall be from July 1, 2006 to June 30, 2007 unless amended by mutual agreement of the parties. C.     The first paragraph in ARTICLE III - Scope of Services is replaced with the following: University agrees to pay Subcontractor for these services a total amount not to exceed $2,110,738 for the period of July 1, 2006 to June 30, 2007. Expenditures incurred prior to the beginning date or subsequent to the termination date are unallowable. University shall not be obligated to reimburse, nor shall Subcontractor be permitted to incur any expenditures in excess of this limitation. Subcontractor shall make obligations in accordance with the budget, which is attached hereto and hereby made a part of this Subcontract as Attachment B dated 7-1-06. D. The second paragraph in ARTICLE III - Payment is replaced with the following: 06-1 052a Payments to Subcontractor shall be made in accordance with this Subcontract and only after receipt of invoices for services performed. Subcontractor is further required to submit monthly narrative program reports to the University by the 15th of each month. E. The third paragraph in ARTICLE III - Payment is replaced with the following: Subcontractor shall submit monthly invoices to University indicating the amounts expended in the current period and cumulatively to date by line item budget category. The invoice shall be certified by an officer or other responsible official of Subcontractor, shall reference University account 5-31138 and shall be sent along with the monthly narrative program report to: Fiscal Director Tennessee Center for Child Welfare Training Middle Tennessee State University P.O. Box 143 Murfreesboro, TN 37132 All other terms and conditions of the above-referenced original Agreement remain the same. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties, through their authorized representatives, have affixed the signatures below. UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY By: Signature Signature Typed Name Sidnev A. McPhee President Date Date APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOAR BY: DATE</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3B804947-197B-48FB-89E3-0A93BB05CCFA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1584</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1594</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode84187590-5E1D-40B4-86ED-DB109211E84E"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3663881B-8CA5-453E-B8C5-3624C0EA9B0C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1584</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1585</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode84187590-5E1D-40B4-86ED-DB109211E84E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7402CE00-DF5A-468A-80FF-77E89DEF6CCB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1585</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1594</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode84187590-5E1D-40B4-86ED-DB109211E84E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2110738</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>