<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369949" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeA709FD86-CE9A-43B1-8643-5DA4CAAF1B1B">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">130000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode1FE570FC-C6AD-4133-AFC4-5A47EB7B3678">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">34.25</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode6CC0DA6B-3F25-4199-ABBE-2C26B6245452">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN SOUTHWEST TENNESSEE COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND DEAFCONNECT OF THE MIDSOUTH This Agreement is made this 30th day of July, 2008, by and between the Southwest Tennessee Community College, hereinafter referred to as the "College", and DeafConnect of the Midsouth, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A.     The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: Provide interpreting services for students who are hearing impaired in accordance with the attached Request for Proposal #B012992, dated May 19, 2008, and Contractor’s response to Request for Proposal #B012992, dated June 20, 2008, for Southwest Tennessee Community College and Tennessee Technology Center at Memphis. B.     The College agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1.     Basic rate of $34.25 per hour per interpreter with a 2-hour minimum. An additional $8.56 per quarter hour is charged for services incurred after the first 2 hours. The College will not be responsible for travel expenses. 2.     Monthly payments shall be due in 30 days after receipt of invoice and monthly services are performed. 3.     Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, provided that payments shall be made only upon submittal of invoices by the Contractor, and after performance of the portion of the services which the invoiced amount represents. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Agreement. If the Contractor is a non-resident alien, payment of any portion of the contract from any source will not be made by the College until an Individual Taxpayer Identification Number or Social Security Number has been assigned to the Contractor by the Internal Revenue Service and Immigration Naturalization Service and presented to the College. 4.     In no event shall the liability of the College under this contract exceed $ 130,000.00 . C.     The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement. 1. The Contractor warrants that no part of the total contract amount provided herein shall be paid directly or indirectly to any officer or employee of the state of 1 Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, sub-Contractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this Agreement. If the Contractor is an individual, the Contractor warrants that within the past six months he/she has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2.     The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3.     Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference as Attachment I. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents College or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. 4.     The Contractor is not a minority owned business. A minority owned business is a business which is solely owned, or at least fifty-one percent (51%) of the assets or outstanding stock which is owned, by an individual who personally manages and controls the daily operations of such business and who is impeded from normal entry into the economic mainstream because of past practices of discrimination based on race, religion, ethnic background, or sex. 5.     The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of this College, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, to pay all taxes incident hereunto, and otherwise protect and hold the College harmless from any and all liability not specifically provided for in this agreement. 6.     The term of this agreement shall be from August 23, 2008 to June 30, 2009, with the option to renew said agreement for four (4) additional twelve (12) month terms. 7.    This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 30 days before the effective date of termination. In that e vent, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 8.     If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this Agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this Agreement, the College shall have the right to immediately terminate this Agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the College for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Agreement by the Contractor. 9.    This Agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 10.   The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the College under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the College or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 11.    The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the College or Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 12.   This Agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or designee, the Vice Chancellor for the Tennessee Technology Centers or designee or the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 13.   This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of Tennessee. 14.    Any and all claims against the College, its officers, agents, and employees in performing any responsibility specifically required under the terms of this agreement shall be submitted to the Board of Claims or the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee. Damages recoverable against the College shall be limited to claims paid by the Board of Claims or the Claims Commission pursuant T.C.A. Section 9-8-301, et. seq. 15.    Reference of incorporated sections: The contract document consists of this agreement, dated; the College’s RFP # B012992, May 19, 2008; and Contractor’s response to RFP # B012992, dated June 20, 2008; and any addenda and/or amendment to this agreement hereafter executed. In the event that provisions of the contract documents conflict, priority for interpretation shall be as follows: addenda and/or amendment (latest addenda or amendment with first priority), the Agreement, the College’s Request for Proposal, and the Contractor’s response to proposal. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. Southwest Tennessee Community ^College a ..... BY: / TITLE:                 ____________ DATE:   nl'bt/ C'?____________ APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF/REGENTS ' 1 BY: DATE:</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB36BACB6-952D-4EF8-B023-3F7BC292EB8D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">962</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">968</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode1FE570FC-C6AD-4133-AFC4-5A47EB7B3678"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9F14467D-9209-4055-816A-E0A48DB312E3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">962</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">963</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode1FE570FC-C6AD-4133-AFC4-5A47EB7B3678"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode2D5F16B9-656D-4B8F-891C-E7C44D0D646A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">963</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">968</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode1FE570FC-C6AD-4133-AFC4-5A47EB7B3678"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">34.25</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeECE2441E-DED8-4BA9-88F8-5A8BEBF69B16">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2087</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2099</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA709FD86-CE9A-43B1-8643-5DA4CAAF1B1B"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA4E4B7F8-26CA-4F74-BFFE-EB8E47368014">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2087</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2088</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA709FD86-CE9A-43B1-8643-5DA4CAAF1B1B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode46713F91-8260-47A2-8C67-74C263B680CA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2089</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2099</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA709FD86-CE9A-43B1-8643-5DA4CAAF1B1B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">130000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>