<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369965" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode3DA1D6D2-E271-466F-A345-B4642E7A278D">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode49DAAE40-AC3E-4AB3-8EA2-D84B7D41715A">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">9000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeC58BE9E6-4979-4A94-94B5-415B5C84D820">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">120400</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode2797D5F5-6420-48C9-878E-F0EE736BA308">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">120400</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode77AA78CA-163C-4476-9C01-67A81731A6F9">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">9000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeA015B2E4-2E3D-4DBE-B458-049E03D4D01D">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">101400</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeCB8D430A-A7C6-4C17-BF38-7A282B090815">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">8450</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode969DCA89-C706-47AF-B556-B2290996EFE9">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">90</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4A5AC6C2-1728-4446-85C1-3D34019E8CA0">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">8450</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode1625CFC3-D0BF-415E-B59A-6E3767FE886D">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS/TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGY CENTERS AND DPC, Inc. This Agreement is made this 1st day of November 2008, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents/Tennessee Technology Centers, hereinafter referred to as the "Institution", and DPC, Inc., hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The Contractor agrees to provide maintenance, support, and backup services for the Student Information Management System (SIMS) at a cost of $8,450 per month to include: 1.  Unlimited telephone support to TBR Central Office personnel; 2.  Maintenance of SIMS system to include off-site backup server and connectivity; 3. Technical support (telephone, on-site, or remote) to 26 Technology Centers as needed; 4.  Backup of each Institution’s database to an off-site location to include: a.  Daily backup of database to secure off-site vault server; b.  Disk storage space for one month of backups for each school; c.  Monthly maintenance and cleanup for prior backups; d. Reporting of successful and unsuccessful daily backups 5. Design and development of data restoration and merging processes needed to combine each Institution’s data into one master database; 6. Training and support to TBR personnel in SQL Server reporting services to support querying for consolidated data; 7.  300 hours of programming and/or consulting services which include but not limited to: a. Enhancements and/or modifications to existing modules; b. Development of new modules; c.  Consultation with user groups (Financial Aid, Instructors, etc.) as needed; d.  Training users in creation of queries and report writing; e. Workshops or meetings to discuss modifications to system; and f.  Software releases as needed to correct errors or bugs as reported by users; 8. Additional programming and/or consulting services beyond the 300 hours not to exceed 100 hours will be charged at a rate of $90 per hour. 9. Development of an encrypted File Transfer Protocol (FTP) application for the Tennessee Technology Center at Chattanooga to transmit TBR Enrollment Reports to the TBR Office of Data and Statistics. The estimated cost of this service will be $5,000 for set-up and installation. 10. Development of a TTC Report Writer for beta testing at five institutions. The estimated cost for this development and testing is estimated at $1,000 per school or a total of $5,000. B. The Institution agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: Service Description Billing Frequency Billing Rate Total Cost Maintenance, Support and Backup Monthly $8,450.00 $101,400.00 Programming, Consulting or Training As Requested $9,000.00 9,000.00 TBR Report Functionality for TTC Chattanooga As completed $5,000.00 5,000.00 Development/Beta Testing of TTC Report Writer As completed $5,000.00 5,000.00 MAXIMUM LIABILITY   $120,400.00 1.  Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, but only after receipt of invoices for service performed. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this agreement. 2.  If the Contractor is a non-resident alien, no payment of any portion of the contract from any source will be made by the Institution until an Individual Taxpayer Identification Number or Social Security Number has been assigned to the Contractor by the Internal Revenue Service and Immigration Naturalization Service and presented to the Institution. 3.  In no event shall the liability of the Institution under this contract exceed $120,400. An amendment shall be required for services in excess of the contracted amount. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement: 1. The Contractor warrants that no part of the total contract amount provided herein shall be paid directly or indirectly to any officer or employee of the state of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, sub-Contractor or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this agreement. If the Contractor is an individual, the Contractor warrants that within the past six months he has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2.  The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of I964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of I972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order II, 246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3.  This Agreement shall not be binding until the Contractor has returned a completed minority/ethnicity report to the Institution. 4.  The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of this Institution, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, to pay all taxes incident hereunto, and otherwise protect and hold the Institution harmless from any and all liability not specifically provided for in this agreement. 5.  The term of this contract shall be from November 1,2008 to October 31,2009. 6.  This agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other at least 30 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. The Institution shall be entitled to receive just and equitable reimbursement for any payments paid to the contractor for work that was not completed. 7.  If the Contractor fails to fulfill in timely and proper manner its obligations under this agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this agreement, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate this agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. 8.  Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this agreement by the Contractor. 9. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 10. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the Institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 11. The Contractor shall not assign this agreement or enter into sub-contracts forany of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution or Board of Regents, as appropriate. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was oris currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 12. This agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the Chancellorfor the Tennessee Board of Regents. 13. Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, reguiresthat Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity fora period of one (1) year from the Rules of Finance and Administration, 0620. D. Voluntary Buyout Program. The Contractor acknowledges and understands that, for a period of two years beginning August 16, 2008, restrictions are imposed on former state employees who received a State of Tennessee Voluntary Buyout Program (VBP) severance payment with regard to contracts with state agencies that participated in the VBP. a.     The State will not contract with either a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or an entity in which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or the spouse of such an individual holds a controlling financial interest. b.     The State may contract with an entity with which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment is an employee or an independent contractor. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Contractor understands and agrees that there may be unigue business circumstances under which a return to work by a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment as an employee or an independent contractor of a State contractor would not be appropriate, and in such cases the State may refuse Contractor personnel. Inasmuch, it shall be the responsibility of the State to review Contractor personnel to identify any such issues. c.     With reference to either subsection a. or b. above, a Contractor may a written request for a waiver of the VBP restrictions regarding a former state employee and a contract with a state agency that participated in the VBP. Any such request must be submitted to the State in the form of the VBP Contracting Restriction Waiver Request format available from the State and the Internet at: www.state.tn. us/finance/rds/ocr/waiver.html. The determination on such a request shall be at the sole discretion of the head of the state agency that is a Party to this Contract, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration, and the Commissioner of Human Resources. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signature. DPC, Inc: Scott Caldwell Director Name Title Signature Date Tennessee Board of Regents/Tennessee Technology Centers: </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA611DEB8-630C-4294-A939-3F2304428E0E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">642</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">648</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4A5AC6C2-1728-4446-85C1-3D34019E8CA0"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6431CF8D-8A97-4673-8052-760F70F09331">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">642</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">643</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4A5AC6C2-1728-4446-85C1-3D34019E8CA0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode80A7EB0F-425D-4237-91C7-EA140796CAED">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">643</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">648</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4A5AC6C2-1728-4446-85C1-3D34019E8CA0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">8450</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0D8577AA-0201-4761-92F0-DBF545A284E3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2072</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2075</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode969DCA89-C706-47AF-B556-B2290996EFE9"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0B71D36-88C6-40D6-B8C5-3B4871AFC765">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2072</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2073</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode969DCA89-C706-47AF-B556-B2290996EFE9"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD8D587EA-3DDB-4126-B54F-D6B4DF451B66">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2073</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2075</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode969DCA89-C706-47AF-B556-B2290996EFE9"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">90</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE1132D4A-F93D-42C0-B70C-EFF247EB3B1C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2720</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2729</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeCB8D430A-A7C6-4C17-BF38-7A282B090815"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9D91FDA4-6D1F-44A6-B5EE-90E5D4307713">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2720</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2721</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeCB8D430A-A7C6-4C17-BF38-7A282B090815"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDD443154-6C41-41B3-A700-EB8A0AFE5D53">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2721</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2729</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeCB8D430A-A7C6-4C17-BF38-7A282B090815"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">8450</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7CD9B3DD-C799-46AB-8AB0-D519B2E50772">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2730</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2731</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA015B2E4-2E3D-4DBE-B458-049E03D4D01D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCF5EC1AD-50ED-41D8-9744-0249E90362F1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2730</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2741</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA015B2E4-2E3D-4DBE-B458-049E03D4D01D"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA3F61DB4-4791-41DC-8FB3-4D0C6909372D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2731</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2741</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA015B2E4-2E3D-4DBE-B458-049E03D4D01D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">101400</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA9231E09-6C73-49D0-872A-3475783BC72A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2791</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2800</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode77AA78CA-163C-4476-9C01-67A81731A6F9"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBF96C1CA-6190-4CEB-BABA-F6E8CF5DFC4B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2791</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2792</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode77AA78CA-163C-4476-9C01-67A81731A6F9"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode696D9252-7848-400A-B8F9-6706D0D65A56">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2792</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2800</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode77AA78CA-163C-4476-9C01-67A81731A6F9"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">9000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6A793B37-8415-4CF9-B9A3-B30BCE9D8401">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2801</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2809</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode49DAAE40-AC3E-4AB3-8EA2-D84B7D41715A"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode62923954-992F-4FD8-B66D-CA40295831B5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2801</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2809</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode49DAAE40-AC3E-4AB3-8EA2-D84B7D41715A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">9000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode86F0D361-777F-403B-B0E0-57518856F4CC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2878</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2886</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3DA1D6D2-E271-466F-A345-B4642E7A278D"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4EEFA28B-4A43-437D-8C76-10A8FCBD1E1B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2878</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2886</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3DA1D6D2-E271-466F-A345-B4642E7A278D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8041167B-A6E1-434C-B7EC-33DDC97FEB43">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2985</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2986</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2797D5F5-6420-48C9-878E-F0EE736BA308"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode77C41F49-757C-470B-B182-945D5F78DED8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2985</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2996</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2797D5F5-6420-48C9-878E-F0EE736BA308"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1D487618-45FC-4852-8B0B-E0055C9A70C8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2986</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2996</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2797D5F5-6420-48C9-878E-F0EE736BA308"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">120400</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode36B35213-EA83-4298-8E71-F44F09C31CF0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3694</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3702</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC58BE9E6-4979-4A94-94B5-415B5C84D820"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8ABE0836-6A39-4F37-8B9E-E3272B511522">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3694</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3695</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC58BE9E6-4979-4A94-94B5-415B5C84D820"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7EE13BE5-A668-4FFF-B053-8642F461D201">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3695</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3702</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC58BE9E6-4979-4A94-94B5-415B5C84D820"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">120400</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>