<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369910" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode27ACE73A-E3FF-457B-BCED-09833B148CD0">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">20000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode888C878F-7D29-415B-A8CA-498E78BCD276">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN Tennessee Board of Regents, Office of Academic Affairs AND Tennessee Technology University This Agreement is made this first day of March, 2008, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as the "TBR", and Tennessee Technology University, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: 1.   The Contractor will develop an Internet based on-line system to support the submission and management of each community college’s proposal to request funding under the Carl D. Perkins Career and Technical Education Act of 2006. The elements of the system will include the following: a.   The budget request based upon activities and costs to be expended for the accomplishment of each performance indicator and for the general development of the career and technical education programs. b.   A state summary report of funds being requested by the colleges. c.   A narrative of activities and functions to be performed related to the budget. d.   The “Assurance and Compliance” documents. 2.   The following tasks will be performed by the Contractor: a. Develop a spreadsheet version of the Carl D. Perkins Career and Technical Education Act of 2006 funding request and proposal elements. The blank form will be available via the web site. b.   Develop an on-line system for institutions to upload and manage their completed spreadsheets to the TBR web server. Institutions will be able to upload, amend, etc. their submissions. c.   Develop an on-line system for the TBR to manage initial submissions and amendments from institutions. It will allow the TBR to view, download, delete, etc. the spreadsheets submitted by the institutions. The user interface will look similar to Windows Explorer. d.   Provide institutions on-line entry and management of their local plans. This will include total budget information and narrative. e.   Provide reporting to include summary budget information across an institution and across the system. f.    Provide an attractive web site to access this information. As appropriate, the web site will provide some publicly and some restricted (username and password) access. The site will also provide search capabilities of the site. B. The TBR agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1. Compensation to the Contractor will be based upon successful completion, ■as-» agreed uptri i by II le twe-parties, of each task wittjin the &gt;f work. ' 2. A final payment of no less than 25% of the contract will be paid upon acceptance of the web site by TBR. 3. Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, provided that payments shall be made only upon submittal of invoices by the Contractor, and after performance of the portion of the services which the invoiced amount represents. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Agreement. 4. In no event shall the liability of the TBR under this contract exceed $ 20,000 . Funds are dependent upon federal funding. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement. If the Contractor is an individual, the Contractor warrants that within the past six months he/she has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2. The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3. Contractor agrees to complete a TBR Annual Title VI Survey or cooperate with a TBR Title VI compliance audit if it received Federal funds under this Agreement. The C agreement. eing an independent contractor a blic liabilit 4. TBR, agrees to carry adeq insurance, to pay all taxes incident h the TBR harmless from an ot an employee of d other appropriate forms of nd otherwise protect and hold provided for ij\thi 5. The term of this contract shall be from March 1, 2008 to August 30, 2008. 6. This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 45 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 7. If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this Agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this Agreement, the TBR shall have the right to immediately terminate this Agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the TBR for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Agreement by the Contractor. 8.   This Agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 9.   The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the TBR under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the TBR or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 10.  The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Tennessee Board of Regents. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 11.  The Contractor shall submit to the TBR periodic progress reports if requested by the TBR. 12.  This Agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or designee, and the Chancellor or designee for the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 13.  Payment to the Contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be in the amount of actual cost or per diem, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the Tennessee Board of Regents policies, as they may be from time to time amended. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. Tennessee Technology University TITLE^ranc’s Otuonye, Ph.D. Aaauc. VP for Research/Uraduate Studies DATE:                _________ DATE:_____Q ''O&amp;</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE2801497-710C-447B-BD53-AA17D44A235A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3213</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3221</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode27ACE73A-E3FF-457B-BCED-09833B148CD0"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8F625323-7A2B-4811-8E0F-7C6B7AC59D03">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3213</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3214</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode27ACE73A-E3FF-457B-BCED-09833B148CD0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE8EAAB23-E3B2-44DA-BB08-274FFBD3847C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3215</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3221</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode27ACE73A-E3FF-457B-BCED-09833B148CD0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">20000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>