<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369981" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeFEDDB931-1071-43B3-A130-31431C314FA9">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">9576468</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode7EE651C1-C1E6-4153-A3BC-B7260EC5C053">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1427990</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeC400C628-D8C4-4109-B35C-C185FAADE5CC">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5711962</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode9CD234D0-3F42-4AEA-A93D-21B8D4019414">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2436516</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeB59C530A-97D0-414C-A12B-9817FA734C87">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">8227377</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8DDD74BF-2B74-451C-A5DA-97C7B9C02C0D">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">8000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeC09A4AE0-62C2-466C-9452-15AA35A291DA">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1600000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode5620F4FC-0284-4F5C-BDF9-62927DE74C24">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">6400000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode56852BE2-491D-44DE-A89E-E1E00C4F31B3">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4921900</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode85B4E072-E282-47EC-AE01-C00A4D13CE1F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">206500</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE6337A3E-F379-437B-B9E0-A8CCD86007E1">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2643016</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode964DA866-FE5C-4B26-8EB2-3FC305FD9F5B">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">009 -0868 MEMORANDUM OF UNDERSTANDING (MOU) between THE CITY OF MURFREESBORO and MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY and approved by the TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS for the reconstruction of MIDDLE TENNESSEE BOULEVARD from MAIN STREET TO GREENLAND DRIVE The purpose of this MOU is to establish a formal cooperative working and funding relationship between the City of Murfreesboro (“City") and Middle Tennessee State University (“MTSU”) for the reconstruction of Middle Tennessee Boulevard from Main Street to Greenland Drive (the “project”) which has been approved by the Tennessee Board of Regents. The parties to this MOU hereby agree to the following roles and responsibilities in facilitation of this project: I. The City is required to be and agrees to be the contractual recipient of federal transportation funds that have been or will be made available for the various phases of implementation of this project including but not limited to design, rights-of-way acquisition and construction. The City will provide general project oversight but day-to-day project management and oversight shall be primarily through the selected project engineering firm to ensure proper work flow and scheduling between the design engineering firm and its sub consultants, federal and state agencies, utility companies, contractors and other involved entities and agencies. It is anticipated that the project engineering firm will provide professional services during the construction phase of the project that will exceed those that are usual and customary and that the compensation will reflect such enhanced construction management. The City will provide coordination of project processes and compliancy with required federal, state and local rules and regulations. The City and MTSU shall cooperate to jointly select an engineering firm that shall be charged to design the project in accordance with the mutual goals and objectives of both entities including but not limited to enhanced bicycle and pedestrian facilities, adequate vehicular facilities, medians, landscaping and other functional and aesthetic project enhancements. The City and MTSU shall mutually participate throughout the design process to ensure that the project is designed in accordance with City standards for roadway construction and in a manner that meets the goals and objectives of both entities including but not limited to enhanced bicycle and pedestrian facilities, adequate vehicular facilities, medians, landscaping and other functional and aesthetic project elements. CO 9 - 0868 The City and MTSU shall require the selected engineering firm to prepare bid and construction documents which contain “add” alternatives as the feasibility of some amenities may depend on pricing. Similarly, the construction documents will allow additional time for the City to approve change orders and progress payments because both City and MTSU will be involved in those processes. The project will be designed with a requirement that the designer’s total cost estimate plus a 10% contingency cannot exceed the funds available as described in Section II below or less if so directed. Total project cost shall include design fees, construction cost, contingencies, consultants, administrative fees and costs, rights-of- way acquisition or easements cost and all other project costs. No construction contract shall be awarded until federal funds available are verified and confirmed and City and MTSU agree to proceed. City and MTSU shall confer on the appropriateness of any change order which increases the contract amount. Only with MTSU’s approval may City authorize a change order which will increase the contract amount and for which MTSU will be financially responsible; City may unilaterally authorize a change order if City is assuming financial responsibility for an increase in the contract amount. II. The project has been previously designed as a five-lane roadway with bicycle lanes and sidewalks. The City had fully funded the project through local resources and City designated federal funds. The project, based on preliminary design plans, totaled $2,643,016 for all phases of the project including engineering, rights-of-way acquisition and construction. The City has previously paid approximately $206,500 for the production of a bid-ready set of design plans to facilitate construction of a five-lane roadway with bike lanes and sidewalks. In mid 2003 MTSU requested substantial project modifications and additions that rendered these current City sponsored plans inadequate. MTSU’s primary goal in the project is to improve pedestrian safety in consideration of the increasing pedestrian traffic in the area, reduce traffic speed, enhance bike paths connecting to the campus and improve the appearance of Middle Tennessee Boulevard at the campus boundary. MTSU has, through an outside engineering firm, provided a conceptual plan and estimate in mid 2003 which totaled approximately $4,921,900 (original roadway cost plus MTSU designated changes and additions). This plan and cost estimate was inclusive of roadway reconstruction and other amenities. In order to financially support the requested safety enhancements and aesthetic elements, MTSU pursued and obtained a federal earmark for supplemental funding to provide for the enhanced roadway reconstruction project. The funding obtained was through the six- year transportation bill known as the Safe, Accountable, Flexible and Efficient Transportation Equity Act-A Legacy for Users (SAFETEA-LU). Funding in the amount of $6,400,000 (federal) was provided in Section 1701-1702-High Priority Projects (HPP)-Project Authorizations, of this bill. C 0 9 - 086 8 These federal funds require a 20% local match and as such the total funds designated in SAFETEA-LU provide funding as follows: $6,400,000 (federal), $1,600,000 (local), $8,000,000 (total). The federal funds designated in SAFETEA-LU are subject to increases or reductions as may be designated by Congress in the annual appropriation bill. The value of MTSU’s land, whether donated or purchased, that may be acquired for rights-of-way or easements necessitated for implementation of this project will be that of MTSU and can be utilized for their sole benefit in matching federal funds through proceeds of sale or as an in-kind soft match. The value of the MTSU land and verification of the match shall be determined prior to award of any construction contract. In the Fall of 2006, MTSU provided an updated cost estimate for the design, rights-of-way acquisition and construction phases for the roadway reconstruction and other amenities totaling approximately $8,227,377. The City is prepared to provide its original funding ($2,643,016) less the actual amount expended for the production of its original bid-ready set of plans ($206,500), through any combination of federal, state and local funds that may be available for this project’s rights- of-way and construction phases. None of the federal earmark supplemental funding obtained by MTSU (HPP #1327+4928) shall be used by City to make up its original funding. Funds currently available for this project are as follows: $2,436,516 (City); $5,711,962 (Federal); $1,427,990 (Local match); $9,576,468 (Total). Any shortage of funds for this project will be the obligation of MTSU/State as City shall not pay more than $2,436,516. The funds for the project as described in this Section II are illustrated on Attachment A. It is acknowledged and understood that MTSU’s participation in the project, specific funding for the project and granting of any additional rights-of-way or easements on MTSU’s property requires state approvals, including the Tennessee Board of Regents and State Building Commission and legislative funding. Simultaneous with award of the engineering contract, MTSU shall deposit $500,000 into a bank escrow account. All interest on the account shall belong to MTSU; City shall be the only party entitled to draw on the account. City shall be entitled to draw on the escrowed funds to pay progress payments to the engineer; City shall then promptly submit requests for reimbursement of said engineering costs from the federal funding sources and deposit said reimbursements in the escrow account. Simultaneous with award of the construction contract, MTSU shall deposit funds sufficient for the escrow account to have a $1,000,000 balance. City shall pay out its $2,436,516 in construction progress payments before City draws on the escrow account for construction payments. City shall promptly submit requests for reimbursement of contractor payments from the federal funding sources. City will be entitled to retain for its own use and purposes such federal funds as may be reimbursed to it for City’s own expenditures on the project as distinct from those reimbursements allocable to MTSU’s share of project expenses. City shall deposit all reimbursements allocable to MTSU’s share of project expenses to the escrow account. City shall provide documentation of its payments to the contractor from its funds and from the escrow account to MTSU. While MTSU and City expect that federal funds for the project will be paid to City on a reimbursement basis for the construction costs C09-0868 so as to make it unnecessary for the escrowed funds to be used for this purpose, MTSU shall deposit additional funds to the escrow account on an "as needed basis" (but not more than 30 days after being notified of the need to do so by City) so as to maintain the $1,000,000 balance until the balance remaining unpaid on the project is less than $1,000,000. MTSU shall deposit additional funds to the escrow account on an “as needed basis” to maintain a balance equal to the balance remaining unpaid on the project until completion of the project when all remaining funds and interest will be released by City and paid to MTSU. Should amounts reimbursed from federal funds for expenses paid for with MTSU escrowed funds be received after completion of the project and closure of the escrow fund, these amounts will be paid to MTSU by City. III. This Agreement shall remain in effect until either party notifies the other in writing that the Agreement is no longer suitable. If or when this occurs, the parties agree to meet as soon as practicable to discuss modifications to this cooperative Agreement. This right of notification and modification is limited as to time. MTSU cannot unilaterally terminate or modify this Agreement after MTSU has approved, and City has entered into, contracts for design engineering services or construction services; any termination or modification of this Agreement after such contracts have been executed requires the agreement of both parties. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties hereto have executed the Memorandum of Understanding effective as of the________day of______________, 2009. CITY OF MURFREESBORO i' Z £&gt;• 0&lt;j Date Approved as to form: City Attorney 7 MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY A By: Sidney A. McPfiee, President APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS Charles Manning, Chancellor C09 -0868 </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6280A887-03E4-45A2-9425-5FE6BE7CDF62">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4121</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4131</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE6337A3E-F379-437B-B9E0-A8CCD86007E1"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6DB54154-7B34-4B87-9F05-75F9D8BBAE89">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4121</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4122</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE6337A3E-F379-437B-B9E0-A8CCD86007E1"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode04EAEC03-C384-4B92-B1DA-CAC4FCD66419">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4122</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4131</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE6337A3E-F379-437B-B9E0-A8CCD86007E1"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2643016</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8EEA0EC7-FF2F-4CE7-A716-75B29710D582">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4272</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4280</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode85B4E072-E282-47EC-AE01-C00A4D13CE1F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3880C27A-3F12-49EF-96A9-7DD4C45EF764">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4272</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4273</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode85B4E072-E282-47EC-AE01-C00A4D13CE1F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4D93753A-82FB-4606-9A17-1976D308165D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4273</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4280</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode85B4E072-E282-47EC-AE01-C00A4D13CE1F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">206500</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA2EE8BD0-1560-48AA-ABB1-F03418451887">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4960</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4970</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode56852BE2-491D-44DE-A89E-E1E00C4F31B3"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7001C7E1-27C1-40CF-A687-E6DA2CCE5CC2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4960</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4961</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode56852BE2-491D-44DE-A89E-E1E00C4F31B3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD5987ACD-9172-490E-AA97-72AA1AEB774B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4961</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4970</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode56852BE2-491D-44DE-A89E-E1E00C4F31B3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4921900</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode14996441-3699-4AF2-B456-3BC1E2ABEF5D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5553</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5554</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5620F4FC-0284-4F5C-BDF9-62927DE74C24"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF18558CC-87FF-43F0-BE4F-C209E859C9AE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5553</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5563</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5620F4FC-0284-4F5C-BDF9-62927DE74C24"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD67DF5A0-2FC8-4A14-8C78-A6ECAFB4F07F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5554</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5563</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5620F4FC-0284-4F5C-BDF9-62927DE74C24"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">6400000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC367C9F8-1D26-45D2-BE4B-4ED3BF8E1951">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5838</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5848</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC09A4AE0-62C2-466C-9452-15AA35A291DA"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode48DF42E7-67A3-45B9-9996-B3FC2CD60AEF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5838</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5839</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC09A4AE0-62C2-466C-9452-15AA35A291DA"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeFD687EA7-9A8C-44A7-B969-F95ED5CAEDEC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5839</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5848</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC09A4AE0-62C2-466C-9452-15AA35A291DA"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1600000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5B4B56A5-846E-45AE-9B8B-EC9C808B70AD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5858</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5859</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8DDD74BF-2B74-451C-A5DA-97C7B9C02C0D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8F5A7360-4F51-4998-8598-A03353215A15">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5858</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5868</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8DDD74BF-2B74-451C-A5DA-97C7B9C02C0D"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7C73865F-08E0-4768-9B82-E46901E4FB1E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5859</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5868</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8DDD74BF-2B74-451C-A5DA-97C7B9C02C0D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">8000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA04A6EE5-2C4F-47E4-892A-6E0E4E09A579">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6649</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6659</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeB59C530A-97D0-414C-A12B-9817FA734C87"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB160D153-A2D4-4609-8318-C449D2DF8083">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6649</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6650</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeB59C530A-97D0-414C-A12B-9817FA734C87"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode135B774B-D51A-48C4-BA77-FB7E746F9AF1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6650</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6659</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeB59C530A-97D0-414C-A12B-9817FA734C87"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">8227377</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDA6D4CFE-FA6E-44AE-A05A-E3D409502D4B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7165</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7175</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9CD234D0-3F42-4AEA-A93D-21B8D4019414"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode303202F5-B1AC-4EA4-9B39-FC790A50C11C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7165</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7166</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9CD234D0-3F42-4AEA-A93D-21B8D4019414"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode81D33E1F-24DF-49F2-9BCA-E7D6E8D55FF5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7166</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7175</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9CD234D0-3F42-4AEA-A93D-21B8D4019414"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2436516</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8FA2CCC5-78D6-47AD-A66E-8F79F5FA2103">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7184</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7185</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC400C628-D8C4-4109-B35C-C185FAADE5CC"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode19BAB517-7455-4147-A19A-02CDFE746688">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7184</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7194</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC400C628-D8C4-4109-B35C-C185FAADE5CC"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode63829CEB-56DD-4B3E-8826-DB81338D083F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7185</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7194</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC400C628-D8C4-4109-B35C-C185FAADE5CC"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5711962</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1777A783-C9D4-4806-A146-C2F4677D56B9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7206</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7216</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7EE651C1-C1E6-4153-A3BC-B7260EC5C053"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode364B48CB-80A5-475F-8FCE-AC3AFDDFF5D9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7206</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7207</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7EE651C1-C1E6-4153-A3BC-B7260EC5C053"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEE059CA6-8A0B-4731-B3BD-63850B021567">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7207</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7216</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7EE651C1-C1E6-4153-A3BC-B7260EC5C053"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1427990</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5DDDEEB1-C0A4-4EFF-9B26-7E88BA520A2E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7232</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7242</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeFEDDB931-1071-43B3-A130-31431C314FA9"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC1B9E598-D71F-4E4A-B3C1-4D4BF3EC20A1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7232</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7233</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeFEDDB931-1071-43B3-A130-31431C314FA9"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode48B3C50A-3AC7-4A6A-A9A8-90C117FD9433">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7233</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7242</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeFEDDB931-1071-43B3-A130-31431C314FA9"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">9576468</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>