<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369972" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeF0534C46-CF28-4E8E-82B7-D7E97F681DBF">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">46000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode9BC47A2B-8402-49A1-81C1-01727975DFEA">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">24000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode6FB5781D-4933-4BE6-802D-7A2EAE0029C2">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">22000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode63AC59F4-18E5-4FAA-B962-1B6E80E81EE9">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">PROFESSIONAL SERVICES AGREEMENT BETWEEN TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS AND TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY This Agreement is made this day December 17,2008, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as the "Institution", and Tennessee State University, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A.    The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: Provide the services of two Graduate Assistants to assist ROCC/TBR with the THEC laptop project and to assist with the TQI (Teacher Quality Initiative) project: Jeffery Norfleet - Laptop Project Sabrina Knowlton - TQI Project TBR agrees to reimburse the Contractor as follows: Actual costs as charged by the Contractor for the graduate tuition and fees not to exceed $22,000/year; and Salary and travel reimbursement as paid by the Contractor to the graduate assistants not to exceed $24,000/year. B. The Institution agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1.  Payments to the Contractor shall be made only after receipt of invoices for services performed. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this agreement. Monthly invoices should be mailed to the following address: Deanna Hall, Director of Fiscal Services Tennessee Board of Regents 1415 Murfreesboro Road, Suite 350 Nashville, TN 37217 2. In no event shall the liability of the Institution under this contract exceed $46,000. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this agreement. 1. The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 2. The term of this contract shall be from January 1,2009 to December 31, 2009, renewable annually for 4 additional consecutive years not to exceed a total of 5 years or 60 months by mutual written consent of both parties. 3. This agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 60 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 4. If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this agreement, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate this agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the Institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this agreement by the Contractor. 5. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 6. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the Institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 7. The Contractor shall not assign this agreement without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution. 8. This Contract is subject to the allotment of state and/or federal binds, and may be null and void unless binds have been appropriated and are available for the purchase of the service or item which forms the basis of the Contract. 9. This agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president and the Chancellor of the Tennessee Board of Regents. 10. Compensation to the Contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be in the amount of actual cost to the Contractor, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the Tennessee Board of Regents policies, as they may be from time to time amended. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. TENNESSEE STATE UHIVpRSITY BY:                        __________________ Mellin N. Johnson TITLE:_______PETS I DENT______________________ DATE:</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode96A71E45-2F26-4E6D-B3FA-3E29B260E20B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">922</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">929</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6FB5781D-4933-4BE6-802D-7A2EAE0029C2"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEFDBB1B6-E5C6-4873-852B-5CA40C183951">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">922</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">923</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6FB5781D-4933-4BE6-802D-7A2EAE0029C2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0940998D-3D4B-4986-8B05-A3076E8BB3B2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">923</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">929</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6FB5781D-4933-4BE6-802D-7A2EAE0029C2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">22000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode42E3D1E1-40D7-4BCC-940B-7023322CA7EA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1039</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1040</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9BC47A2B-8402-49A1-81C1-01727975DFEA"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4412426F-39B2-45DB-88D6-FE330F16667A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1039</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1046</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9BC47A2B-8402-49A1-81C1-01727975DFEA"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode33497672-DF34-4769-82AD-AB6A7511DC6A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1040</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1046</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9BC47A2B-8402-49A1-81C1-01727975DFEA"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">24000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode10F284AA-1804-4E2C-B018-AA805B1E0E5A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1599</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1606</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF0534C46-CF28-4E8E-82B7-D7E97F681DBF"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDEC21387-469A-444B-A9A2-9CD8A17075F6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1599</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1600</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF0534C46-CF28-4E8E-82B7-D7E97F681DBF"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA5353C8C-CA11-4D7A-A670-C9B24B28EF8D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1600</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1606</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF0534C46-CF28-4E8E-82B7-D7E97F681DBF"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">46000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>