<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369874" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4D4E80AF-DAEE-424E-85CB-9C94CBA36347">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">750000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode54EEE664-8B17-4FF8-A587-33859951B76B">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">THIRD AMENDMENT TO AGREEMENT BETWEEN THE TOMBRAS GROUP AND THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS The following terms and conditions, as applicable, shall amend, modify, add or delete certain other terms and conditions to the above-referenced Agreement dated December 23, 2005 between THE TOMBRAS GROUP (“Contractor”), and THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS (“University”), and are incorporated thereunto by reference and made an integral part thereof. The terms and conditions of this Third Amendment shall control in the event same conflict with any term or condition of the above-referenced Agreement. Payment Terms and Conditions- The contract amount shall not exceed $ 750,000.00, which includes any travel costs for filming crew or other expenses the proposer incurs during the time frame of this Contract. In no event shall University’s liability to the Contractor under the Contract exceed $ 750,000.00. Term- This contract shall be effective for a period commencing on July 1, 2007 and shall end on June 30, 2010. Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12- 4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached as Attachment 1. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. The maximum liability under this Amendment is $ 750,000.00. Subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this Third Amendment, the above-referenced original Agreement dated December 23, 2005 between the parties is hereby ratified and confirmed. THE TOMBRAS GROUP Signature                     f Charles P. Tombras, Jr. Typed Name President &amp; CEO_______________ Title June 19, 2007 Date THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS Typed Name President Title yyrpy Dal/^ , . HtViEWED '■'b »O LEGAL FORM &amp; CONTENT _____£&gt; u 0 A- OFFICE OF LEGAyC0UNSEL~ _______ DATE? f Approved by: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS M By: C,_______ Chancellor Charles Maripyig^ Date:  ^-^7-1'7________ </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeAA44B1C9-9554-4D73-AE4E-CCF15A200332">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">650</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">662</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4D4E80AF-DAEE-424E-85CB-9C94CBA36347"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9E6A14E8-B0FC-4E5F-BE5A-E3087DF8CCEB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">650</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">651</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4D4E80AF-DAEE-424E-85CB-9C94CBA36347"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5BF6EEB1-BAC8-4E8B-898E-0011CF350732">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">652</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">662</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4D4E80AF-DAEE-424E-85CB-9C94CBA36347"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">750000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>