<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369821" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8367BA6C-E964-493F-873E-9DC096BE840A">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4952.24</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode6EC63B2B-1FBC-4702-A637-26BE05E94C02">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">SUPPLEMENTAL TAXIWAY LEASE AGREEMENT This Supplemental Taxiway Lease Agreement is entered into by and between The City of Murfreesboro, a municipal corporation in Rutherford County, Tennessee (“Lessor”), and the State University and Community College System of Tennessee, (“Lessee”), as of this_____day of___________________, 2006. RECITALS A.    Lessor is the owner and operator of the Murfreesboro Municipal Airport (“Airport”). B.    Lessee leases certain real property from Lessor at the Airport pursuant to various lease contracts, and operates a professional pilot program as part of Lessee's educational curriculum at the Airport. C.    Lessee is constructing an additional classroom and hangar facility on property it currently leases known as the "Miller Lanier" site which, when completed, will alter and increase the flow of airplane traffic in and around the Lessee facilities. D.    Lessor and Lessee desire to accommodate such traffic flow and to assure maximum safety for all airport users. NOW THEREFORE, in consideration of the premises, and the mutual promises made herein, and other good and valuable consideration, the receipt and sufficiency of which is hereby acknowledged, the parties hereto agree as follows: 1. Lessor leases to Lessee, and Lessee accepts and leases from Lessor, the real property depicted on Exhibit “A," containing an estimated 17,360 square feet, as the dai 12/28/2005 10:19 AM c:\documents and settings\pgregory\local settings\temporary internet files\olkf5\1_taxiway lease rev. 7.14.06 (rent amt.)1.doc 1 04-0104/? “Additional Taxiway Area” for the purpose of providing more convenient, more efficient and safer taxiway access to and from the Lessee hanger facility. Lessee shall cause a survey to be prepared and a legal description of the Additional Taxiway Area (which Area shall include appropriate land adjacent to the asphalt taxiway for safe clearances) and a calculation of the precise amount of square feet to be leased. Upon approval and acceptance by the Airport Board, a copy of such legal description and calculation shall be attached hereto as Exhibit B. 2.     Lessee shall be responsible for all costs of design, construction and maintenance of the Additional Taxiway Area, including all required lighting and signage (including "MTSU Aerospace Only" signage), installation or relocation of any required conduit, and the cost of improvement to or relocation of surface drainage required by the construction, PROVIDED that all plans and specifications shall be subject to the approval of the Airport Board. 3.     Initial rent for the Additional Taxiway Area shall be $4,952.24 per acre per year. Rent shall be increased by 3% annually, adjusted effective July 1, 2007, and each year thereafter. 4.    The term of this Agreement shall commence on such date as Lessee begins utilizing the taxiway for aircraft operations, and rent on the Additional Taxiway Area as finally determined shall run from that day. The initial term shall end June 30, 2017, unless terminated earlier as provided herein. At the end of the initial term, if possession is not surrendered, this Agreement may be continued from year to year only if Lessee agrees to a new rental amount to be determined solely in Lessor’s discretion. 0 4-01 04/4 5.    All applicable terms and conditions of the "Miller Lanier" lease are hereby incorporated by reference. 6.    This Agreement shall be contingent upon approval of the Murfreesboro City Council. LESSEE: STATE UNIVERSITY AND COMMUNITY COLLEGE SYSTEM OF TENNESSEE BY: Sidney A.TVfc^hee, President Date:                   ______________ Date:                 ________________ BY:________________________________ M.D. Goetz Jr., Commissioner Finance and Administration Date:_________________________________ Approved as to form and legality State Attorney General Date:________________________________ Governor Date:________________________________ By; Charles Manning, ChancqflD 04-0104/ LESSOR: CITY OF MURFREESBORO City of Murfreesboro Approved as to form this the ^c^dav of                          , 2006. Susan Emery MdGannon, City Attorney ity Of, Murfreesboro Da\/id A. lves, Assistant City Attorney City of Murfreesboro 04-01 04/? STATE OF TENNESSEE     ) ss COUNTY OF RUTHERFORD ) Before me, the undersigned authority, a Notary Public in and for said County and State, personally appeared TOMMY BRAGG AND JAMES B. PENNER, with whom I am personally acquainted or who proved to me on the basis of satisfactory evidence, and who, upon their oath acknowledged themselves to be respectively the Mayor and City Recorder of the City of Murfreesboro, and that they as such Mayor and City Recorder, being authorized to do so, executed the within and foregoing instrument for the purposes therein contained, by signing thereto the name of said City, and by attesting said instrument, by themselves as such Mayor and City Recorder, respectively. this the S MY HAND, and Official Seal at office in Murfreesboro, Tennessee, on day of                 _, 2006. « (1 KO/Wo NOTARY PUBLIC My Commission Expires: STATE OF TENNESSEE      ) : ss COUNTY OF RUTHERFORD ) Before me, the undersigned notary public, personally appeared Sidney A. McPhee, with whom I am personally acquainted (or proved to me on the basis of satisfactory evidence), and who, upon oath, acknowledged himself to be the President of Middle Tennessee State University, the within named bargainor, and that he, being authorized to do so, executed the foregoing instrument for the purposes therein contained by personally signing the name of Middle Tennessee State University in his capacity as such officer. WITNESS MY HAND, and Official Seal at office in Murfreesboro, Tennessee, on this the        day of                  , 2006. 0 My Commission Expires: OFRlA^'' Y PUBLIC ' TC   STATE '         OF (SE^L)  TENNESSEE -       NOTARY S' PUBLIC </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9B3C6870-5CA1-43F7-AB40-ED018EF2E58A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2629</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2638</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8367BA6C-E964-493F-873E-9DC096BE840A"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode03E3DEEF-0D7F-471D-A2DE-C26FC4BB7B45">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2629</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2630</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8367BA6C-E964-493F-873E-9DC096BE840A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode535ED157-FD7F-42E5-AFA3-DE66B88321F6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2630</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2638</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8367BA6C-E964-493F-873E-9DC096BE840A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4952.24</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>