<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369909" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeBB7125C0-A752-440A-B7B6-75F15CBB039F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2700</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode94924601-2B60-4867-9D7E-3FB3FD4E6525">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1200</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode6506DDAD-445C-4F78-9A03-331E9D0AA9F9">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">PROFESSIONAL SERVICES AGREEMENT AGREEMENT BETWEEN TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS AND ROBERT MULLEN This Agreement is made this 10th day of March, 2008, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as the "Institution", and Robert Mullen, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: 1. Robert Mullen, Associate Director of Institutional Research and Planning, University of Missouri System, on April 7, 2008 will provide a presentation on Data Warehousing. B. The Institution agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1. Rate of compensation: $1500 for providing the presentation and participating in discussions. Also, in addition, actual travel costs within TBR policy will be reimbursed for an amount not to exceed $1,200. 2. Payment will be made in full upon completion of the presentation and discussions. Payment to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, but only after receipt of invoices for services performed/items delivered. Final payment to the Contractor shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Contract 3. In no event shall the liability of the Institution under this contract exceed $2,700.00. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this agreement. 1. The Contractor warrants that no part of the total contract amount provided herein shall be paid directly or indirectly to any officer or employee of the state of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, subContractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this agreement. If the Contractor is an individual, the Contractor warrants that within the past six months he has not been and during the term of this contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 2. The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990_and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age disability, veteran status or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3. The term of this contract shall be from April 6, 2008 to April 8,2008. 4. This agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 10 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 5. If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this agreement, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate this agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this agreement by the Contractor. 6. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 7. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the Institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 8. The Contractor shall not assign this agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution or Board of Regents, as appropriate. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractorwas or is currently ineligible'to bid on the contract.................................................. 9. This agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 10. Compensation to the Contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be in the amount of actual cost to the Contractor, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the Tennessee Board of Regents policies http://www.tbr.state.tn.us/policies guidelines/business policies/4-03-03-00.htm, as they may be from time to time amended. 11. Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, 0620 In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signature. (EDUCATIONAL POLICY INSTITUTE) Robert Mullen (TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS) BY: Charles W. Manning TITLE:                  __ DATE:  ^lil/tedg__________ TITLE: Chancellor_______ DATE: ADDRESS: 5205 Forest Glen Drive Columbia, MO 65203 </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode45B349CC-D363-4BF0-B97C-5D7A25433079">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">980</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">986</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode94924601-2B60-4867-9D7E-3FB3FD4E6525"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6276EAF6-71A4-483A-B31F-4206C4C7BD2A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">980</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">981</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode94924601-2B60-4867-9D7E-3FB3FD4E6525"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6FE2CE20-A598-402C-B743-E0F8C27CD9A8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">981</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">986</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode94924601-2B60-4867-9D7E-3FB3FD4E6525"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1200</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode25C7825D-D525-4837-8E7F-0315B83F6715">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1438</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1447</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeBB7125C0-A752-440A-B7B6-75F15CBB039F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4EA8FAAD-AECD-448E-9A37-E7525BBED586">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1438</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1439</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeBB7125C0-A752-440A-B7B6-75F15CBB039F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD09C8EC5-99D6-4353-8911-BE989F790798">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1439</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1447</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeBB7125C0-A752-440A-B7B6-75F15CBB039F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2700</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>