<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369976" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode9CF47C04-DC06-42D0-9845-B0EC23F6D802">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">220000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode3B7F2660-CAF1-4A0A-A834-9DC66BE3172F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">120000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode92747371-5A65-4557-BEA2-E26F08CE8FDB">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">200000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode84F4E451-469B-4BBB-BFC4-589260F659F7">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">CO 9 - 0613 AGREEMENT BETWEEN MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY AND TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS This Agreement is made this 1st day of January, 2009, by and between Middle Tennessee State University hereinafter referred to as the "Institution", and the Tennessee Board of Regents, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: 1. Provide a training program to teach the D2L course management system to the Tennessee Center for Child Welfare curriculum development staff and others at a mutually agreeable time according to the pricing schedule below. 2.  Provide the development of course shells, registration of students, uploading students into courses, monitoring course management system, and general maintenance of course management system. 3.  Provide 24x7 technical help desk for end user. 4. Provide reporting system to be accessed by Middle Tennessee State University, Tennessee Center for Child Welfare, and Tennessee Board of Regents. 5.  Provide ongoing support to course developers B. The Institution agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: •  In the fiscal year ending June 30, 2009, The Tennessee Center for Child Welfare is estimated to pay the College of Continuing Education and Distance Learning $200,000 for the development and provisioning of these services. •  In the fiscal year ending June 30, 2009, the College of Continuing Education and Distance Learning will pay the Tennessee Board of Regents 60% of the funds received which is estimated to result in $120,000 payable to TBR. •  In the fiscal year ending June 30, 2010, The Tennessee Center for Child Welfare is estimated to pay the College of Continuing Education and Distance Learning $200,000 for the development and provisioning of these services. The Tennessee Center for Child Welfare will be billed monthly in equal amounts. •  In the fiscal year ending June 30, 2010, the College of Continuing Education and Distance Learning will pay the Tennessee Board of Regents 50% of the funds received which is estimated to result in $100,000 payable to TBR. 2.     Payments will be made on a one time basis for FY2009 and on a quarterly basis for FY2010. The amount will based upon the applicable percentages of the gross receipts for that period. 3.     Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, provided that payments shall be made only upon submittal of invoices by the Contractor, and after performance of the portion of the services which the invoiced amount represents. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Agreement. 4.     In no event shall the liability of the Institution under this Contract exceed $220,000.00. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement. 1.     The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 2.     The term of this Contract shall be from January 1, 2009 to December 31, 2010. Thereafter, this Contract shall remain in effect for the additional periods of one (1) year each, up to a total of five (5) years subject to successful negotiation. 3.     This Contract may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 90 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 4.     If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this Agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this Agreement, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate this Contract and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. 5.     This Contract may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 6.    The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the Institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 9.     This Contract is subject to the allotment of state and/or federal funds, and may be null and void unless funds have been appropriated and are available for the purchase of the service or item which forms the basis of the Contract. 10.    This Contract shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or designee and the Chancellor of the Tennessee Board of Regents. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. Tennessee Board of Regents BY: TITZE: John W. Cothern TITLE: Charles Manning Chancellor Senior Vice President DATE: _</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB1C2E0D4-F5E0-4F71-8E19-2A20AE50FF23">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1455</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1463</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode92747371-5A65-4557-BEA2-E26F08CE8FDB"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode71DE56A7-D942-4E4E-BAB1-B76ACA4F4F73">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1455</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1456</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode92747371-5A65-4557-BEA2-E26F08CE8FDB"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode602D2350-6845-4D9D-9996-63C7536E5CED">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1456</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1463</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode92747371-5A65-4557-BEA2-E26F08CE8FDB"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">200000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode306251AD-18E5-4635-A691-7BF9AE9184BD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1720</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1721</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3B7F2660-CAF1-4A0A-A834-9DC66BE3172F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode2878D98F-721A-47DA-A2D7-C3471C390456">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1720</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1728</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3B7F2660-CAF1-4A0A-A834-9DC66BE3172F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode66973318-8E96-4B1F-9E79-0D395328E24D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1721</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1728</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3B7F2660-CAF1-4A0A-A834-9DC66BE3172F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">120000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode72B1F6AE-9F79-4DB4-82BA-9F30EECA92D7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2935</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2946</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9CF47C04-DC06-42D0-9845-B0EC23F6D802"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBD39BFCF-5FCD-4A75-9475-3B45251E7882">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2935</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2936</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9CF47C04-DC06-42D0-9845-B0EC23F6D802"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD291692D-CE5C-4327-B6FE-98E839AA37E3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2936</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2946</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9CF47C04-DC06-42D0-9845-B0EC23F6D802"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">220000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>