<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369879" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeD09E0A8A-1EC1-4626-A2C6-9877230A9BC2">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2322</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode77C086A2-931E-410C-BAF5-648FDD51E5C3">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AMENDMENT TO ROOMS CONTRACT BETWEEN HOLIDAY INN EXPRESS HOTEL &amp; SUITES AND TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS This amendment to the Rooms Contract (“Agreement”) by and between the Holiday Inn Express Hotel &amp; Suites (“Hotel”) and the Tennessee Board of Regents (“TBR”) is made and entered into and effective August 22,2007. WITNESSETH: WHEREAS, Hotel and the TBR agree, through this Amendment, to reflect certain modifications, additions, and clarifications to the terms and conditions in the Agreement. NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration for the mutual covenants undertaken herein the parties hereby agree to amend the terms and conditions of the Agreement specifically as set forth herein: 1.      Prevailing Documents. In the event of any conflict or inconsistency between the terms and conditions of this Amendment and the Agreement, the terms of this Amendment shall prevail. 2.      No. 1. Room Rates. Delete this section and replace with the following: “Hotel shall provide room rates as quoted to TBR, regardless of the number of rooms utilized.” 3.      No. 2. Deposit/Roominq List, Delete the first sentence of this section and replace with the following: “As a state agency, TBR shall not pay deposits. All charges for function space, audio visual rental, food, as well as certain guest rooms for TBR Staff only will be applied to a master bill which will be paid in full upon receipt of invoice from Hotel.” 4.      No. 4. Cancellation. Delete the second and third sentence of this section and replace with the following, “As a state agency, TBR shall not pay penalty or cancellation charges. TBR shall pay any actual reasonable documented damages or loss to Hotel for which it is liable under Tennessee Law.” 5.      No, 8. Alternative Accommodations. Add the following sentence to this section: “All alternative accommodations must be pre-approved, in writing, by TBR.” 6.      No. 9. Delete this section in its entirety and replace with the following: “The Hotel shall work with TBR to reschedule this event, at no additional expense, due to Hotel’s non-performance of this contract when causes prevent or interfere with the Hotel’s performance of this Agreement.” Please add the following clauses: 7.      Hold Harmless. As a state agency, TBR shall not hold harmless or indemnify the Hotel. Any and all claims against TBR for property damage or loss resulting from acts or omissions or TBR through its employees or agents in performing its responsibilities under this Amendment Holiday Inn Express and TBR Page 2 agreement shall be submitted to the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee for disposition in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Tennessee Code Annotated. Damages recoverable against TBR shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Commission. 8.      Maximum Liability. The maximum liability under this Agreement shall not exceed $2,322.00. 9.      Audit. The Hotel shall maintain documentation for all charges against TBR under this agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Hotel, insofar as they related to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 10.     Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4- 124, requires that Hotel attest in writing that Hotel will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on Attachment A, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference. If Hotel is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Hotel shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Hotel may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. In witness of the acceptance of the terms of this Amendment, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBC08F20D-8E61-4399-A790-1AA14BA4BB50">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2873</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2882</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD09E0A8A-1EC1-4626-A2C6-9877230A9BC2"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode12578D7A-9DAA-460E-A914-A6B2B7886D24">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2873</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2874</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD09E0A8A-1EC1-4626-A2C6-9877230A9BC2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1FDE29F0-480E-4926-9BDA-D262DE099EB3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2874</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2882</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD09E0A8A-1EC1-4626-A2C6-9877230A9BC2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2322</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>