<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369836" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode60FF112C-6BDE-40BA-A543-D9038994C799">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">510000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode45CFBF09-EE39-4F75-8BE9-9581D7C938EE">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AMENDMENT No. 2 TO THE SYSTEM PURCHASE CONTRACT BETWEEN PACIOLAN, INC. AND UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS This Amendment No. 2 (“Amendment”) to the System Purchase Contract executed on May 25, 1999, as amended (“Original Agreement”) is entered into effective as of___________________ , 2007 (“Amendment No. 2 Effective Date”) by and between PACIOLAN, INC., a Delaware corporation (“Paciolan”), and the UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS (“Customer”). Background WHEREAS, Paciolan and Customer previously amended the Original Agreement under that certain Amendment No. 1 effective June 30, 2003 (“Amendment No. 1); and WHEREAS, Paciolan and Customer now wish to amend and supplement the Original Agreement to provide new hardware, software, professional services, and hosting services, as well as specify the applicable costs. NOW THEREFORE, in consideration of the foregoing and other good and valuable consideration, the receipt of which is hereby acknowledged, the parties hereto agree to further modify the Original Agreement as set forth in this Amendment. Original Agreement Amendments 1.      Hosting Services. Paciolan shall provide to Customer hosting services as set forth on Exhibit A.. 2.     Supplemental Investment Analysis. The Supplemental Investment Analysis attached hereto as Exhibit B supplements the Investment Analysis to the Original Agreement, as amended by Amendment No. 1. The Supplemental Investment Analysis contains the listing of new hardware, software, and professional services being provided to Customer under this Amendment. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in the Original Agreement, all Software shall be provided in object code only. 3.     Fee and Payment Terms. The fees for Paciolan to provide the new hardware, software, professional services, and hosting services are attached hereto as Exhibit C. The maximum liability to the Customer under this Amendment shall not exceed $510,000.00. 4.     Term. The Original Agreement is hereby amended to include the following language which is provided in lieu of, and supersedes, any conflicting language in the Original Agreement: “The term shall begin on the effective date hereof and shall continue through the five (5) year anniversary of the Amendment No. 2 Effective Date.” 5.      Defense Against Claims. The following language shall be added to this Section: “No cost or expenses shall be incurred for the account of CUSTOMER without its written consent. The Attorney General for the State of Tennessee reserves the right to participate in the defense of any such action. CUSTOMER shall not be liable for any award or judgment against CUSTOMER or the State of Tennessee reached by compromise or settlement unless CUSTOMER accepts the compromise or accepts the settlement. CUSTOMER shall have the right to enter into negotiations for the right to effect settlement or compromise of any such action, but no such settlement or compromise shall be binding upon CUSTOMER and the State of Tennessee unless approved by the Attorney General”. 6.     Limitation of Liability. The second sentence of this Section shall be amended to read: “To the maximum extent allowed by applicable law: Paciolan is not liable for any indirect, special, or consequential damages arising out of the use of any of the components or services covered by this contract”. 7.      Settlement of Disputes. This Section is deleted in its entirety. 8.      All exhibits attached hereto are incorporated herein by reference. Except as amended by this Amendment, all other terms and conditions set forth in the Original Agreement, as amended by Amendment No. 1, including the defined terms, shall remain in full force and effect. If there is any conflict between the terms and conditions of this Amendment and the Original Agreement, as amended by Amendment No. 1, then the terms and conditions of this Amendment shall prevail. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have caused this Amendment to be executed and do each here by represent that their respective signatory whose signature appears below has been and is on the Amendment Effective Date duly authorized by all necessary and appropriate corporate action to execute this Amendment. REVIEWED TO LEGAL FORM &amp; CONTENT A D’O A. offTce OF LEGAL counsel” 3/2«/o7 UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS REVIEWED TO LEGAL FORM &amp; CONTENT A D’O A. offTce OF LEGAL counsel” 3/2«/o7 UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS Signature:  Name:  Title:  Date:    TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS Approved:  Signature: it/,   Name:  Title: CAftwce (lor Date: *+ 30-0? </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1FB27D04-AC5F-4958-AC33-39F7921E2D3B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1901</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1912</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode60FF112C-6BDE-40BA-A543-D9038994C799"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode000EE568-B976-425C-8B35-1217F2FB3CB9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1901</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1902</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode60FF112C-6BDE-40BA-A543-D9038994C799"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6768F332-4979-4063-A6E6-974BD82D528B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1902</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1912</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode60FF112C-6BDE-40BA-A543-D9038994C799"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">510000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>