<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369939" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode5279A40C-29C5-47BB-95A6-0078452636EE">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">100000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEA60571-894F-4418-93C6-90A29A249306">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeA46C01BC-8887-47BE-9D7B-74CB32114797">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2650000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode02F66A57-A09A-4E3F-B958-9CFDC7DA3D33">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">265000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode5B9D9EEA-44FF-4EAC-B534-6029ACA09F97">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">CONTRACT BETWEEN MOTLOW STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND Follett Higher Education Group This Contract, by and between Motlow State Community College, hereinafter referred to as the "Institution" or "College" and Follett Higher Education Group, hereinafter referred to as the "Contractor," is for the management and operation of the Institution's bookstores, as further defined in the "SCOPE OF SERVICES." The Contractor is A FOR-PROFIT CORPORATION. The Contractor's address is: 1818 Swift Drive Oak Brook, IL 60523-1567 The Contractor's place of incorporation or organization is Illinois. A.      SCOPE OF SERVICES: A.l. The scope of this Contract is to operate the Institution's Bookstores and to maintain the bookstore's services as an integral element of the Institution's educational and academic mission. The bookstore is established and maintained solely for the convenience of students, faculty, staff, alumni, visitors and guests of the College in space to be provided by the College. Additional specific service to be provided are detailed in Section C of the Contractor's proposal dated April 29, 2008. B. CONTRACT TERM: B.l. Contract Term. This Contract shall be effective for the period commencing on July 1, 2008 and ending on June 30, 2009 with an annual option for nine (9) renewals through June 30, 2018. The Institution shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. B.2. Term Extension. The Institution and Contractor reserves the right to extend this Contract for an additional period or periods of time representing increments of no more than one year and a total contract term of no more than ten years, provided that the Contractor notifies the Institution in writing of its intention extend the Contract at least 60 days prior to the Contract expiration date. An extension of the term of this Contract will be effected through an amendment to the Contract. B.3. Subject to Funds Availability. The Contract is subject to the appropriation and availability of State and/or Federal funds. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, the Institution reserves the right to terminate the Contract upon written notice to the Contractor.   Termination under this Section E.2 shall not be deemed a breach of Contract by the Institution. Upon receipt of the written notice, the Contractor shall cease all work associated with the Contract. Should such an event occur, the Contractor shall be entitled to compensation for all satisfactory and authorized services completed as of the termination date. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to recover from the Institution any actual, general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. c. PAYMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS: C.l. Monetary Terms and Conditions. Monetary terms and conditions of this Contract are detailed in Attachment 6.4 - Project Narrative and Documentation (Scope of Services) Section 6.0 and Attachment 6.6 - Monetary Proposal s Scoring Guide of the Contractor's response to proposal dated April 24, 2008. The minimum guarantee to be paid to Institution by Contractor is $265,000/year. Commission paid to Institution will begin when yearly sales volume exceeds the benchmarks provided in Contractor's proposed in the monetary proposal and scoring guide. The minimum commission to be paid by the Contractor to the institution over the ten (10) year life of this Contract is $2,650,000. D. TERMS AND CONDITIONS: D.l. Required Approvals. The Institution is not bound by this Contract until it is approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee laws and regulations as shown on the signature page of this Contract. D.2. Modification and Amendment. This Contract may be modified only by a written amendment executed by all parties hereto and approved by the appropriate officials. D.3. Ethnicity. This Contract shall not be executed until the Contractor has completed the Minority/Ethnicity Form. D. 4 . Termination for Convenience. The Institution may terminate this Contract without cause for any reason. Termination under this Section D. 4 shall not be deemed a Breach of Contract by the Institution. The Institution shall give the Contractor at least sixty (60) days written notice before the effective termination date. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to any actual general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. D.5. Termination for Cause. If the Contractor fails to perform its obligations under this Contract in a timely or proper manner, or if the Contractor violates any term of this Contract, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate the Contract. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the Institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Contract by the Contractor. D.6. Subcontracting. The Contractor shall not assiqn this Contract or enter into a subcontract for any of the services performed under this Contract without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution. If such subcontracts are approved by the Institution, they shall contain, at a minimum, sections of this Contract pertaining to "Conflicts of Interest" and "Nondiscrimination". Notwithstanding any use of approved subcontractors, the Contractor shall be the prime contractor and shall be responsible for all work performed. D. 7 . Conflicts of Interest. The Contractor warrants that no part of the total Contract amount shall be paid directly or indirectly to an employee or official of the State of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as an officer, agent, employee, subcontractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this Contract. D.8. Nondiscrimination. The Contractor hereby agrees, warrants, and assures that no person shall be excluded from participation in, be denied benefits of, or be otherwise subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Contract or in the employment practices of the Contractor on the grounds of disability, age, race, color, religion, sex, veteran status, national origin, or any other classification protected by Federal, or State constitutional or statutory law. The Contractor shall, upon request, show proof of such nondiscrimination and shall post in conspicuous places, available to all employees and applicants, notices of nondiscrimination. D.9. Prohibition of Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4- 124, requires that Contractor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the service of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance ("the Attestation"), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference as Attachment I. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents Institution or any other sate entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. D.10. Records. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all commissions paid to the Institution under this Contract. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or commissions paid under this Contract, shall be maintained for a period of three (3) full years from the date of the final payment and shall be subject to audit at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice by the Institution, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. The financial statements shall be prepared in accordance with generally accepted accounting principles. D. 11. Monitoring. The Contractor's activities conducted and records maintained pursuant to this Contract shall be subject to monitoring and evaluation by the Institution, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. D.12. Progress Reports. The Contractor shall submit brief, periodic, progress reports to the Institution as requested. The Institution requests annual reports as a minimum. However, should the situation warrant, the reports may be requested more frequently. A sales breakdown supporting the commission paid must be submitted to the Institution monthly. D.13. Strict Performance. Failure by any party to this Contract to insist in any one or more cases upon the strict performance of any of the terms, covenants, conditions, or provisions of this Contract shall not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of any such term, covenant, condition, or provision. No term or condition of this Contract shall be held to be waived, modified, or deleted except by a written amendment signed by the parties hereto. D. 14 . Independent Contractor. The parties hereto, in the performance of this Contract, shall not act as employees, partners, joint venturers, or associates of one another. It is expressly acknowledged by the parties hereto that the parties are independent contracting entities and that nothing in this Contract shall be construed to create an employer/employee relationship or to allow either to exercise control or direction over the manner or method by which the other transacts its business affairs or provides its usual services. The employees or agents of one party shall not be deemed or construed to be the employees or agents of the other party for any purpose whatsoever. The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of the Institution, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance on the Contractor's employees, and to pay all applicable taxes incident to this Contract. D.15. Institution Liability. The Institution shall have no liability except as specifically provided in this Contract. D.16. Force Majeure. The obligations of the parties to this Contract are subject to prevention by causes beyond the parties' control that could not be avoided by the exercise of due care including, but not limited to, acts of God, riots, wars, epidemics or any other similar cause. D.17. State and Federal Compliance. The Contractor shall comply with all applicable State and Federal laws and regulations, including Institution policies and guidelines in the performance of this Contract. D. 18 . Governing Law. This Contract shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee. The Contractor agrees that it will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Tennessee Claims Commission in actions that may arise under this Contract. The Contractor acknowledges and agrees that any rights or claims against the Institution or its employees hereunder, and any remedies arising therefrom, shall be subject to and limited to those rights and remedies, if any, available under Tennessee Code Annotated, Sections 9-8-101 through 9-8-407. D.19. Severability. If any terms or conditions of this Contract are held to be invalid or unenforceable as a matter of law, the other terms and conditions hereof shall not be affected thereby and shall remain in full force and effect. To this end, the terms and conditions of this Contract are declared severable. D.20. Headings. Section headings of this Contract are for reference purposes only and shall not be construed as part of this Contract. E. ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS: E. 1. Communications and Contacts. The Institution: Mike Posey Vice President for Business Affairs P. 0. Box 8500  Lynchburg, Tennessee 37352-8500 The Contractor: Gerald Sullivan Vice President Marketing 230 Woodlawn Avenue Athens, Georgia 30606-4354 All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications shall be sent in a manner that verifies proof of delivery. Any communication by facsimile transmission shall also be sent by United States mail on the same date as the facsimile transmission. All communications which relate to any changes to the Contract shall not be considered effective until agreed to, in writing, by both parties. E.2 . Breach. A Party shall be deemed to have breached the Contract if any of the following occurs (However, this list is not exclusive): failure to perform in accordance with any term or provision of the Contract; partial performance of any term or provision of the Contract: _any act prohibited or restricted by the Contract, or violation of any warranty. E.3. Performance Bond. Contractor shall furnish a performance bond in the amount equal to One hundred thousand ($100,000), guaranteeing full and faithful performance of all undertakings and obligations under this Contract for the initial Contract term and all extensions thereof. The bond shall be in the manner and form prescribed by the Institution, must be issued through a company licensed to issue such a bond in the State of Tennessee. The Contractor shall provide the bond to the Institution no later than the effective date of this Contract. Failure to provide the performance bond prior to the deadline as required shall result in contract termination E.4. Institution Furnished Property. The Contractor shall be responsible for the correct use, maintenance, and protection of all articles of nonexpendable, tangible, personal property furnished by the Institution for the Contractor's temporary use under this Contract. Upon termination of this Contract, all property furnished shall be returned to the Institution in good order and condition as when received, reasonable use and wear thereof expected. Should the property be destroyed, lost, or stolen, the Contractor shall be responsible to the Institution for the residual value of the property at the time of loss. E.5. Contract Documents. Included in this Contract by reference are the following documents in the following order: a.      This Contract document and its attachments b.      The Request for Proposal and its associated amendments c.      The Contractor's response to the Institution's questions. d.      The Contractor's Proposal In the event of a discrepancy or ambiguity regarding the interpretation of this Contract, these documents shall govern in order of precedence as listed above. E. 6. Prohibited Advertising. The Contractor shall not refer to this Contract or the Contractor's relationship with the Institution hereunder in commercial advertising in such a manner as to state or imply that the Contractor or the Contractor's services are endorsed. E.7 . Hold Harmless. The Contractor aqrees to indemnify and hold harmless the Institution as well as its officers, agents, and employees from and against any and all claims, liabilities, losses, and causes of action which may arise, accrue, or result to any person, firm, corporation, or other entity which may be injured or damaged as a result of acts, omissions, or negligence on the part of the Contractor, its employees, or any person acting for or on its or their behalf relating to this Contract. The Contractor further agrees it shall be liable for the reasonable cost of attorneys for the Institution in the event such service is necessitated to enforce the terms of this Contract or otherwise enforce the obligations of the Contractor to the Institution. In the event of any such suit or claim, the Contractor shall give the Institution immediate notice thereof and shall provide all assistance required by the Institution in the Institution's defense. The Institution shall give the Contractor written notice of any such claim or suit, and the Contractor shall have full right and obligation to conduct the Contractor's own defense thereof. Nothing contained herein shall be deemed to accord to the Contractor, through its attorney(s), the right to represent the Institution in any legal matter, such rights being governed by Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 8-6-106. E.8. Debarment and Suspension. The Contractor certifies, to the best of its knowledge and belief, that it and its principals: a.      are not presently debarred, suspended, propoOsed for debarment, declared ineligible, or voluntarily excluded from covered transactions by any Federal or state department or agency; b.      have not within a three (3) year period preceding this Contract been convicted of, or had a civil judgment rendered against them from commission of fraud, or a criminal offence in connection with obtaining attempting to obtain, or performing a public (Federal, State, or Local) transaction or grant under a public transaction; violation of Federal or State antitrust statutes or commission of embezzlement, theft, forgery, bribery, falsification, or destruction of records, making false statements, or receiving stolen property; c.      are not presently indicted for or otherwise criminally or civilly charged by a government entity (Federal, State, or Local) with commission of any of the offenses listed in section b. of this certification; and d.      have not within a three (3) year period preceding this Contract had one or more public transactions (Federal, State, or Local) terminated for cause or default. Successful Proposer must provide and maintain a commercial general liability policy. The policy shall provide coverage which includes, but is not limited to, bodily injury, personal injury, death, property damage and medical claims, with minimum limits of $1,000,000 per occurrence, $3,000,000 in the aggregate. The Proposer shall maintain workers' compensation coverage or a self-insured program as required under Tennessee law, with Employer's Liability Limits of $100,000. The Proposer shall deliver to the Institution a certificate of insurance no later than the effective date of the contract. If any policy providing insurance required by the contract is cancelled prior to the policy expiration date, the Proposer, upon receiving a notice of cancellation, shall give immediate notice to the Institution. The enumeration in the contract or in this document of the kinds and amounts of liability insurance shall not abridge, diminish or affect the contractor's legal responsibilities for the consequences of accidents arising out of or resulting from the services of the successful bidder under this contract. Failure to provide evidence of such insurance coverage is a material breach and grounds for termination of the contract negotiations. Any insurance required by the Institution shall be in form and substance acceptable to the Institution. IN WITNESS WHEREOF: Follett Higher Education Group [NAME AND TITLE] Date APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS (IF APPLICABLE) : Attachment ATTESTATION RE PERSONNEL USED IN CONTRACT PERFORMANCE ATTESTATION RE PERSONNEL USED IN CONTRACT PERFORMANCE SUBJECT CONTRACT NUMBER:  CONTRACTOR LEGAL ENTITY NAME:  FEDERAL EMPLOYER IDENTIFICATION NUMBER: (or Social Security Number)  The Contractor, identified above, does hereby attest, certify, warrant, and assure that the Contractor shall not knowingly utilize the services of an illegal immigrant in the performance of this Contract and shall not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor who will utilize the services of an illegal immigrant in the performance of this Contract. SIGNATURE &amp; DATE: NOTICE:  This attestation MUST be signed by an individual empowered to contractually bind the Contractor. If said individual is not the chief executive or president, this document shall attach evidence showing the individual's authority to contractually bind the Contractor.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6F663871-0E24-4192-9718-3F8D10BB8DDC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3223</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3231</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode02F66A57-A09A-4E3F-B958-9CFDC7DA3D33"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE34F5D56-F258-4F95-BCF9-B0A39D31ECA5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3223</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3224</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode02F66A57-A09A-4E3F-B958-9CFDC7DA3D33"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0E4EC81-9AC7-4FED-BE90-21D915F84505">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3224</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3231</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode02F66A57-A09A-4E3F-B958-9CFDC7DA3D33"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">265000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode10C09EE0-CECF-48B3-AD6E-2200F5BABBEF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3525</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3526</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA46C01BC-8887-47BE-9D7B-74CB32114797"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0703DCD-39F2-4038-B55E-0020A9980F15">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3525</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3535</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA46C01BC-8887-47BE-9D7B-74CB32114797"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0CEA9705-5E41-40F1-A9E5-DDF7D1846051">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3526</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3535</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA46C01BC-8887-47BE-9D7B-74CB32114797"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2650000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7F2CFDA3-0734-4D42-972F-1A41C725CC1A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">13139</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">13159</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5279A40C-29C5-47BB-95A6-0078452636EE"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">100000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0AA24F28-528E-43D9-A78A-FD237B6DDF9D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">13139</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">13159</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5279A40C-29C5-47BB-95A6-0078452636EE"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDA6C3C3A-B8AF-480C-8729-55C1504A060E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17987</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17997</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEA60571-894F-4418-93C6-90A29A249306"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD2242B19-BB5F-4099-B431-29EB93723FB5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17987</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17988</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEA60571-894F-4418-93C6-90A29A249306"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode29BDAC32-35E6-4CE1-954E-8CA800C6BAE7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17988</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">17997</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEA60571-894F-4418-93C6-90A29A249306"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>