<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369898" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE48E33CD-A605-4B89-8E06-5622A4055F26">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">0.3</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode21BC0B52-938D-43B6-80C3-66B3B892AFE3">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeF6DE7B25-97B2-43FE-B651-10689A07FBA1">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">0</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode78198E76-47CB-4471-9149-D056B29566C0">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">250</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeEA68109F-E587-4D71-8AEF-56750040FDFC">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode70CADA9C-2D29-4DD7-B27F-40996F763589">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">99</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeF916C8C1-1DE5-425B-97B9-646866E62174">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">hotel I J ■[RESTQN TN Board of Regents 1415 Murfreesboro Road Suite 350 Nashville, TN 37217-2833 615-366-4442 This contract is presented, as of this day, December 14, 2007 between the Hotel Preston and the TN Board of Regents GUEST ROOM ACCOMODATIONS AND RATES: Upon receipt of this signed contract, the following rooms will be placed on hold until your specific cut-off date as provided in this contract. Check In - 1/6/2008 Check Out - 1/10/2008 ROOM TYPE RATE* 1/6/2008 1/7/2008 1/8/200 8 1/9/2008   Sunday Monday Tuesday Wednesd ay   King or Double $99.00 5 30 30 30   Total  5 30 30 30   *AU rates are subject to a city and state tax, which are currently 15.25% plus a $2.00 convention tax per room, per night. The Hotel recognizes that the TN Board of Regents is tax exempt and will therefore only incur a 6% occupancy tax. BILLING: Indidvidual guest are responsible for Charges COMMISSION: All room rates quoted are non-commissionable. CHECK-IN / CHECK-OUT TIMES: Check in time is 3:00pm. Check out is time is 12:00 pm. CANCELLATION If cancellation of group rooms becomes necessary the hotel must be notified in writing. As a state agency, TBR shall not pay deposits, penalty or cancellation charges. Should the reservations not be fully utilized by TBR, TBR shall pay any actual, reasonable documented damages or loss to the Hotel for which it is liable under Tennessee law. RESERVATION PROCEDURES: Individual Guest will Call Hotel Direct for Reservations RESERVATION CUT-OFF DATE: The Hotel agrees to hold the above room block until 12/24/2007. At that time, rooms not utilized will be released. The Hotel may continue to accept reservations from your attendees after that date, subject to availability. MEETING REQUIREMENTS MEETING REQUIREMENTS DAY DATE START END FUNCTION ROOM SETUP ATTD RENTAL Monday 1/7/2008 08:00 AM 11:59 PM Meeting Two- Hermitage/One- Donelson Crescent Rounds 35 $250 Monday 1/7/2008 05:00 PM 09:00 PM Dinner Create-Lincoya Rounds 8 35 $0 Tuesday 1/8/2008 08:00 AM 11:59 PM Meeting Two- Hermitage/One- Donelson Crescent Rounds 35 $250 Tuesday 1/8/2008 11:00 AM 01:30 PM Lunch Create-Lincoya Rounds 8 35 $0 Tuesday 1/8/2008 05:00 PM 09:00 PM Dinner Create-Lincoya Rounds 8 35 $0 Wednesday 1/9/2008 08:00 AM 11:59 PM Meeting Two- Hermitage/One- Donelson Crescent Rounds 35 $250 Wednesday 1/9/2008 11:00 AM 01:30 PM Lunch Create-Lincoya Rounds 8 35 $0 Wednesday 1/9/2008 05:00 PM 09:00 PM Dinner Create-Lincoya Rounds 8 35 $0 Thursday 1/10/2008 08:00 AM 05:00 PM Meeting Two- Hermitage/One- Donelson Crescent Rounds 35 $250 Thursday 1/10/2008 11:00 AM 01:30 PM Lunch Create-Lincoya Rounds 8 35 $0 Tax &amp; Gratuity: To ensure the superior service of Hotel Preston, 20% gratuity will be added to all room rental, food, beverage, and audiovisual costs. 9.25% sales tax will apply. Hotel understands that TBR is exempt from sales tax. Guarantee: Final menu selections should be submitted FOUR weeks prior to the function to insure the availability of the desired menu. All food and beverage must be supplied and prepared by the Hotel. No outside food or beverage is permitted in any banquet or meeting room without prior written approval of the hotel. Unconsumed food is not permitted to be taken out of the hotel. In order to provide for all attendees, a guaranteed count will be needed 72 hours in advance of the function. TBR understands that the hotel id relying on TBR’s use of food and beverage. Should these not be fully utilized by TBR, TBR shall pay any actual, reasonable documented damages or loss to the hotel for which it is liable under Tennessee Law. Should you be unable to provide us with a count, Hotel Preston will refer to the originally contracted number and prepare accordingly. This will ensure the comfort of all in attendance. Labor Charge: In the case on-site changes are requested, additional labor fees may be assessed. Food &amp; Beverage: Outside food and beverage is prohibited and Hotel Preston does not permit the removal of any foods provided by the hotel. Room Rental: Room rental fees are determined upon original program details. Room Assignments: The Catering Department reserves the right to reassign functions rooms to best service and utilize space according to the final guaranteed number of guests upon written consent of TBR. Boxes: Hotel Preston will gladly receive the supplies necessary for any function. The shipment of such material will be accepted no sooner than 3 days prior to the function. No charge for 5 parcels or less. For 6 or more parcels a fee of $3.00 per box (under 50 pounds) will be applied. For all boxes over 50 pounds, a fee of $0.30 per pound will be applied. Force Majeure: The performance of this agreement by either party is subject to acts of God, war within the continental US, governmental authority, disaster, or civil disorder within 20 miles of the hotel, facilities, or any other cause making it illegal to provide the facilities, or to hold the meeting. Hotel Approval: The hotel reserves the right to exercise final authority over bands, DJ’s, musicians and other entertainment in regard to volume and professionalism, whether they are engaged by the customer or through the hotel. The hotel reserves the right to require security for any functions the hotel deems appropriate or necessary at the clients’ expense with written approval from the TBR. Any and all claims against the TBR for property damage or loss resulting from acts or omissions of the TBR through its employees or agents in performing its responsibilities under this agreement shall be submitted to the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee for disposition in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Tennessee Code Annotated. Damages recoverable against the TBR shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the commission. Billing: AU charges for function space, audio visual rental, food and beverage, and service charges will be applied to the master bill which will be paid in full upon receipt of invoice from the hotel. The master bill shall be paid within 30 days of receipt of invoice by TBR. Participants shall be responsible for sleeping rooms independent of the master bill. Cancellations: If cancellation of group rooms becomes necessary the hotel must be notified in writing. As a state agency, TBR shall not pay deposits, penalty or cancellation charges. Should the reservations not be fully utilized by TBR, TBR shall pay any actual, reasonable documented damages or loss to the Hotel for which it is liable under Tennessee law. Acceptance: Space will be confirmed on a definite basis with the return of your signed agreement by 12/18/07. Failure to do so will result in function space being released and contract void. INSURANCE Each of us shall carry adequate personal property, liability and other insurance protecting against any claims arising from any activities conducted in the Hotel Preston during your stay. Upon request, you shall provide a certificate evidencing your insurance to the Hotel. Hotel understands that TBR, as a state agency, is self-funded and does not carry or maintain professional liability insurance. Upon requests, TBR shall provide the hotel a copy of the State’s Certificate of Self-Insurance. The Hotel Preston shall not be responsible for the security of exhibits, presentation materials or other personal property of your organization, your attendees, guests or exhibitors. You acknowledge that the Hotel Preston, its owners, employees and agents, do not maintain insurance coverage covering such exhibits, materials or personal property. INDEMNIFICATION As a state agency, TBR shall not hold harmless or indemnify the hotel. Any and all claims against the TBR for property damage or loss resulting from acts or omissions of the TBR through its employees or agents in performing its responsibilies under this agreement shall be submitted to the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee for the disposition in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Tennessee Code Annotated. Damages recoverable against the TBR shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the commission. CONTRACT AUTHORIZATION: The persons signing this contract on behalf of the Hotel Preston and TN Board of Regents, respectively, each warrant that they are authorized to make the agreements set out on behalf of the Hotel Preston and TN Board of Regents, respectively, and have the authority to bind the Hotel Preston and organization to this contract. If these arrangements meet with you approval, please sign and return this document to the attention of Kristin Myers - Sales Manager. The Hotel Preston, in turn, will countersign and return a copy to you. A definite acceptance will occur upon receipt of a signed contract by the Hotel Preston. A new contract will be executed should changes to the original be required. At this time, no rooms or function space are being held. Once a signed agreement has been executed on behalf of both parties, a definite room block commitment will be placed. CONTRACT EXPIRATION DATE; If this contract meets your approval, please sign and return to the Hotel Preston. This contract, which includes your discounted group rate, will expire on 01/10/2008. Should the Hotel Preston not receive this contract by the expiration date, upon request, a new contract will be issued. However, the new contract may not provide the same accommodations and rate as the original contract. Maximum Liability: The maximum liability under this agreement should not exceed $________ Audit: the contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against TBR under this agreement. The books,, records and documents of the contractor, insofar as they related to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. Prohibition on Hiring Legal Immigrants: TN public chapter no. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that contractor attest in writing that contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this contract, who will utilizes illegal immigrants in the performance of this contract. The attestation shall be made attachment E, attestation re personnel used in contract performance, (the attestation) which is attached and hereby incorporated as attachment A If contractor is discovered to have breached the attestation, the commissioner of finance and administration shall declare that the contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any TN Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one year by utilizing an appeals process in the rules of finance and administration, Chapter 0620. ♦ 733 Briley Parkway Nashville, Tennessee ♦ phone 615-361-5900 ♦ fax 615-367-4468 www.hotelpreston.com</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4C2EC67D-D145-4F4B-AC7B-C153C815A057">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">553</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">559</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode70CADA9C-2D29-4DD7-B27F-40996F763589"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode73177020-D595-4D9D-BE75-C55D2EF324C6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">553</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">554</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode70CADA9C-2D29-4DD7-B27F-40996F763589"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC08869A3-0DE6-4A54-9709-A2D46D1BAC9F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">554</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">559</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode70CADA9C-2D29-4DD7-B27F-40996F763589"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">99</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode854B7638-C598-460F-BBD6-69E979B540D3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">674</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">679</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEA68109F-E587-4D71-8AEF-56750040FDFC"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4ED4ECAC-91D1-485E-B0B9-309FEFA36C00">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">674</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">675</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEA68109F-E587-4D71-8AEF-56750040FDFC"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF5FAF976-E1E8-4B31-824E-669467DB2996">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">675</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">679</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeEA68109F-E587-4D71-8AEF-56750040FDFC"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4FD5DDD4-4456-44EB-93FE-059F7623CFA2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1896</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1897</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode78198E76-47CB-4471-9149-D056B29566C0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5CADE35F-C537-4D61-B251-076F056C0455">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1896</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1900</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode78198E76-47CB-4471-9149-D056B29566C0"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5C38B450-A359-4B36-899D-48E4C8377DC1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1897</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1900</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode78198E76-47CB-4471-9149-D056B29566C0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">250</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7AB099E8-8BF3-4E97-B278-072D0BB32EFB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1969</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1970</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF6DE7B25-97B2-43FE-B651-10689A07FBA1"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5159A01D-15A5-43C6-A894-129E39B1FE48">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1969</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1971</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF6DE7B25-97B2-43FE-B651-10689A07FBA1"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode526EF6A7-59C5-4B99-8634-68366B2D70A0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1970</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1971</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF6DE7B25-97B2-43FE-B651-10689A07FBA1"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">0</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEC9DF594-F40A-47D0-8C27-65AE388B68A5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4528</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4533</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode21BC0B52-938D-43B6-80C3-66B3B892AFE3"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode51E7BA9F-6B79-4DF7-B093-E70BFF72EB74">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4528</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4529</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode21BC0B52-938D-43B6-80C3-66B3B892AFE3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode34007918-1B1A-4926-A0C1-BE5406310461">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4529</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4533</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode21BC0B52-938D-43B6-80C3-66B3B892AFE3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC144BACC-04AC-465B-9D53-3D919B02313B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4616</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4621</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE48E33CD-A605-4B89-8E06-5622A4055F26"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeFDE32260-5AC7-43B3-8AB3-AD11CF95D8A7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4616</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4617</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE48E33CD-A605-4B89-8E06-5622A4055F26"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5E503671-54BB-46EC-96CA-9745FF89ABC0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4617</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4621</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE48E33CD-A605-4B89-8E06-5622A4055F26"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">0.3</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>