<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369900" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE166EEF4-CC32-4347-A460-9A0EECD8B38D">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">350000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeD01B28DF-904F-4E8C-928C-225BDD0A2317">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY and Vanderbilt University THIS AGREEMENT, made this 30th day of November 2007 , by and between Tennessee Technological University, hereinafter referred to as the "University,” and Vanderbilt University , hereinafter referred to as "Contractor.” WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A. The Contractor agrees to perform the following services as detailed in the Statement of Work (Attachment A) for: Award Name:     Advanced Portable Power Institute - Phase 2 (TTU# 5-32364) Award Number:   Contract W15P7T-07-C -P218 Federal Agency: US Army CECOM It is understood this is a subcontract under Tennessee Tech’s prime award which is incorporated by reference into this agreement. B. The University agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1.  A fee of $350,000 shall be paid the Contractor for services November 30, 2007-June 28, 2008. 2.  The rate reimbursable for individual salaries shall not exceed the individuals’ regular compensation rates. 3.  Payment will be made upon receipt of detailed monthly invoices and reports as noted in Item #C- 11 below. In addition, reimbursement for travel expenses must be accompanied with receipts of expenses incurred. See Item #C-15 for Tennessee Board of Regents (TBR) imposed limitations. All invoices should reference Contract #________________for award W15P7T-07-C-P218 and be submitted to: Center for Manufacturing Research TTU Box 5077 115 W. Tenth Street Cookeville, TN 38505 4.  Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, but only after receipt of invoices for services performed. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed his duties under this agreement. 5.  The final billing, clearly marked Final, shall be submitted no later than 45 days after the end of the period of performance. In no event shall the liability of the University under this contract exceed $350,000. C. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this agreement. 1.  The Contractor warrants that no part of the total Contract amount provided herein shall be paid directly or indirectly to any officer or employee of the State of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, subcontractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this agreement. 2.  The parties agree to comply with Title VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to employees or applicants for employment and/or students, because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during the employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employments. 3. Contractor agrees to complete a TBR Annual Title VI Survey or cooperate with a TBR Title VI compliance audit if it received Federal funds under this Agreement. 4. The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of the University, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, to pay all taxes incident hereunto, and otherwise protect and hold the University harmless from any and all liability not specifically provided for in this agreement. 5. The term of this contract shall be from November 30, 2007 - June 28, 2008. 6. This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least z 30 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. This Agreement may be cancelled effective June 30, 2008 if sufficient funding for its continuance is not appropriated by the General Assembly of the State of Tennessee. 7. If the Contractor fails to fulfill in timely and proper manner its obligations under this agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this agreement, the University shall have the right to immediately terminate this agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Not withstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the University for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this agreement by the Contractor. 8. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. Any modifications to contract terms and conditions, contract budget, and scope of work must be approved in writing by the University. 9. Within thirty (30) days following written request by University, Contractor shall make available for inspection and/or audit any and all records related to its performance under this Agreement, which shall include any exceptions noted on the audit. Said records are subject to inspection and audit by representatives of University and the Tennessee Comptroller of the Treasury or the Comptroller’s duly appointed representative during reasonable business hours throughout the term of this Agreement and for the three (3) years immediately following the University’s final payment to Contractor under this Agreement. In the event an audit is initiated by University during the three (3) years following the University’s final payment, Contractor agrees to retain any and all records associated with this Agreement until such time as any disputes arising therefrom are resolved. All audit disallowances under this Agreement shall be the responsibility of Contractor. Contractor acknowledges that it is aware of and agrees to comply with Office of Management and Budget Circular A-133, or A-128 as appropriate. Contractor agrees to provide University with audit information attesting to the fact that Contractor’s records covering the period of this Agreement have been audited in accordance with OMB Circulars A-133 or A-128, whichever is appropriate. Contractor further agrees to notify University in writing if at any time during the period of this Agreement it is no longer in compliance with Circular A-133, or A-128 as appropriate, or if there are audit findings that relate specifically to this Agreement. In cases of such non- compliance or audit findings, Contractor will promptly provide University with its written plan for corrective action. Audit reports and notifications should be sent to: Tennessee Technological University Office of Research and Graduate Studies Box 5037 Cookeville, TN 38505 ATTN: A-133 10. Consent to Subcontract. a. Consent is given for the following subcontract. University of Missouri - Columbia Office of Research 205 Jesse Hall Columbia, MO 65211 b. The Contractor shall not assign this agreement or enter into other subcontracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the University or Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 11. The Contractor shall submit to Dr. Ken Currie at Tennessee Technological University a monthly progress report that details the Contractor’s progress of the effort. This report shall discuss efforts completed, issues or anticipated problems and future plans. The report shall also note the expenditure of funds and obligation plans for the remaining funds, identify all component items and their status: designed, built, procured, and integrated. The report shall address but not be limited to the following: - Evaluate progress, both relative to schedule and relative to budget - Assess level of design definition and any design risks - Assess risk with supplier and manufacturing processes - Project major milestones or planned activities for subsequent month Any report which contains potentially patentable subject matter, shall have the following legend prominently displayed on its cover: “Notwithstanding any other legends marked hereon, this document contains information which may disclose a patentable invention in which the Government has a right, title or interest. Further distribution of this document to any non-govemmental agency is prohibited without the written approval of US Army C-ELCMS&lt; Fort Monmouth, NJ (see 35 USC 205).” In addition, the Contractor shall document design solutions, fabrication issues, breadboard testing, completed hardware, and test setups with color digital photographs. This digital imaging will be submitted with the final report. 12. This agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or his designee, or the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 13. Disclosure of Information: a. The Contractor shall not release to anyone outside the Contractor’s organization any unclassified information, regardless of medium (e.g., film, tape, document), pertaining to any part of this contract or any program related to this contract unless the Contractor has prior written approval or the information is otherwise in the public domain before the date of release. b. Requests for approval shall identify the specific information to be released, the medium to be used, and the purpose for the release. The Contractor shall submit this request to the University 45 days before the purposed date of release. c. The Contractor agrees to include a similar requirement in each subcontract under this contract. Requests for authorization to release by subcontractors should be submitted to the University through the Contractor. 14. The Contractor shall provide the University with a list of e-mail addresses for all administrative and technical personnel assigned to this contract. The Contractor is required to forward their email address, name, title, office symbol, contract number, telephone number and fax number to the University to the email addresses below: gjohnson@tntech.edu kcurrie@tntech.edu henry@tntech.edu 15. Compensation to the Contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be reimbursed to the appropriate person in the amount of actual cost, subject to the maximum amounts and limitations specified in the State Board of Regents policies, as they may be from time to time amended. In-State limitations can be accessed at tntech.edu while out-of-state limitations can be accessed on the federal CONUS website. http://www.gsa.gov/Portal/gsa/ep/contentView.do?contentld=17943&amp;contentType=GSA_BASIC 16. Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contractor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of the Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance ("the Attestation"), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, 0620. 17. Utilization of Small Business Concerns (May 2004) a. It is the policy of the United States that small business concerns, veteran-owned small business concerns, service-disabled veteran-owned small business concerns, HUBZone small business concerns, small disadvantaged business concerns, and women-owned small business concerns shall have the maximum practicable opportunity to participate in performing contracts let by any Federal agency, including contracts and subcontracts for subsystems, assemblies, components, and related services for major systems. It is further the policy of the United States that its prime contractors establish procedures to ensure the timely payment of amounts due pursuant to the terms of their subcontracts with small business concerns, veteran-owned small business concerns, service-disabled veteran- owned small business concerns, HUBZone small business concerns, small disadvantaged business concerns, and women-owned small business concerns. See Attachment B for definitions. b. The Contractor hereby agrees to carry out this policy in the awarding of subcontracts to the fullest extent consistent with efficient contract performance. The Contractor further agrees to cooperate in any studies or surveys as may be conducted by the United States Small Business Administration or the awarding agency of the United States as may be necessary to determine the extent of the Contractor's compliance with this clause. c. Contractors acting in good faith may rely on written representations by their subcontractors regarding their status as a small business concern, a veteran-owned small business concern, a service-disabled veteran-owned small business concern, a HUBZone small business concern, a small disadvantaged business concern, or a women-owned small business concern. 18. Allowable Costs: For the performance of the work hereunder, University agrees to pay Subcontractor the costs determined to be allowable under the cost principles applicable to the Subcontractor’s type of organization (i.e., OMB Circular A-21-Institutions of Higher Education; OMB Circular A-87-State, Local and Federally Recognized Indian Tribal Governments; OMB Circular A-122-Nonprofit Organizations; 45 CFR 74, Appendix E- Hospitals; or 48 CFR Subpart 31.2-For-Profit (commercial) Organizations). 19. General Provisions: This subcontract is awarded under the US Army CECOM Contract W15P7T-07-C-P218. Contractor agrees to abide by all applicable laws and regulations that pertain to this grant as cited in the prime award, Exhibit A. 20. Assurances: By signing this subcontract, Contractor certifies that: - It is not delinquent on the repayment of any Federal debt. - It is not presently debarred, suspended, proposed for debarment, declared ineligible, nor voluntarily excluded from covered transactions by and Federal department or agency. -Is is in compliance with the Drug-Free Workplace Act of 1988 (34 CRF Part 85, Subpart F). - It is in compliance with the Byrd Anti-Lobbying Amendment (31 U.S.C.1352) regarding restrictions on lobbying - It is in compliance with the Federal regulations governing the protection of human research subjects, 45 CRF Part 46, as amended. Subcontractor further agrees that activities involving human subjects will be reviewed by a designated Institutional Review Board (IRB) and to continue annual monitoring and compliance with requirements for the protection of human subjects. - It will comply with the Clean Air Act (42 U.S.C. 7401 et seq.) as amended, and the Water Pollution Control Act (33 U.S.C. 1251 et seq.), as amended, if the value of this subcontract is over $100,000. - Contractor certified that it maintains an appropriate written enforced policy on conflict of interest that complies with appropriate agency regulations concerning Conflict of Interest. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signature. Vanderbilt University                 EIN 62-0476822___________ Division of Sponsored Research 110 21s' Avenue South Baker Building, Suite 937 Nashville, TN 37203 Hohn T. Childress, Director                   Date q])ivision of Sponsored Research TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY Glen Johnson Principal Investigator, TTU Project 5-32364 /2-6-07 Date S. Deivanayagam Associate Deapf College of Engineering Sammie Sparks. ContracTcompFakce Assistant   Authorized Signatory for Dr. Precis Otuonye, / 'I- /A by:-----------------Assoc. VP for Research/Graduate Studies------ Francis Otuonye                             Date Associate Vice-President for Research and Graduate Studies Dr. Robert B resident TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4FF16B54-F6B0-4F55-B243-4FAE3A415789">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">949</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">957</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE166EEF4-CC32-4347-A460-9A0EECD8B38D"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeFFAB70B7-C821-46A1-8E78-0BFB2EA4B483">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">949</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">950</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE166EEF4-CC32-4347-A460-9A0EECD8B38D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEDDA08E6-6D2D-4885-A79E-DDE007291760">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">950</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">957</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE166EEF4-CC32-4347-A460-9A0EECD8B38D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">350000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>