<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369945" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode6AA165EE-A56E-47F2-8D5C-358C5DAF36FC">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">24657.34</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode41D11F7F-4827-483C-94D6-9E9D95C03F76">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Inilfr Gi.tllW |£|U.' MAY 2 F ?nnc; ’enriccsee uoara of Regents Tennessee Technology Centers AMENDMENT TO AGREEMENT BETWEEN - TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGY CENTER AT SHELBYVILL AND SOUTHERN CONNECTIONS CATERING, INC. Wartrace Tennessee 37813 7Z''                    -Z This renewal of agreement, made this ^7 day of nf/itf , 2009, by and between The Tennessee Technology Center at Shelbyville (TTCS) and Southern Connections Catering, Inc. (Contractor), for the purpose of extending the Agreement between the parties providing services of the purchase, preparation, serving and sale of food, food products, and non-alcoholic beverages, and textbooks for student and public purchase at the existing concession area of the Tennessee Technology Center at Shelbyville located at 1405 Madison Street, Shelbyville, Tennessee. WITNESSETH Section A. is modified to read as follows: This Contract shall be extended for 90 days effective for the period commencing on July 1, 2009 and ending on September 30, 2009. TTTCS shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. Pursuant, the maximum liability for this term shall not exceed $ 24,657.34. In addition, the following provision is hereby added to the Agreement: 4.       Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference as Attachment A. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. 5.      Voluntary Buyout Program. The Contractor acknowledges and understands that, for a period of two years beginning August 16, 2008, restrictions are imposed on former state employees who received a State of Tennessee Voluntary Buyout Program (VBP) severance payment with regard to contracts with state agencies that participated in the VBP. a.      The State will not contract with either a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or an entity in which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or the spouse of such an individual holds a controlling financial interest. b.      The State may contract with an entity with which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment is an employee or an independent contractor. Nothwithstanding the foregoing, the Contractor understands and agrees that there may be unique business circumstances under which a return to work by a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment as an employee or an independent contractor of a State contractor would not be appropriate, and in such cases the State may refuse Contractor personnel. Inasmuch, it shall be the responsibility of the State to review Contractor personnel to identify any such issues. c.       With reference to either subsection a. or b. above, a Contractor may submit a written request for a waiver of the VBP restrictions regarding a former state employee and a contract with a state agency that participated in the VBP. Any such request must be submitted to the State in the form of the VBP Contracting Restriction Waiver Request format available from the State and the Internet at: www.state.tn.us/fJnance/rds/ocr/waiver.html. The determination on such a request shall be at the sole discretion of the head of the state agency that is a Party' to this Contract, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration, and the Commissioner of Human Resources. All other terms and conditions of the original agreement are hereby ratified and affirmed. IM WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties, through their authorized representatives, have affixed their signatures. ATTACHMENT A ATTESTATION RE PERSONNEL USED IN CONTRACT PERFORMANCE ATTESTATION RE PERSONNEL USED IN CONTRACT PERFORMANCE CONTRACT NUMBER: iC'l l 7 7 CONTRACTOR LEGAL ENTITY NAME: JCxdh-efn (CeCoder FEDERAL EMPLOYER IDENTIFICATION NUMBER: (or Social Security Number) ms-maTosi/ The Contractor, identified above, does hereby attest, certify, warrant, and assure that the Contractor shall not knowingly utilize the services of an illegal immigrant in the performance of this Contract and shall not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor who will utilize the sendees of an illegal immigrant in the performance of this Contract. SIGNATURE &amp; ( \ DATE:     M NOTICE: 'TLismtfestatromM-UST be signed by an individual empowered to oontraokially)binalhe Contractor. If said individual is not the chief executive or presiaent, this docutoentshall attach evidence showing the individual’s ,authbQtyt^co'ntractuall y HncnffiTContractor.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode159ABCE3-9334-4851-BF57-79BE33AD59E7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1182</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1193</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6AA165EE-A56E-47F2-8D5C-358C5DAF36FC"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1B388CE3-E41A-475C-A22A-741A7DE6633F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1182</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1183</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6AA165EE-A56E-47F2-8D5C-358C5DAF36FC"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode2AF27FD2-93B2-4793-AEF6-0C609E9464B2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1184</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1193</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6AA165EE-A56E-47F2-8D5C-358C5DAF36FC"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">24657.34</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>