<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369955" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode34A1DBB1-8457-4F88-946D-4918911D61C3">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1700</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode6780B366-03D9-4B75-A185-91F35779CC42">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">MILLENNIUM MAXWELL MOLISE HOTEL NASHVll.U Catering Contract August 27, 2008 Ms. Deanna Stacey Tennessee Board of Regents 1415 Murfreesboro Road Nashville, TN 37217 Re: Tennessee Board of Regents Dear Ms. Stacey: We are pleased to confirm the tentative reservation for your Function scheduled for Tuesday, November 11, 2008 and offer you the following: B             Start T,ne End Time Function Setup Agr Room 1 5 ' ■' ' ’ 1 11/11/2008 6 30 PM 8 30 PM Dinner Rounds of 8 45  Expected Attendance: 45 People MINIMUM GUARANTEE: $1,700.00 Food &amp; Beverage Minimum before service charge and tax. Date of Function(s) Tuesday, November 11, 2008 MEALS/FOOD/OTHER SERVICES &amp; RATES: See menu for pricing LIQUOR &amp; RATES: See menu for pricing The Function Rates do not include applicable taxes, which are 9.25%, 22% service charge and 15% state alcohol tax as of the date of this agreement and are subject io change without notice. In addition to taxes, all other applicable governmental charges, service charge, assessment, and surcharges shall be applied to the Function Rates. We will reserve proper space for your Function until September 11, 2008, by which date a copy of this agreement, signed by you, and a form of payment must be returned to us. If we have not received this signed agreement accompanied by the guarantee by Thursday, September 11, 2008, we will release the Function Space and have no further obligations to you. When this agreement is signed and returned to us by September 11, 2008 along with the guarantee, it will be a binding contract between the Hotel and you for the Function Space and the food, drinks, other services, and your Event as set forth above. CREDIT ARRANGEMENTS / PAYMENT TERMS Unless proper credit has been established to our satisfaction under our credit policies, total payment is due 10 Working Days before the Function Date in the form of a cashiers check. We may require, at our discretion, that a deposit be made 30 days prior to the Function Date to establish proper credit and/or a credit card be on file to guarantee all charges. All additional charges incurred shall be paid directly and immediately to the Banquet Captain prior to the function. In entering this agreement, you acknowledge that we anticipate benefits from your Function that go beyond any food and beverage and meeting space charges contained in this agreement. Accordingly, if you cancel or terminate the Function for any reason other than a force majeure event (defined below), the actual amount of damages that we will incur will be difficult or impossible to ascertain. CANCELLA TION AND LIQUIDA TED DAMA GES Therefore, if you cancel the Function for any reason other than a force majeure event or you otherwise terminate or breach this agreement, you agree to pay us a cancellation fee equal to 100% of the anticipated food, beverage, room rental, and audio visual as liquidated damages and not as a penalty (the "Liquidated Damages") after acceptance of this agreement. The applicable amount of Liquidated Damages, plus any applicable taxes thereon, is due within 10 days after the date of your notice of cancellation. Any amounts of Liquidated Damages and applicable taxes that are not paid within 10 days of that date will bear interest at a rate equal to the lesser of (a) 18% per annum; or (b) the maximum rate allowed under applicable law from the due date until paid in full. All amounts paid in advance or deposited with us under this agreement shall be retained by us and applied first to the Liquidated Damages and then to any other costs or expenses incurred by us as a result of such cancellation, termination, or breach of this Agreement. The Function may be cancelled by either party without penalty or liability on written notice to the other party if an act of God, court or governmental action or regulation, disaster, strike, labor strife, civil disorder, criminal activity, casualty, regulation, or other event beyond our reasonable control makes it unreasonably dangerous, illegal, or impossible to provide our facilities for the Function or to hold the Function at the Hotel (a “force majeure event’’). Except for a force majeure event, this agreement shall not be cancelled or terminated by either party except for a breach of the agreement’s terms by the other party. If we breach this agreement by failing to provide the Function Space or Function Services contracted for any reason other than a force majeure event, you will be entitled to recover your actual damages that are the result of such breach, subject to mitigation as required by law and provided that your maximum recovery shall not exceed the amount you actually pay to us under this agreement. Further, in no event are we liable for any indirect, special, consequential, or incidental damages of any kind. Please be advised that neither your group nor any of its guests is permitted to use any meeting space or other part of the Hotel for any activity that is illegal or prohibited under any applicable law, rule, or regulation. You will be liable for any damage to the Hotel caused by any of your officers, agents, outside contractors, or guests. Further, you agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless us, our management company, and our respective employees from and against any losses, liabilities, claims, or damages that result from the negligence or intentional misconduct of your group or any of its officers, employees, outside contractors, guests, or agents related in any way to your group's activities at the Hotel except the extent any such loss, liability, claim, or damage is the result of the negligence or intentional misconduct of the Hotels employees or agents. Please note also that we will be liable for any loss or damage to samples, displays, property, or personal effects brought to the Hotel by you or any of your guests only to the extent so provided under local innkeepers laws. GOVERNING LA W; ATTORNEY’S FEES; SEVERABILITY We both acknowledge that this agreement contains the entire agreement between us. If any portion of this agreement is found to be unenforceable, the remaining provisions shall remain enforceable as if the provision found to be unenforceable were not included. If written notice to you is required under this agreement, the notice is to be sent to you at the address set forth above unless you advise us of another address in writing. If written notice to us is required under this agreement, the notice is to be sent to the Hotel’s address set forth above and a copy is to be sent to our General Counsel at 6560 Greenwood Plaza Boulevard, Suite 300, Greenwood Village, Colorado 80111. A notice under this agreement will be deemed given on the date of delivery if sent by nationally recognized overnight courier or three days after its deposit, properly addressed and postage prepaid with the United States Postal Service. Should any legal proceedings be required to enforce any provision of this agreement, the prevailing party, as determined by the finder of fact, will be entitled to recover all of its costs and expenses related thereto including without limitation expert witness', consultants', and attorneys' fees and court costs. This agreement is not assignable except it will be deemed assigned to any purchaser of the Hotel or of a controlling interest in it. If you would like to make arrangements for a block of sleeping rooms at a special rate, please contact our Sales Department at (615) 313-1378 regarding availability and rates. We realize that you had a bice of many fine hotels and we are honored that you have chosen our Hotel. Your signalurf'below indicatesfiMr acceptance of the terms of this agreement and you^j^epresentationThpt thfeach person wha signs on your behalf is fully authorized to do so. By: \ The terms of this agreement are hereby acknowledged and agreed to as of this Wednesday, August 27, 2008. Thd Millennium Maxw   2(^25 Rosa L. Parks/boule Nashville, TN 37228 rizqne, General Mana Name: Tennessee Board of Regents</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBF318054-A350-40F4-B0E1-CAA528F61416">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">525</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">534</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode34A1DBB1-8457-4F88-946D-4918911D61C3"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1084C5A2-9327-4034-954F-1AB25383D1CA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">525</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">526</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode34A1DBB1-8457-4F88-946D-4918911D61C3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode670FEF3E-DE92-4201-9ACE-2475DAAEFD4A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">526</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">534</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode34A1DBB1-8457-4F88-946D-4918911D61C3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1700</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>