<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369835" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8C8882B9-9226-49EA-A11B-DC7B10913545">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5500</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode5A35A2A3-3956-4B71-9CB3-BBA58088086B">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT BETWEEN THE ’’TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS (TBR)” AND THE BOARD OF CONTROL FOR SOUTHERN REGIONAL EDUCATION SCORE (Sharable Content Objects Repositories for Education) initiative This AGREEMENT is entered into between SREB state education agencies and the Board of Control for Southern Regional Education d/b/a Southern Regional Education Board, a non-profit compact created by its 16 member states, hereinafter referred to as “SREB.” WHEREAS, SREB is interested in sharing quality digital learning objects among participating SREB state education agencies; and, WHEREAS, participating SREB state education agencies want to provide and access quality digital content designed to support high-quality teaching; and, W'HEREAS, SREB has surveyed its members and has found considerable interest in participating in the Sharable Content Objects Repositories for Education initiative hereafter known as SCORE; and, W'HEREAS, SREB, working with states participating in the SCORE initiative will coordinate sharing of digital content through the creation of a regional registry; and WHEREAS,’’THE TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS (TBR)” has made the commitment to participate in the initiative and will abide by the terms of this Agreement. NOW, THEREFORE, the parties desire to enter into this Agreement under the following terms and conditions: 1.  SCORE is defined as a reciprocal partnership between the SREB and those member states whose education agencies choose to participate (hereafter known as “State Partners”) to create and maintain a regional registry of quality digital content made available by State Partners for use at no cost by other State Partners. 2.  SREB or any State Parmer or other entity is not authorized to change any element of this Agreement. All changes shall be accomphshed by an amendment signed by the authorized representative of each party. 3.  SREB will serve as fiscal agent and manage the budget for the SCORE initiative including the management of the registry, receive funds from participating state education agencies and grants, disburse funds to meet contractual obhgations, and coordinate the initiative. 4.  State Partners shaH provide necessary personnel, services, facihties and equipment and otherwise do all things necessary for their level of membership as detailed in the SCORE Business Plan attached to and made a part of this Agreement. 5.  The SREB in concert with State Partners will actively seek funding to implement and advance this SCORE initiative. In addition, State Partner will be required to provide support in the form of in-kind contributions, based on their level of membership, in order to accomplish the Business Plan. 6.  State Partners will provide access to content they own or content in the public domain through the SCORE registry to be shared among partners. This Agreement restricts use of the accessible content to participating State Partners and each State Partner shall have the right for itself, its affiliates and successors to a royalty-free, non-exclusive license to reproduce, distribute, exhibit and use the work or reuse it in other works except as otherwise prohibited by this Agreement. 7.  The SREB and State Partners are restricted from the commercial distribution of content or any aspect of content that has been received from other states through SCORE. 8.  Any State Partner that develops content independently is not restricted from selling the content that it has created and which resides in a SCORE affiliated repository. Copyrighted content and products, regardless of their form, developed during participation in the SCORE initiative shall be vested in the partner that created the content. A partner shall have the right for itself, its affiliates and successors to a royalty-free, non-exclusive license to reproduce, distribute, exhibit and use the work or reuse it in other works. Content co-developed by several State Partners will be jointly copyrighted in the name of the several partners and all permissions to reproduce, distribute, exhibit or use the product shall be granted jointly by the partners or their designated representatives. 9.  Neither SREB nor any State Partner shall assign this Agreement to a third party, whether by instrument or by operation of law, without the prior written consent of the other SCORE participants. 10. No State Parmer shall use the names of any other state or the name “SCORE” in connection with any products, promotion or advertising without the prior written permission of other SCORE participants. 11. Each State Partner retains the right to release information resulting from its own independent projects and studies related to SCORE but shall have no right to release or publish project results and data involving other partners without the approval of the affected partners. Every publication should identify that it has been produced through SCORE and, where appropriate, should contain a disclaimer indicating that the opinions, findings, conclusions or recommendations expressed therein are those of the individual state partners and do not necessarily reflect the views of all SCORE participants. Each State Partner shall furnish the other partners with a copy of any published materials, regardless of medium, within 30 days of their pubheation. 12. The SCORE initiative will establish procedures that will allow transfer of Sharable Content Objects from and to partner-repositories directly to reduce staff time and to ensure accuracy of content transferred. 13. Sharable Content Objects that reside in a SCORE affiliated repository will be maintained as submitted to the repository. Changes or modifications to the original Object will be placed in the repository with a version number. The revised object will be linked to the original Object and intellectual property rights of the original Object extend to all subsequent versions. 14. The SREB and State Charter and Associate Partners agree to participate in the development of an Annual Program Plan for the SCORE initiative. This plan will serve as the work statement for the forthcoming year and will serve as the basis for review and funding. The SCORE plan will describe accomplishments of the previous year, detail progress of each State Partner and set out proposed plans and budgets for the next year. Each partner shall identify equipment and service acquisition costs and may include proposed changes in membership, educational plans, services, timelines and application technologies. 15. State Partners agree that during the term of this Agreement, states shall use reasonable efforts to protect proprietary data furnished by any other states through SCORE which may be necessary for the conduct of the initiative. 16. State Partners agree that all knowledge or information not already considered within the public domain or within the control of the states will not be disclosed to any third party without the written consent of all SCORE participants. States agree to exercise reasonable efforts to protect information that is clearly marked “Confidential.” States shall hold confidential and not disclose information to others not already considered within the public domain in their reports or work products, together with any activities or documents produced as part of SCORE. 17. SREB and SCORE partner states shall not discriminate against any individual, including students, teachers, or applicants for employment because of race, color, religion, and sex or national origin. 18. This Contract shall be effective for the period commencing on August 1, 2006 and ending on July 31, 2008. TBR shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. 19. TBR reserves the right to extend this Contract for an additional period or periods of time representing increments of no more than one year and a total contract term of no more than five (5) years, by mutual written consent of both parties. An extension of the term of this Contract will be effected through an amendment to the Contract. If the extension of the Contract necessitates additional funding beyond that which was included in the original Contract, the increase in the TBR’s maximum liability will also be effected through an amendment to the Contract and shall be based upon rates provided lor in the original Contract. 20. In no event shall the maximum liability of TBR under this Contract exceed $5,500.00. 21. This Contract is subject to the appropriation and availability of State and/or federal funds. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, TBR reserves the right to terminate the Contract upon written notice to SREB. Termination under this Section 20 shall not be deemed a breach of Contract by TBR. Upon receipt of the written notice, the SREB shall cease all work associated with the Contract. Should such an event occur, the SREB shall be entitled to compensation for all satisfactory and authorized services completed as of the termination date. Upon such termination, the SREB shall have no right to recover from TBR any actual, general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. 22. SREB shall maintain documentation for all charges against TBR under this Contract. The books, records, and documents of SREB, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Contract, shall be maintained for a period of three (3) full years from the date of the final payment and shall be subject to audit at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice by TBR, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. The financial statements shall be prepared in accordance with generally accepted accounting principles. 23. TBR is a state agency subject to state public records requirements. This AGREEMENT will continue in force until either party terminates this AGREEMENT by giving at least thirty days written notice to the other party. At the time of discontinuance of participation, access to any content that the State Partner has created will be removed from SCORE at that state’s request. Such removal will be completed within 12 months of the request of removal, thus providing other partners with time to replace the removed content. State Partners will have the right to continue to use the content until the partner providing the content requests that content be removed from the repository. The official contact persons for each of the respective entities for this AGREEMENT ate as follows: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS Dr. Robbie Melton Associate Vice Chancellor of Affairs/ e-Leatning 1415 Murfreesboro Road Suite 350 Nashville, TN 37217 Southern Regional Education Board William R. Thomas Director, Educational Academic Technology Southern Regional Education 592 10th Street. NW Atlanta, GA 30318 This AGREEMENT shall take effect upon the execution by the patties. For SouthctzrRcgional Education Board By: David S. Spence, Presi &gt;- / 3 'I Date: For TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS By: Dr. Charles Manning, ChajnceHcf Dare:                            /</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3942CA45-A64B-40E2-B66E-A07C27192AF8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8465</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8474</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8C8882B9-9226-49EA-A11B-DC7B10913545"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB590BA82-D36E-4FE2-B346-F704B956E8A9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8465</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8466</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8C8882B9-9226-49EA-A11B-DC7B10913545"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCF1F5BD9-76B4-4F21-A2EA-0956CA8CF2F6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8466</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8474</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8C8882B9-9226-49EA-A11B-DC7B10913545"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5500</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>