<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3369889" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode3FFE036D-5CBE-4F98-9337-B0BEDD28695C">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">13</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode58635E9B-B2E2-4E78-B93C-BAEA530CD67A">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">10000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeDD49336C-AB90-451E-9295-E3261038C392">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">GAS PURCHASE CONTRACT GAS PURCHASE CONTRACT  Between THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS And ATMOS ENERGY MARKETING, LLC Table of Contents ARTICLE HEADINGS I Definitions II Measurement III Quality Specifications IV Transport and Delivery Point V Effective Date VI Price VII Billing, Accounting, and Reports VIII Term IX Quantities to be Sold and Purchased X Miscellaneous XI Force Majeure Xll State of Tennessee Requirements XIII Acknowledgements GAS PURCHASE CONTRACT This Contract made and entered into as of the 1st day of October, 2007, by and between The University of Memphis, hereinafter referred to as Buyer, and Atmos Energy Marketing, LLC. hereinafter referred to as Seller: WITNESSETH WHEREAS, Seller has supplies of gas available for sale; and WHEREAS, Buyer requires a supply of natural gas and intends to purchase from Seller all of its requirements of such gas as set forth below. NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration of the premises and of the mutual covenants and agreements herein contained, the parties hereto covenant and agree as follows: I. DEFINITIONS A.      The term “Gas” and “Natural Gas” as used herein, shall be construed to include both Gas Well and Oil Well Gas. B.      The term “month,” as used herein, shall mean a period of time beginning at 9:00 a.m. on the first day of each calendar month and extending to 9:00 a.m. on the first day of the immediately succeeding calendar month. C.      The term “transporting pipelines” as used herein, shall mean Texas Gas Transmission or Trunkline Gas Company. D.      The term “Anniversary Date” shall mean the date first written above and the end of each twelvemonth period thereafter. E.      The term “Btu” shall mean British Thermal Units measured at 14.73 psia, sixty degrees Fahrenheit (60 degrees F), and water vapor measured under dry conditions. F.      The term “MMBtu” shall mean one million Btu’s. 11 MEASUREMENT All gas delivered by Seller to Buyer hereunder shall be measured as specified by the transporting pipeline. Ill QUALITY SPECIFICATIONS The gas received by Buyer or its designee under this Contract at each delivery point shall be merchantable natural gas of the quality specified by the transporting pipeline. IV TRANSPORT AND DELIVERY POINT Seller agrees to deliver Buyer’s daily nominated quantity for the account of Buyer to the transporting pipeline(s) for subsequent transport to the city gate connection of Memphis Light, Gas &amp; Water Division (MLG &amp;W) [the delivery point], and title to the gas shall transfer to Buyer when such gas has been accepted by MLG&amp;W at the delivery point. Seller shall be responsible for making all arrangements with transporting pipeline(s) for transportation of the gas sold hereunder to the city gate of MLG&amp;W, and Buyer shall be responsible for contracting with MLG&amp;W for transport service to the campus meter. V EFFECTIVE DATE This Contract shall become effective as of the date first hereinabove written. VI PRICE 1.               Commencing with initial deliveries and continuing until the first Anniversary Date of the Contract, the price payable shall be as follows: Buyer may on any NYMEX trading day lock in the price (Fixed Price) for a specified quantity to be delivered during a specified future month(s). Such Fixed Price shall be quoted by Seller at the time of Buyer’s decision to lock in and shall equal the then current NYMEX trading price for the applicable month(s), plus $.13 + applicable Texas Gas Transmission Zone SL-1 FT Fuel/mmbtu (Fixed Price Adder). Seller and Buyer shall execute a confirmation of the price payable within two (2) business days thereafter. For quantities delivered each month which are in excess of quantities subject to a Fixed Price pursuant to the preceding paragraph, the price (Index Price) shall be the NYMEX settle price on the last trade date for the month of delivery, plus $.13 + applicable Texas Gas Transmission Zone SL-I FT Fuel /mmbtu (Index Price Adder). In no event shall the liability of The University of Memphis under this contract exceed $10,000,000.00. The above prices are inclusive of all charges upstream of the delivery point (MLG&amp;W city gate) and include the commodity cost, basis differentials, taxes or fees paid by Seller, Seller’s margin, and pipeline charges, (excluding fuel). 2.               Within the thirty (30) day period immediately preceding the first Anniversary Date and each subsequent Anniversary Date, Buyer and Seller shall renegotiate the Fixed Price Adder and Index Price adder for the next twelve (12) month period. In the event Buyer and Seller cannot agree upon the Adders to be in effect the following year, either party may suspend its obligation under this contract until such time that agreement has been reached. During such period of suspension, Buyer may purchase its gas requirements from other suppliers. 3.                If the University’s nomination for any given day during a month exceeds the initial first of month nomination by more the 15% and the cash market price for gas at the time of the increase exceeds the Index Price for the month, the incremental volume over 15” that is subject to index pricing shall be subject to price renegotiations. If the parties cannot agree on a price for the incremental volume, Seller shall not be obligated to deliver it and Buyer may satisfy its requirements by other means. Example: Suppose the Buyer has placed 2500mmbtu under Fixed Price for the month of January and the January 1st nomination is 1000 mmbtu (806 mmbtu/d subject to Fixed Price. 194 mmbtu/d subject to Index Price). If the January 10th nomination is increased to 1500 mmbtu, the following would apply: 806 mmbtu @ Fixed Price 344 mmbtu @ first of month Index Price 350 mmbtu subject to price adjustment 4.               If during any month in which a NYMEX based Fixed Price is applicable to a specified quantity and Buyer’s failure to nominate or purchase all such specified quantity causes Seller to Incur a loss in disposition of the untaken quantity, Buyer agrees to compensate Seller for such actual, documented loss. VII BILLING, ACCOUNTING, AND REPORTS SELLER SHALL RENDER TO Buyer, on or before the fifteenth (IS'1') day of each month, a gas purchase statement setting forth the volume of gas received by Buyer at the Delivery Point provided for under this Contract which was delivered during the preceding month by Seller. After Buyer receives such gas purchase statement, buyer agrees to make payments to Seller in accordance with provisions of the "Prompt Pay Act of 1985” of the State of Tennessee, to the Seller’s bank at the address shown below. SELLER’S BANK:     Bank: Bank of America Address: Dallas, TX ABA #026-009-593 Acct #375-156-1125 Officer: Atmos Energy Marketing, LLC. In the event Buyer fails to pay the amount due Seller within 45 days after receipt of invoice, interest shall accrue and be charged on payments overdue under TCA Section 12-4-703 at one and one-half percent (1-1/2%) per month beginning on the day after payment is due. Buyer shall not be obligated to pay any severance taxes, overriding royalties or any payments out of production due on such gas. If an error is discovered in the amount paid by Buyer, said error shall be adjusted within thirty (30) days after the correct amount is determined. Claim for errors shall be made promptly upon discovery. Vlll TERM Subject to all the terms and conditions hereof, this Contract shall remain in full force and effect for a primary term ending at 9:00 a.m. one (1) year from the effective date hereof. Thereafter, this Contract shall remain in effect for the additional periods of one (1) year each, up to a total of five (5) years subject to successful negotiation. Either party may terminate this Contract at the end of the primary term or at the end of any subsequent one (1) year period by giving at least thirty (30) days written notice to the other party. IX QUANTITIES TO BE SOLD AND PURCHASED Subject to the other provisions of this agreement, Buyer shall purchase and Seller shall sell and deliver 100% of Buyer’s daily-nominated quantity at the Point(s) of delivery set forth in this Contract up to 1500 mmbtu per day. Each day during the term of this agreement, buyer will notify seller of the quantity it desires to purchase for the succeeding day. Such nomination shall be rendered in sufficient time to permit dispatches of both parties to make necessary arrangements to effectuate deliveries. Should Seller deliver a daily volume of gas hereunder in excess of nominated request. Buyer shall not be required to purchase and receive said excess gas unless Buyer requested said additional volumes of Seller’s gas prior to delivery by Seller. In the event Seller fails to deliver all of Buyer’s nominated quantity on any day when not excused by force majeure or by prior consent of Buyer, Seller shall reimburse Buyer for any imbalance charges and/or penalties, or any incremented cost incurred in using alternate fuels, which may result from such failure to deliver. Pipeline curtailment shall not constitute a force majeure event unless the pipeline itself has declared a force majeure. X MISCELLANEOUS Filings with Regulatory Authorities A.       It is recognized that it may be necessary for Seller or Buyer to make certain filings with Federal or State regulatory authorities with respect to the sale and purchase of gas hereunder. Each party hereto agrees to file promptly with the applicable regulatory authority and to prosecute diligently all applications, notices or reports required with respect to the sale of gas hereunder. Headings and Subheadings B.      The headings and subheadings contained in this contract are used solely for convenience and do not constitute a part of the agreement between the parties hereto nor should they be used in any manner in construing this Contract. Jurisdiction C.      This Contract shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee and all disputes and controversies, or arising from, this Contract shall be resolved within the boundaries of the State of Tennessee. Governmental Regulations D.      This Contract is subject to all present and future valid laws, orders, rules and regulations of any regulatory body of the Federal Government or the State in which these premises are situated, having jurisdiction. Responsibility for Gas E.       As between the parties hereto, the party in possession of the gas shall be in exclusive control thereof and shall be responsible for any injury or damage caused thereby while the gas is in its possession. Warranty F.       Seller hereby warrants the title to all gas delivered hereunder, the right to sell the same, and that it is free from all liens and adverse claims, and agrees to indemnify Buyer against all suits, actions, debts, accounts, damages, costs (including reasonable attorneys’ fees), losses and expenses arising from or out of any adverse claims of any and all persons to or against said gas. Contract Binding on Successors, Heirs, and Assigns G.      All terms and conditions of this Contract shall extend to and be binding upon the respective successors, heirs, and assigns of the parties hereto. Any party hereto may assign their right, title and interest in, to and under this agreement, including, without limitation, any and all renewals, extension amendments and/or supplements hereto, provided, however, that no such assignment shall in any way operate to enlarge, alter, or change any obligation of the other party or parties hereto. No assignment shall be effective or binding until a certified copy or duplicate original of same has been furnished to and has been approved by the other party. Third Party Beneficiary H.      There is no third party beneficiary to this contract, and the provisions of this Contract shall not impart rights enforceable by any person, firm or organization not a party or not a successor or assignee of a party to this Contract. Joint Preparation I.       This Contract was prepared jointly by the parties hereunder and not by either party to the exclusion of the other. Addresses of Parties J.       Any Notice, request, demand, statement, or payment under this Contract, except as otherwise herein provided for, may be given in writing, delivered in person or by United States Postal Services Mail, to the parties hereto at the addresses set out below or at such other addresses as may hereafter be furnished to the other party in writing: SELLER: Company:     ATMOS ENERGY MARKETING, LLC. Address:         313 Frederica St         2179 Glenalden Drive Suite 300               Memphis, TN 38139 Owensboro, KY 42301 Phone:          (270) 685-8155          (901) 755-8185 Attention:       Stan McDivitt            Ira Stanfill (nominations &amp; operations) BUYER: THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS PROCUREMENT SERVICES 115 ADMINISTRATION BUILDING MEMPHIS, TENNESSEE 38152-3370 Phone:         901-678-2265 Attention:      JAMES L. NABORS, C. P. M„ ASSOCIATE DIRECTOR PROCUREMENT SERVICES Maintenance K. Maintenance whether scheduled or unscheduled, affecting operations of either Seller of Buyer shall be deemed to reduce the obligation of the party affected to supply or purchase hereunder to the extent that such maintenance in fact reduced Seller’s ability to deliver or Buyer's ability to accept such gas; provided, however, that with respect to scheduled maintenance, Buyer or Seller, as appropriate, shall give not less that three days prior written notice to the other. A temporary shutdown or reduction of the operation or operations of the facilities at the plants for purposes of temporarily suspending or reducing production of any commodity for economic reasons, including (but not limited to) lack of sales, inventory control, or an election to purchase rather than make such commodity shall reduce the obligation of the Buyer to purchase hereunder; provided, however, that Buyer shall give not less than fifteen (15) days written notice prior to each shutdown or reduction of operation; and provided further that Buyer’s obligation to purchase hereunder may be reduced for not more than sixty (60) consecutive days. IX FORCE MAJEURE In the event of either party’s being rendered unable, wholly or in part, by force majeure to carry out its obligations under this Contract, it is agreed that on such party’s giving notice and reasonable full particulars of such force majeure to the other party in writing or by telegraph within a reasonable time after the occurrence of the cause relied on, then the obligations of the party giving such notice (including, but not limited to. the obligation to make payments for gas not taken because of force majeure), so far as they are affected by such force majeure, shall be suspended during the continuance of any inability so caused, but for no longer period, and such cause shall so far as possible be remedied with all reasonable dispatch. Buyer shall have no obligation to pay for gas not taken to the extent the failure to take is caused by force majeure. The term “force majeure,’’ as employed herein, shall mean acts of God, strikes, lockouts or other industrial disturbances, acts of the public enemy, wars, blockades, insurrections, riots, epidemics, landslides, lighting, earthquakes, fires, storms, floods, high water, washouts, arrests and restraints of government and people, civil disturbances, explosions, breakage or accident to machinery or lines of pipe, the necessity for making repairs or alterations to machinery or lines of pipe, freezing of wells or lines of pipe, partial or entire failure of any wells, the refusal of transporting pipeline to carry purchased volumes, temporary or permanent closure of plants, and any other causes, whether of the kind herein enumerated or otherwise, not reasonably within the control of the party claiming suspension; such term shall likewise include (a), in those instances where any party hereto is required to obtain servitudes, rights of way grants, permits or licenses to enable such party to fulfill its obligations hereunder, the inability of such party to acquire, or the delays on the part of such party in acquiring, at reasonable cost and after the exercise of reasonable diligence, such servitudes, right of way grants, permits or licenses, and (b). in those instances where any party hereto is required to furnish materials and supplies for the purpose of constructing or maintaining facilities or is required to secure permits or permission from any governmental agency to enable such party to fulfill its obligations hereunder, the inability of such party to acquire, or the delays on the part of such party in acquiring, at reasonable cost and after the exercise of reasonable diligence, such materials and supplies, permits and permission. It is understood and agreed that the settlement of strikes or lockouts shall be entirely within the discretion of the party having the difficulty and that the above requirement that any force majeure shall be remedied with all reasonable dispatch shall not require the settlement of strikes or lockouts by acceding to the demands of an opposing party when such course is inadvisable in the discretion of the party having the difficulty. XII STATE OF TENNESSEE REQUIREMENTS 1.       The Contractor warrants that no fee has been nor shall be paid directly or indirectly to any officer or employee of the University or the state of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, subcontractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with this Agreement. 2.       The parties agree to comply with Title VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Title IX of the Education amendments of 1972, section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973. Executive Order 11246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990. and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual, including but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during the employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited by the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 3.       The contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of the University, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, to pay all taxes incident hereto, and otherwise protect and hold harmless the University from any and all liability not specifically provided for in this agreement. 4.       Any and all claims against the State of Tennessee, including University or its employees, for personal injury and/or property damage resulting from the negligence of the University in performing any responsibility specifically required under the terms of this Agreement shall be heard and determined by the Board of Claims or the Claims commission of the State of Tennessee. Damages recoverable against University shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Board of Claims or Claims Commission pursuant to T. C. A. Section 9-8-301 et. seq. 5.       The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all payments and charges under this Agreement. The books, records and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period to three (3) full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice, by the University or the Comptroller of the Treasury or their duly appointed representatives. XIII ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties hereto have caused this agreement to be executed in duplicate originals as of the date first hereinafter written. ATMOSENERGY MARKETING. LLC. ”  WITNESS: THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS . J APPROVED BY: (if required) </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5469D61B-B2B6-459A-BC94-AC66989E9E33">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3411</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3412</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3FFE036D-5CBE-4F98-9337-B0BEDD28695C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3857466B-B86B-457C-96A9-F29AC918F001">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3411</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3415</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3FFE036D-5CBE-4F98-9337-B0BEDD28695C"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5F1D8809-03F8-437B-8E1E-B01656A70F5D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3413</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3415</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3FFE036D-5CBE-4F98-9337-B0BEDD28695C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">13</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6D8D6922-827A-4004-8855-B366B41F03DE">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4023</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4037</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode58635E9B-B2E2-4E78-B93C-BAEA530CD67A"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1AA5C870-E17F-41AA-9193-D9026EBEA3F1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4023</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4024</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode58635E9B-B2E2-4E78-B93C-BAEA530CD67A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9B8C0E93-A70E-45B7-BA2B-481F4CE0157F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4024</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4037</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode58635E9B-B2E2-4E78-B93C-BAEA530CD67A"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">10000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>