<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370022" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeC9E6FB27-377D-4A63-B2CE-1A56E5370578">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">20</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeD5C0549C-E77B-48F9-BD0C-57FBB597D992">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT CHATTANOOGA STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY As a part of the continued effort to provide greater access to education, Chattanooga State Community College (ChSCC) and Tennessee Technological University (TTU) agree to cooperatively provide educational programs for the ChSCC service area. Under the auspices of this agreement, institutions will provide the opportunity for students to earn credits toward the Associate, Baccalaureate, Master’s and Educational Specialist degrees while taking classes at CSCC. This agreement specifies the nature of the services each institution will provide as a part of the instructional programs offered. The term of this agreement shall be from July 1, 2009, through June 30,2013. The following conditions are agreed upon by each institution: 1.  ChSCC will offer all 1000 and 2000 level credit courses. 2. TTU will coordinate and offer upper division and graduate credit courses for TTU degrees. 3. Each institution will provide appropriate library holdings and services for their students. All holdings and services will be available to any student enrolled. 4.  Each institution will collect maintenance fees for their respective courses. 5. Each institution will receive the FTE generated for their respective courses. 6. TTU will reimburse ChSCC for the following: a. Access fee of $20 per 2+2 student per semester to enable TTU 2+2 students to have access to ChSCC campus privileges. b.  TTU will purchase and maintain computers for faculty and staff, and purchase technology equipment for specialized courses such as the 21st Century Classroom course, and develop web-based materials. ChSCC will provide general-purpose computer labs for student use, connectivity to ChSCC data lines and computer network, and maintain and service computers for faculty, staff, and students. ChSCC will not maintain the Macintosh iBook computers. c.  Facilities rental for all TTU courses, including classroom and office space, at the rate of $5,000.00 per year, payable in two installments of $2,500.00, due in July and January. d.  Costs incurred for long distance phone calls, printing, postage, catering, etc. Refer to section 8.f. 7. TTU will also be responsible for the following expenses as they may occur: a.  Telephone line/s to the ChSCC campus, if there is any cost. b.  Data line/s to the ChSCC campus, if there is any cost. c. Audio-visual and presentation equipment. d.  Computers, printers, and data communication devices for faculty and staff. e.  Furnishings for TTU 2+2 classroom and office space. f.  The cost of any course specific rentals, labs, supplies, and equipment (e.g., 21st Century Classroom hardware, software, and related equipment and materials). g.  Salary, travel, and benefit costs for assigned faculty and staff. h. If any TTU student has a disability when completing the 2+2 program while attending classes at ChSCC, TTU Disability Services will be responsible for the cost of any accommodations. TTU and ChSCC Disability Services will work together for each student. i.  TTU is responsible for submitting all book orders to ChSCC Bookstore for classes per semester. TTU students will be responsible for paying for their books for TTU courses.  j.  TTU 2+2 faculty and staff are responsible for signing for ChSCC keys. TTU 2+2 faculty or staff will submit an authorization building key form to the Vice President for Academic Affairs for approval. TTU 2+2 faculty and staff will return ChSCC keys to the Physical Plant upon separation from the program at ChSCC. TTU will notify the ChSCC Liaison when any TTU 2+2 faculty or/and staff leaves the program. k. TTU 2+2 faculty, staff and students will follow the requirements for receiving a CSCC decal. TTU will give to the ChSCC Bursar’s Office and ChSCC Liaison a list of TTU 2+2 students. TTU will ensure that all TTU 2+2 students obtain ChSCC parking decals. TTU students who receive ChSCC parking violation tickets will be subject to the same restrictions as TTU campus students. l.  TTU will be responsible for purchasing and maintaining the operations of specialized equipment for the 2+2 program such as the Edison Die Cut, the Laminator Machine, and other tools. m. TTU will provide information to ChSCC about liability, workmen’s compensation, and emergency medical situation pertaining to students in the 2+2 Program. n. TTU staff will sign for all deliveries for the 2+2 Program. o. TTU faculty and staff will work very closely with the ChSCC Liaison for the 2+2 Program. 8. ChSCC will be responsible for the following: a. Providing adequate office space for two TTU 2+2 faculty members and one support staff member.  b.  Classroom space for all TTU classes. Due to the limited availability of classrooms, ChSCC will provide adequate classroom space to accommodate up to ninety 2+2 students (two cohort groups of 45) each semester. TTU will maintain occupancy of the current 2+2 classroom and two offices (OMNI 10). Based upon availability, ChSCC will provide TTU with additional use of shared classroom space necessary to meet their instructional needs. Prior to the beginning of each semester, TTU will provide to ChSCC a schedule of TTU class meetings. c. General purpose computer labs for TTU student use, the same as provided for ChSCC student use. d. Connectivity to ChSCC data lines, telephone lines, and computer network e.  Maintenance and service of computers for faculty, staff, and students, with the exception of specialized equipment such as the Macintosh iBook computers for the 21st Century Classroom. f.  Creation of an agency account code recognized as TTU 2 + 2 for faculty and staff. Faculty and staff will use the code for printing services, postages, long distance telephone calls, catering, etc. ChSCC will invoice TTU for all costs. g. TTU 2+2 students will be eligible to have child care if needed for children up to PreK. TTU students will be considered as a Priority III level and will follow all the same liability rules and regulations as ChSCC students. 9. This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by both parties. 10. The annual liability of TTU under the terms and conditions of section 6 of this agreement is estimated in Attachment A and shall not exceed $20,000 annually. 11. Either party may terminate this agreement by giving written notice to the other at least 30 days before the effective date of termination. 12. The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, and Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, American Disabilities Act of 1990, Executive Order 11,246 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, veteran status or national origin. Such action shall include, but not limit to the following: Employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 13. TTU's Vice President of Extended Programs and Regional Development will be consulted prior to any obligations, which would significantly impact the cost incurred by TTU. IN WITNESS HEREOF, the parties cause this agreement to be executed. Tennessee Technological University Date Provost and Vice Pres, for Academic Affairs Tennessee Technological University Z- 7^7 __________•?- I -O r! Date</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCD14CACA-CA09-495A-B1A4-145CFB77D2BB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1376</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1379</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC9E6FB27-377D-4A63-B2CE-1A56E5370578"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode88228E1A-E5D8-493C-949F-95835752A585">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1376</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1377</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC9E6FB27-377D-4A63-B2CE-1A56E5370578"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4DC157C8-94CF-440E-9CF6-BE763F64D406">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1377</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1379</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC9E6FB27-377D-4A63-B2CE-1A56E5370578"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">20</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>