<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370369" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode0DA1EE04-895E-4052-BD80-CC98033278E8">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">BYR</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">4300000000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode3AA8B34C-2AB4-4E3A-A667-EF1BD02E8621">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Indicators of SME development On the 1st of April 2008, the number of small enterprises in Belarus amounted to 51,000. Compared with the same period in 2007, their number increased by 36%. 20.5 thousand small enterprises (40% of the total) functioned in the sphere of trade and catering industry, 10.7 thousand (21% of the total) - in industry, 5.3 thousand (10% of the total) - in construction. In January-March 2008, there were 440.3 thousand employees working in small enterprises (10% of the total work force), including in industry - 171.8 thousand, in trade and catering - 110.8 thousand, in construction -67.3 thousand people. During the first three months of 2008, small enterprises produced goods and provided services worth BYR 4.3 trillion, which is a 22.6% increase when compared with January-March 2007.The actual number of medium enterprises is not included in Belarusian statistics. However, one could hardly foresee any significant increase of their number in the near future. Despite the efforts of the authorities directed at improving the business climate, the changes that already have been made are still not sufficient for mass appearance of new private enterprises. The Ministry of Statistics itself explains the increase in the number of small enterprises by their campaign on shifting individual entrepreneurs in private unitary enterprises. At the same time, because a considerable amount of legal and administrative barriers for doing business persists, the majority of individual entrepreneurs resist to shift to the form of an private unitary enterprise and continue to function either under a status as an Individual Entrepreneur (and having also registered their employees as such), or in the shadow economy</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode463C2A38-292C-4520-8459-782C4DCEE429">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">734</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">750</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode0DA1EE04-895E-4052-BD80-CC98033278E8"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8EA03713-700D-4EE6-A01A-5D593C014ED1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">734</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">737</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode0DA1EE04-895E-4052-BD80-CC98033278E8"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">BYR</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF208A806-55E3-4259-B7E4-F6FAC204BBD4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">738</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">750</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode0DA1EE04-895E-4052-BD80-CC98033278E8"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">4300000000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>