<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370093" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode71D2F672-F928-4994-8AC4-B57877E67A6C">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">16</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode327966F1-16CD-4EC0-B3F5-AAD7A788FB72">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Electronically Recorded Official Public Records Tarrant CountyTexas 11/5/20101:39 PM D210275924 PGS 1      $16.00 Amendment To Oil And Gas Lease- ~ (To extend Primary Term, Paid-Up Lease) State:    Texas County: Tarrant Lessor: Betty Hamilton, 3501 Canyon Ridge Ave., Fort Worth, TX 76103-3009 Lessee: XTO Energy, Inc., 810 Houston Street, Fort Worth, Texas 76102 Effective Date: November 8,2007 Lessee, named above, is the present owner of the oil and gas lease (the “lease”), dated November 8, 2007, executed by Lessor, Named above, in favor of Hollis R. Sullivan, Inc., Lessee, estimated to contain 0.3834 acres of land (the “Land”), whether actually, more or less, in the county and state named above. The Lease is recorded in Document #D208008258 of the Official Public Records of that county, Reference is made to the Lease and its recording for a complete description of the Lands it covers and for all other purposes. It is the desire of Lessor to extend the primary term provided for in the Lease. For adequate consideration, Lessor agrees that the Lease is amended so that the primary term of three (3) years provided in the Lease shall be changed to four (4) years from the original date of the Lease having the effect of extending the primary term of the Lease for an additional one (1). Lessor leases and lets to Lessee, its successors and assigns, the Lands for the purposes and on the terms and conditions provided in the Lease, as amended and extended by this Amendment. Lessor warrants to be the owner of the Lands and the minerals in and under the Lands with full right and authority to execute this Amendment to extend the primary term of the Lease. This Amendment shall extend to and be binding on Lessor, and Lessor’s respective heirs, executors, administrators, successors, and assigns. Except as stated in this Amendment, the Lease shall continue in full force and effect as to all of its other terms and provisions. The consideration paid to Lessor for this Amendment is the full consideration for the extension of the primary term of this Lease. The Lease is deemed a “Paid Up” Lease for its entire extended primary term. This Amendment is signed by Lessor as of the date of Acknowledgment of their respective signature below, but is effective for all purposes as of the Effective Date stated above. Lessor(s): Betty W. Hamilton Acknowledgement State of Texas County of Tarrant This instrument was acknowledged before me on the Betty W. Hamilton.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode87278FCE-3512-461D-9F95-12CB82407FCA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">107</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">113</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode71D2F672-F928-4994-8AC4-B57877E67A6C"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7455940D-DF4E-4622-A566-9DB0EEF3C0D4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">107</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">108</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode71D2F672-F928-4994-8AC4-B57877E67A6C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode418F4B3B-B130-4B81-8B2D-6720DC3F7BD1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">108</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">113</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode71D2F672-F928-4994-8AC4-B57877E67A6C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">16</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>