<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370042" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4B2A2A65-361C-4BB5-B356-597B713ED3AB">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">45000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode911C6FFA-1F70-476E-BAB7-99FA76FAAA41">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">8000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode2DB17B3B-838A-418C-9B95-00F762B8B583">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">27000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode62331565-3246-4550-878F-5D45DB4C64FB">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN Tennessee Board of Regents Tennessee Technology Centers AND Tennessee Technological University This Agreement is made this first day of February, 2010, by and between the Tennessee Board of Regents/Tennessee Technology Centers, hereinafter referred to as the "TBR/TTC", and Tennessee Technological University, hereinafter referred to as "Contractor". WITNESSETH: In consideration of the mutual promises herein contained, the parties have agreed and do hereby enter into this Agreement according to the provisions set out herein: A.    The Contractor agrees to perform the following services: 1.   Development of the Tennessee Technology Centers website for state-wide use with emphasis on nontraditional student information and career guidance. 2.   Develop and print an integrated marketing campaign which includes developing brochures to market and provide career guidance information for the TTC RODP programs to the state’s stakeholders, including potential students, other state-funded entities, and business and industry. 3.   Provide additional video production and editing services to include program/career videos on the TTC websites for student career guidance. B.    The following tasks will be performed by the Contractor: 1. The Contractor will develop a common website for the Tennessee Technology Center Central Office and all TTC campuses and an integrated marketing campaign to increase traffic directed toward the website is to include, but not restricted to: a. print campaign material, b.   electronic media, c.   the utilization of direct mail, and d.   tradeshow material.($27,000) e.   Delivery dates: the first four (4) websites will be available February 10th, 2010; an additional ten (10) websites will be available February 25th, 2010; the remaining thirteen (13) websites will be completed March 11, 2010. 2.   Develop and print a targeted integrated marketing campaign directed toward the Tennessee Career Center RODP program. ($8000) Delivery date shall be on or before February 14th, 2010. 3.   Collect and prepare additional video vignettes for the TTC websites to emphasize how individual programs serve all aspects of business and industry within their service area and to provide career guidance for prospective students. In addition, these videos will showcase non-traditional programs and career fields. ($10,000) Delivery date shall be on or before March 31st, 2010. C. The TBR/TTC agrees to compensate the Contractor as follows: 1.   Compensation to the Contractor will be based upon successful completion, as agreed upon by the two parties, of each task within the scope of work. 2.   Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, provided that payments shall be made only upon submittal of invoices by the Contractor, and after performance of the portion of the services which the invoiced amount represents. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this Agreement. 4. In no event shall the liability of the TBR/TTC under this contract exceed $ 45,000 . Funds are dependent upon federal funding. D. The parties further agree that the following shall be essential terms and conditions of this Agreement. 1.   The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitmentor recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 2.   Contractor agrees to complete a TBR Annual Title VI Survey or cooperate with a TBR Title VI compliance audit if it received Federal funds under this Agreement. 3.   The term of this contract shall be from February to September 30, 2010. 4.   This Agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 45 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Contractor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. 5.   If the Contractor fails to fulfill in a timely and proper manner its obligations under this Agreement, or if the Contractor shall violate any of the terms of this Agreement, the TBR/TTC shall have the right to immediately terminate this Agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the TBR/TTC for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Agreement by the Contractor. 6.   This Agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. 7.   The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the TBR/TTC under this Agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the TBR or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. 8.   The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into sub-contracts for any of the work described herein without obtaining the prior written approval of the Tennessee Board of Regents. Approval shall not be given if the proposed subcontractor was or is currently ineligible to bid on the contract. 9.   The Contractor shall submit to the TBR/TTC monthly progress reports beginning March 1,2010 and the first of every month throughout the duration of this agreement. 10.  This Agreement shall not be binding upon the parties until it is approved by the president or designee, and the Chancellor or designee for the Tennessee Board of Regents, as appropriate. 11.  Payment to the Contractor for travel, meals or lodging shall be in the amount of actual cost or per diem, subject to maximum amounts and limitations specified in the Tennessee Board of Regents policies, as they may be from time to time amended. 12.  Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, reguires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference as Attachment A. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. In witness whereof, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set their signatures. Tennessee Technological University Tennessee Board of Regents ~LE:          - DATE: 2 DATE: titi c. Francis Otuonye, Ph.D. 111 L /Xssoc. VP for Research/Graduate Studies 5-5~-/O Date</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode922A7446-B64E-4837-9C7B-80974695493A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1613</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1620</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2DB17B3B-838A-418C-9B95-00F762B8B583"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode242ACD2B-D709-4CEE-8275-6D6622A6E7E9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1613</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1614</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2DB17B3B-838A-418C-9B95-00F762B8B583"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEFB7FF26-065F-4862-8609-CF281E118168">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1614</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1620</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2DB17B3B-838A-418C-9B95-00F762B8B583"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">27000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode85AB9FC3-B74F-4EB9-829D-3F757E9B586B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1975</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1976</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode911C6FFA-1F70-476E-BAB7-99FA76FAAA41"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7DE234FE-F32C-4F3F-BABE-3FF64EE7CBAC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1975</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1980</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode911C6FFA-1F70-476E-BAB7-99FA76FAAA41"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeAA7F1B55-B026-4BBC-9528-6A8B3FF1687E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1976</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1980</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode911C6FFA-1F70-476E-BAB7-99FA76FAAA41"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">8000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7FB076DC-E72E-4ACC-B4BF-AE12D3DCA550">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3097</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3105</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4B2A2A65-361C-4BB5-B356-597B713ED3AB"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE9D189FB-2743-4380-9E2B-706BC36BEFCB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3097</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3098</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4B2A2A65-361C-4BB5-B356-597B713ED3AB"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4C32B305-137E-4E2C-B13B-FEB9748E1D0C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3099</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3105</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4B2A2A65-361C-4BB5-B356-597B713ED3AB"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">45000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>