<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370037" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeC834BDE6-DB96-476E-9699-AA9E493CF847">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1666.66</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode3F343724-A72A-4DAA-A94F-024CD2DD609B">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">25000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode0D2D1E70-B294-4FC8-9948-00AAB0C3DF29">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT For Participants in the Doctoral Scholars Program of The Tennessee Board of Regents Commencing Academic Year 2009-2010 This agreement is entered into between Mittie K. Carey (scholar), the Tennessee Board of Regents (TBR or “state”), and the University of Memphis (institution). SCHOLAR RESPONSIBILITIES The scholar, Mittie K. Carey as a condition of participation: A.    Agrees to maintain satisfactory academic progress toward completion of the doctoral degree, and to submit to the TBR and the Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) grades/progress reports at the end of each term. B.    Agrees not to accept any other fellowship or scholarship award while receiving the TBR Scholars Dissertation Award without the written approval of TBR and SREB. C.     Agrees not to accept part-time or full-time employment, other than defined in Item “A” of Departmental Responsibilities, while receiving program support without first receiving permission from the TBR program director or the SREB program director. D.     Agrees to enroll full-time (as defined by the institution) in consecutive terms (including summers) until degree requirements are completed (whichever occurs first). Exceptions must be approved in advance by the TBR or SREB program director. E.     Agrees to attend the Doctoral Scholars Program’s annual meeting (Institute) at the expense of the program. F.     Agrees to designate a mentor/advisor in the scholar’s major field of study to attend the annual Institute at program expense for the three years of program support. G.    Agrees to notify and obtain approval from the institution (departments) and the Doctoral Scholars Program director before changing degree program. H.    Agrees to consult with SREB program staff concerning any academic, financial, or personal conditions (not in violation of Americans with Disability Act) that might affect the scholar’s status as a program participant. I.      Agrees that in the event the scholar decides to leave the program prior to achieving the terminal degree, the scholar will give at least three months notice to the institution, the state (TBR) and program officials. The SREB Doctoral Scholars Program director and other appropriate officials shall review the scholar’s decision and determine the proper course of action as directed by institutional, program and state rules and regulations, including the possibility of renewing enrollment in a degree program at a later date or the need for the scholar to repay any expended program funds. J.     Agrees to seek employment with a TBR institution or within the state of Tennessee, upon course completion or graduation. K.     Agrees to any additional terms specified by the state and/or institution as a condition of participation. All additional agreements should be attached to this document before signing. INSTITUTION RESPONSIBILITIES I. Financial Institution: A.     Agrees to accept state and/or private foundation support for students up to three years B.     Agrees that if progress is satisfactory but the scholar has not completed the doctoral degree at the end of the three-year period funded through the Doctoral Scholars Program, the institution will provide the same level of stipend support (see attachment 1, Funding Summary Addendum) for at least two additional years. University support beyond the third year will be subject to annual review by the university. C.     Agrees not to require student to pay tuition and fees (in-state or out-of-state) for up to five years of program support. D.     Agrees not to decrease the internal funds available for minority financial support as a result of the Doctoral Scholars program effort nor substitute Doctoral Scholars Program support for other internal scholarship programs. II. Sei ection/Application The Institution: E.     Agrees to work with TBR to identify and select student participants for the Doctoral Scholars Program. F.     Agrees to general eligibility requirements for Doctoral Scholar participants that specify: •     Must be a resident of Tennessee; •     Racial/ethnic minority students who hold or will receive a bachelor’s or master’s degree from an accredited college or University are eligible to apply; •     Students must have completed all course work and be in the dissertation stage of degree completion; •     Emphasis is given to students seeking a Ph.D. in the fields of science, mathematics and engineering; and •     The Doctoral Scholars Program will not support students pursuing professional degrees such as the M.D., D.D.S., J.D., and D.V.M. Also, graduate study in education is not supported, with the exception of students pursuing the Ph.D. in math or science education. III. Miscellaneous The Institution: G.    Agrees that students who receive Doctoral Scholar awards will not be allowed to accept I “double-up” support (in addition to tuition and fee support) from other scholarship or fellowship awards. (See Item “A” of Departmental Responsibilities). H.     Retains control over all admissions, retention, and graduation decisions. I.     Agrees to provide progress reports on program participants to TBR and SREB. J.     Agrees to encourage the employment of program scholars within the TBR system upon the successful completion of the degree within the institution or at other institutions within the state of Tennessee. INSTITUTION DEPARTMENTAL RESPONSIBILITIES The Communication Department: A.    Agrees not to provide scholars with financial assistance or awards (including assistantships) in addition to tuition and fee support without approval from Doctoral Scholars program director. (See Item “G” Institutional Responsibilities). B.     Agrees to provide a mentor/advisor in the student’s major field of study who will establish a supportive environment for the scholar. The mentor (or a person approved by the Doctoral Scholars Program) will be invited to accompany the scholar to the Doctoral Scholars Program’s annual Institute. C.     Agrees to designate an individual (presumably the faculty mentor) responsibility for monitoring and reporting on the academic progress of the doctoral scholar. D.     Agrees that following the first year for students entering the program from the baccalaureate, or any time for students entering the program with a master’s degree, each Scholar will be provided a graduate teaching/research opportunity. Any appointment as a graduate (research or teaching) assistant shall be at a rate of compensation consistent with institutional practices. E.     Agrees to develop and promote activities to enhance the professional development and teaching expertise of the scholar. F.     Agrees to encourage scholar participation in the appropriate disciplinary association. TBR RESPONSIBILITIES The TBR: A.     Agrees to support the cooperative regional program for a sufficient period of time to allow a significant number of scholars to complete degrees and assume faculty positions. Support is contingent upon availability of appropriated funds. B.     Agrees to provide support for the scholar for up to three years in the amount of $25,000 per year beginning fall 2009, contingent upon the availability of state funds. Participating institutions will provide further support if necessary. See attached addendum - FUNDING SUMMARY. C.     Agrees to seek the involvement of appropriate TBR system universities that grant doctoral degrees. D.    Agrees to promote the scholarship program and the recruitment of minority students outside the traditional students sought by many institutions - scholars who are prepared to teach in a variety of institutional settings. E. Agrees to put in writing and attach to this document any contracts, agreements, rules, or regulations necessary and proper to carry out the purposes and intent of the Doctoral Scholars Program. (For example, any payback, service requirement, or forgivable loan stipulations that are not specified under SREB, student, departmental or institution responsibilities). APPLICABLE LAW The terms and conditions of this Agreement will be governed by the laws of the State of Tennessee. Any modifications which change the intent of any item in this document will be subject to review and the document must be re-signed by all parties. Should any part of this agreement be judged in error, remaining content and conditions will continue in effect. EFFECTIVE DATE This Agreement will be effective when executed by all parties and upon execution, its terms and conditions shall apply retroactively to the month and date the student enrolled as a recipient of the TBR Doctoral Scholars award, which, for all purposes, will be deemed the anniversary date. Addendum attached: Funding Summary ADDENDUM Doctoral Scholar Funding Summary Scholar: Mittie K. Carev            SSN: 410-86-2277 5382 Heritage Avenue Memphis, TN 38115 Institution: University of Memphis Field of Study: Communication Effective Date: August 1, 2009 Student’s failure to fulfill any of the requirements outlined in the Scholar Responsibilities section of this agreement may result in suspension or forfeiture of all funding and support services. Funding Participants: Tennessee Board of Regents/ University of Memphis Funding Arrangements: Doctoral The State of Tennessee agrees to provide support for the above scholar for up to three years in the amount of $25,000 per year beginning Fall 2009, contingent upon the availability of state funds. The above scholar will receive an annual stipend of $20,000 ($l,666.66/mo., paid on or about the 28lh of the month) for up to three years while completing the doctoral degree. The Southern Regional Education Board will provide program and fiscal management services, in addition to arranging for payment of expenses for the scholar to attend the annual Institute on Teaching and Mentoring. Institution will not require the scholar to pay tuition and fees for a period up to five years. SIGNATURES All participating parties in the TBR Doctoral Scholars Program have read and understand the responsibilities and regulations that govern the Program and have caused their Agreement to be executed on the date set forth below by their affixed signatures. DATE: DATE: DcarKof the Graduate School University of Memphis DATE:   r /Z) ~Q STATE: STATE: Charles Manning, Chancellor      '—J13 Tennessee Board of Regents 1 ? DATE: | ---1--v—-----— /U?)ZD,         fittf'd- TBR-MOA Mittie K.TAirey 2009                      Page 7 of 7</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE3ED2CA3-8FD7-4822-B0CE-0D13807D5D95">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7137</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7144</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3F343724-A72A-4DAA-A94F-024CD2DD609B"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7671008A-5272-44B6-84C0-4CCEF558AFE0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7137</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7138</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3F343724-A72A-4DAA-A94F-024CD2DD609B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA9224E42-6D64-40F9-93B9-8A3924E79C15">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7138</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7144</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode3F343724-A72A-4DAA-A94F-024CD2DD609B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">25000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD8BB1703-BC1B-4CE2-9B78-B46F29A16827">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9536</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9537</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC834BDE6-DB96-476E-9699-AA9E493CF847"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode97551A25-D394-4CB9-93C6-0E4A4FCF9818">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9536</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9545</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC834BDE6-DB96-476E-9699-AA9E493CF847"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEF6A1957-FA2A-43D6-8E97-E4D963CA92AD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9537</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">9545</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC834BDE6-DB96-476E-9699-AA9E493CF847"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1666.66</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>