<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370046" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeD1B29CCA-C456-40E2-BAC2-E6C0CF5C672E">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3324.92</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeAA715CF2-F2BD-422B-B918-64873462ED6B">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">39899</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode132A2244-39FA-44CB-BE1F-1F1287852CD7">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">17</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode433106FE-B0E9-45AA-B2EA-A3A822140B53">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR AND IN CONSIDERATION of the mutual benefits according to the parties hereto, Shelby County Health Care Corporation, d/b/a The Regional Medical Center at Memphis (hereinafter referred to as “LICENSOR”) hereby issues a License to The University of Memphis (hereinafter referred to as “LICENSEE”) for and on behalf of the Memphis Speech and Hearing Center, pursuant to the terms and conditions set out herein: WITNESSETH: 1.     LICENSEE has been utilizing space in the Adams Pavilion of the Regional Medical Center at Memphis, 877 Jefferson Avenue, Memphis, Tennessee, (hereinafter referred to as “Facility"), under the terms of a License Agreement effective November 1, 1996; and 2.     LICENSEE desires to use space in the Facility for faculty research, office, laboratory and other educational purposes. NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration of the premises above recited, the parties agree as follows: 1.     LICENSE - LICENSOR hereby grants to LICENSEE the privilege to use 2347 square feet of space in the Adams Pavilion of the Regional Medical Center, 877 Jefferson Avenue, Memphis, Tennessee, for educational and related activities certain areas in the Facility as reflected in the attached Exhibit A. This License shall not confer upon or vest in LICENSEE any title, interest or estate in the Facility and may be revoked by LICENSOR subject to the terms and conditions hereof. 2.     TERM - The term of this License Agreement shall be three (3) years from April 1, 2010 until March 31, 2013. 3.    FEE - The LICENSEE agrees to pay LICENSOR an annual license fee of $17.00 per square foot used for a total annual amount of $39,899 ($3324.92 per month). The fee shall be paid on a monthly basis at the end of each month beginning May 2010. 4.    SPACE MODIFICATION - The LICENSOR agrees to modify the space to meet LICENSEE’S initial requirement at no cost. Any later modification will be at LICENSEE’S expense unless agreed otherwise by the parties. 5.     KEYS - LICENSOR shall furnish LICENSEE keys to the licensed space. At LICENSEE’S request, LICENSOR may cause or permit LICENSEE to key the laboratory space containing specialized equipment so only LICENSEE staff shall have access. 6.    TERMINATION - The LICENSOR or LICENSEE may terminate this License Agreement at-will with sixty (60) days written notice to the other. 7.    LICENSEE EQUIPMENT AND FURNISHING - During the term hereof LICENSEE may install equipment and furnishing in the space that shall remain the property of LICENSEE. Upon termination or expiration of this License Agreement, LICENSEE may remove all equipment and furnishings that it installs or uses in the space. Except as otherwise provided in this License Agreement, Licensee shall be solely responsible for repair and maintenance of equipment and furnishings that it installs or uses as well as any cost associated with installing or modifying any such equipment or furnishings. 8.     LICENSEE LIABILITY - Any and all claims against the State of Tennessee including LICENSEE, its officers, agents and employees, based upon this License Agreement or for damages, expenses, or attorney’s fees shall be heard and determined by the Board of Claims or the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee in the manner prescribed by law. Damages recoverable against the LICENSEE shall be limited expressly to claims paid by the Claims Commission pursuant to Tennessee Law. 9.     ASSIGNMENT - This License Agreement shall not be transferred, conveyed or assigned to another party. 10.    NOTICE - Unless otherwise provided herein, all written notices shall be delivered to the respective parties as follows: TO THE LICENSEE: Procurement Services The University of Memphis 115B Administration Building Memphis, Tennessee 38152 TO THE LICENSOR: Regional Medical Center at Memphis Support Operation 877 Jefferson Avenue Memphis, Tennessee 38103 11. ACCESS - The LICENSOR shall provide LICENSEE access to the Facility and licensed space at all times for the uses authorized herein. LICENSEE shall also have access to common areas and restrooms. 12. SERVICES - LICENSOR shall furnish to the LICENSEE, at no additional cost to LICENSEE, the following services and supplies: Janitor Services &amp; Supplies Drinking Fountain Elevator Service Air Conditional Equipment Security Hot and Cold Water Equipment Restroom Supplies Heat Equipment Utilities (heat and air conditioning) Genera] Maintenance Communications Access The janitorial service shall be provided in accordance with the following schedule: Daily - Dust all furniture, counters, and cabinets and window sills; sweep all floors, empty all wastebaskets and ashtrays, dispose of all rubbish; clean and maintain in sanitary condition all restrooms and plumbing fixtures; sweep sidewalks, stairways and halls; remove snow from entrance ways and parking areas if present; clean the parking area; and replace light bulbs, tubes, ballasts ands starters if necessary. Weekly - Mop all floors and dust all Venetian blinds, vacuum rugs, if any. Every other month - Strip and wax all floors. Semi- Annually - Wash all windows, Venetian blinds, light fixtures, walls and painted surfaces. LICENSOR shall also maintain the Facility in a condition that is free of pests, rodents, and other vermin. In the event of the failure Dy LICENSOR to furnish any such service, utilities or supplies in a satisfactory manner, LICENSEE may furnish the same at its own cost, and, in addition to any other remedy may have, may deduct the amount thereof from the license fee that may then be or thereafter become due hereunder. 13.   REPAIR AND MAINTENANCE - Initially, LICENSOR shall modify the space to meet LICENSEE’S requirement and paint the licensed space. Further, during the license term, the LICENSOR shall maintain the licensed space and appurtenances which it provides in good repair and tenantable condition, including, but not limited to, the maintenance and repair of the elevator, if any, plumbing, heating, electrical, air conditioning and ventilating equipment and fixtures to the end that all such facilities are kept in good operative condition except in case of damages arising solely from a willful or negligent act of the LICENSEE’S agent, invitee, or employee. LICENSOR’S obligations shall also include, but are not limited to, periodic painting to the satisfaction of LICENSEE, furnishing and replacing electrical light bulbs, fluorescent tubes, ballasts and starters, and air conditioning and ventilating equipment filters. In case LICENSOR, after notice in writing from LICENSEE requiring LICENSOR to comply with the requirements of this paragraph in regard to a specific condition, shall fail, refuse or neglect to comply therewith, or in the event of an emergency constituting a hazard to the health or safety of LICENSEE’S employees, property, or invitees, the LICENSEE may perform such maintenance or make such repair at its own cost, and in addition to any other remedy LICENSEE may have, may deduct the amount thereof from the license fee that may then be or thereafter become due hereunder. 14.    COMPLIANCE - Should either party fail or neglect to comply with any term or condition of this License Agreement or to comply with written notice and demand, this License Agreement shall be subject to immediate termination by the non-defaulting party. 15.   HOLDING OVER - In the event LICENSEE remains in possession of the licensed space after the expiration of the original term, or any extension thereof, this License Agreement shall be automatically extended on a month to month basis, subject to thirty (30) days termination by either party, and otherwise on the terms and conditions herein specified, so far as applicable. 16.    CODES - LICENSOR shall maintain the Facility in accordance with any applicable fire, building, life safety and handicapped accessibility codes. 17.    APPROPRIATIONS - All terms and conditions of this License Agreement are made subject to the continued appropriations by the appropriate legislative body. In that regard, LICENSEE shall have the right to terminate this License Agreement at the end of its fiscal year (June 30th) in the event that sufficient funds are not appropriated by the Tennessee General Assembly and/or budgeted for continuation of this License. 18.   SURRENDER OF POSSESSION - Upon termination or expiration of this License Agreement, LICENSEE will peaceably surrender to the LICENSOR the licensed space in as good order and condition as when received, reasonable use and wear thereof and damage by earthquake, fire, public calamity, the elements, acts of God, or circumstances over which LICENSEE has nc control or for which LICENSOR is responsible pursuant to this license excepted. LICENSEE shall have no duty to remove any improvements or fixtures placed by it on the premises or to restore any portion of the premises altered by it, save and except in the event LICENSEE elects to remove any such improvement or fixture and such removal causes damages or injury to the licensed space and then only to the extent of any such damage or injury. 19.    DESTRUCTION - If the licensed space is totally destroyed by fire or other casualty or otherwise rendered uninhabitable, this License Agreement shall terminate. 20.    This License Agreement shall supersede and void the License Agreement effective April 1, 2005. 21.    GTLA: LICENSOR is governed by the terms of the Tennessee Governmental Tort Liability, T.C.A. 29-20- 101 et seq. (“GTLA”), which limits the liability of LICENSOR. 22.    NONDISCRIMINATION: The parties hereto agree not to discriminate against any individual on account of race, religion, national origin, sex, those of Vietnam era veterans’ status or handicap unrelated to the reasonable requirements of this Agreement. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties hereto have caused this License Agreement to be executed by their duly authorized representatives on the dates indicated. LICENSEE: THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS Shirley C. Raiwe: President (y LICENSOR: SHELBY COUNTY HEALTH CARE CORPORATION, D/B/A THE REGIONAL MEDICAL CENTER AT MEMPHIS / A —i . A Dated:      / -O / ,7 _____________________ TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS 1         —--A"" Charles Manning, Chancellor       {J Dated:               A --</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode2B52A968-7273-41D3-8650-189E45CF69DD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1589</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1595</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode132A2244-39FA-44CB-BE1F-1F1287852CD7"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode655A9247-288E-4932-A2C9-1F1BDDE83C80">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1589</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1590</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode132A2244-39FA-44CB-BE1F-1F1287852CD7"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode63E0180C-EEFA-4227-ADBA-7AA09E06128E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1590</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1595</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode132A2244-39FA-44CB-BE1F-1F1287852CD7"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">17</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBF60F1E1-F6F0-4F37-93F9-447326DA12E8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1646</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1647</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeAA715CF2-F2BD-422B-B918-64873462ED6B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5E029FCA-CE84-44B9-920E-2750EA6B743F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1646</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1653</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeAA715CF2-F2BD-422B-B918-64873462ED6B"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD30E4BC8-2A9C-4C9F-8713-A7E6B4A619B6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1647</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1653</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeAA715CF2-F2BD-422B-B918-64873462ED6B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">39899</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode74C0246B-78B7-44C7-8D3E-7EBABAFAB15B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1655</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1663</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD1B29CCA-C456-40E2-BAC2-E6C0CF5C672E"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode59D029AA-AE94-44B1-879E-1CD3BC7AB4E2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1655</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1656</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD1B29CCA-C456-40E2-BAC2-E6C0CF5C672E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA966124C-855C-4EB9-975A-3D4B4607EB02">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1656</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1663</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD1B29CCA-C456-40E2-BAC2-E6C0CF5C672E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3324.92</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>