<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370035" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE2686576-B348-4426-9BD0-8E7FF158BBDE">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">250</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeDC1B55C0-7AEB-41BB-9B5D-30736F188AC4">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">9000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeAD26F13C-0ED6-43DF-8010-CEFB2E7DD0F0">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">65</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeECE47993-0B48-410E-9494-DC244EDE3380">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">GROUP SALES AGREEMENT The following represents an agreement (“Agreement”) between Radisson Hotel Nashville Airport (“Hotel”) and Tennessee Board of Regents (“Organization”) entered into as of December 4, 2009 and outlines specific conditions and services to be provided. Description of Group and Event: Organization:                       Tennessee Board of Regents Treva Berryman Associate Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs 1415 Murfreesboro Road, Suite 324 Nashville, TN 37217 PH: 615-366-4442 EMAIL: Treva.berryman@tbr.edu Name of Event:              Tennessee Board of Regents Regents Academic Leadership Institute (RALI) Anticipated Attendance: 26 Guest Room Commitment: The Hotel will provide and Organization agrees that it will be utilizing the 66-72 Total Room Nights” as follows:  SUNDAY MONDAY TUESDAY WEDNESDAY THURSDAY FRIDAY SATURDAY DATE  1/4/10 1/5/10 1/6/10 1/7/10   SINGLE  24 24 24 CIO   Total # of Rooms  24 24 24    Guest Room Rates: The Organization agrees to compensate the hotel as follows: Based upon Organization’s Total Room Nights as described in this Agreement, Hotel confirms the following group rates (net of all taxes): Single:        $65.00*        * Breakfast included in rate * Double:       $65.00* In addition, hotel room rates are subject to applicable state and local taxes (9.25% sales tax, 6% occupancy tax, $2.50 city tax) in effect at the time of check-in. Hotel Understands that organization is exempt from State sales tax. Method of Reservation: Reservations for the Event will be made by rooming list. Group will submit the rooming list by Monday, December 21, 2009. Function Space: The following represents an outline for your meeting and estimated function needs. The following represents an outline for your meeting and estimated function needs. Day / Date Time Function Setup Attendees Rental / Set up fee F&amp;B Pricing See Attached Function Space Grid for Daily Meeting Room Requirments       It is our understanding that you have made the above arrangements at the Hotel for meeting and/or banquet facilities. The details and terms of any such arrangements may be contained in a separate Banquet Event Order, the terms and conditions of which are incorporated herein by reference. It has been determined that set up fee charges for the entire program will be 250.00+ per day or $750.00 total for the week. In addition, a $2,000.00 food and beverage minimum is required. A 15% gratuity is required on food, room set-up, and AV equipment. All pricing is per hotel’s response to Request for Quotation #10-0432. Billing Arrangements: The following billing arrangement will apply: X Room and tax charges go to Master Account. Individuals pay own incidental charges. X All banquet and catering charges to Master Account ‘Authorized signatories allowed up to $200.00 miscellaneous charges if needed. Master Account: Hotel must be notified in writing at least 2 weeks prior to arrival of the authorized signatories and the charges that are to be posted to the Master Account. As a state agency, Organization shall not pay penalty or cancellation charges. Organization shall pay any actual reasonable documented damages or loss to Hotel for which it is liable under Tennessee Law. Payment: The method of payment of the Master Account will be established upon approval of the Organization’s credit. In order to establish credit with the Hotel for the purpose of billing to a Master Account, Organization must complete a credit application form supplied by the Hotel; this application must be completed and returned to the Hotel Sales Manager no later than 1 month prior to the scheduled Event. As a state agency, Organization shall not pay deposits. All charges for this event will be applied to a master bill which will be paid in full upon receipt of invoice from Hotel. The outstanding balance of the Master Account (exclusive of disputed charges) will be due and payable upon receipt of invoice. Organization will notify Hotel of any disputed charge(s) within twenty (20) days after receipt of the invoice. The Hotel will work with Organization in resolving any such disputed charges, the payment of which will be due upon receipt of invoice after resolution of the dispute. If Organization does not remit within forty-five (45) days after receipt of an invoice, Organization will pay a late charge of the lesser of 1.5% a month or the maximum amount permitted under the Prompt Pay Act of 1985 (Tennessee Code Annotated Section 12-4-701 et.seq.). Organization shall be not liable for the payment of collection costs, attorneys fees, or court costs associated with this Agreement. Payments to the Contractor shall be made according to the schedule set out above, but only after receipt of invoices for services performed. The final payment shall be made only after the Contractor has completely performed its duties under this agreement. Rooms Attrition: Organization understands that the Hotel is relying upon Organization’s use of the Total Room Nights. Organization shall pay any actual reasonable documented damages or loss to Hotel for which it is liable under Tennessee State Law. Food &amp; Beverage Policy: All food and beverage service within the Hotel must be provided by the Hotel and serviced by Hotel personnel. Food and beverage may not be brought in from outside of the Hotel. Organization understands that, if alcoholic beverages are to be served on the Hotel premises (or elsewhere under the Hotel’s alcoholic beverage license), the Hotel’s alcoholic beverage license requires such beverages be dispensed only by its employees and bartenders. The Hotel’s alcoholic beverage license requires the Hotel to (a) request proper identification of any person of questionable age and refuse alcoholic beverage service if the person is either underage or proper identification cannot be produced, and (b) refuse alcoholic beverage service to any person who, in the Hotel’s sole judgement, appears intoxicated. The Hotel encourages the adoption by banquet groups of a designated driver program, whereby one or more persons accept the responsibility of not consuming alcoholic beverages and providing transportation of others in the party. The Hotel will be happy to assist anyone upon request in making alternative transportation arrangements and/or overnight accommodations during the course of Organization’s function. Cancellation: In no event shall the liability of the Organization under this contract exceed $9000.00 This agreement may be terminated by either party by giving written notice to the other, at least 30 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, the Hotel shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory authorized work completed as of the termination date. Impossibility: The performance of this Agreement is subject to any circumstance making it illegal or impossible to provide or use the Hotel facilities, including acts of God, war, government regulations, disaster, strikes, civil disorder, or curtailment of transportation facilities. Neither a change of ownership or management of the Hotel, nor a change in management of Organization shall relieve either party of the responsibilities and obligations of this agreement. Compliance with Law: The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this agreement. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon notice, by the Institution or the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. Changes, Additions and other Modifications: This agreement may be modified only by written amendment executed by all parties hereto. Litigation Expenses: Organization shall be not liable for the payment of attorney’s fees or court costs associated with this Agreement. Any and all claims against Organization for property damage or loss resulting from acts or omissions or Organization through its employees or agents in performing its responsibilities under this agreement shall be submitted to the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee for disposition in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Tennessee Code Annotated. Damages recoverable against Organization shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Commission. Acceptance: Prior to execution by both parties, this Agreement represents an offer by the Hotel. Unless the Hotel otherwise notifies Organization at any time prior to Hotel’s receipt of the Agreement executed by December 11, 2010. Upon receipt by Hotel of this Agreement signed by Organization, this Agreement will be placed on a definite basis and will be binding upon Hotel and Organization. If a signed Agreement is not received by Hotel from Organization by the Acceptance Date, the offer will revert to a second-option basis. In any event, this Agreement shall not be binding on the parties until signed by both parties, including any changes, additions or deletions. Hotel and Organization have agreed to and have executed this Agreement by their authorized representatives as of the Effective Date. -J Radisson Ho^l Nashville Airport Signature:   "Ik, 2 C.WjLzr Name: Date: Title: Director of Sales &amp; Marketing___________ Tim Struzynski i^| Wo?</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeFD317063-5830-4641-878F-910496392F6E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1170</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1176</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeAD26F13C-0ED6-43DF-8010-CEFB2E7DD0F0"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode94C38C9D-B4AE-49AA-8734-3B8E493B3373">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1170</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1171</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeAD26F13C-0ED6-43DF-8010-CEFB2E7DD0F0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode51DE10E6-79B4-4B80-A527-FE647357E13E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1171</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1176</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeAD26F13C-0ED6-43DF-8010-CEFB2E7DD0F0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">65</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4BE353D3-BD4E-4C52-ABFE-413159D71115">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2312</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2318</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE2686576-B348-4426-9BD0-8E7FF158BBDE"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode426D1640-7366-4A8D-AC6F-90E257A14568">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2312</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2318</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE2686576-B348-4426-9BD0-8E7FF158BBDE"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">250</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA5058969-0CA6-427A-8800-0A34175F7509">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6463</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6471</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeDC1B55C0-7AEB-41BB-9B5D-30736F188AC4"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE7F8CDB3-4BEF-4012-A80F-1FCFEA91B857">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6463</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6464</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeDC1B55C0-7AEB-41BB-9B5D-30736F188AC4"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode029962E8-3900-4BEE-8676-FEA5F1E73C2E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6464</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">6471</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeDC1B55C0-7AEB-41BB-9B5D-30736F188AC4"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">9000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>