<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370024" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8F9AA27F-33C9-4F19-B003-8D8502AECC11">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">321610</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode1298176F-99FB-4977-8495-6B7C09FF53D3">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN VOLUNTEER STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND THE UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS This Agreement, by and between Volunteer State Community College, hereinafter referred to as the “Institution” and The University of Memphis, hereinafter referred to as the “Contractor,” is for the provision of the help desk services, as further defined in the "SCOPE OF SERVICES." The Contractor’s address is: The University of Memphis Administration Building, Room 377 Memphis, TN 38152-3370 A.    SCOPE OF SERVICES. A.1. The objective of this service level agreement is to establish service levels for all technical support and informational assistance to be provided to Volunteer State by the University of Memphis Information Technology Division helpdesk and to document expectations of two-way accountability between the Information Technology Division and Volunteer State. Services to include items defined in Attachment A. B.    AGREEMENT TERM: B.1. Agreement Term. This Agreement shall be effective for the period commencing on August 24, 2009 and ending on June 30, 2010. The Institution shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. B. 2.    Term Extension. The Institution reserves the right to extend this Agreement for an additional period or periods of time representing increments of no more than one year and a total Agreement term of no more than 5 years, provided that the Institution notifies the Contractor in writing of its intention to do so at least 30 days prior to the Agreement expiration date. An extension of the term of this Agreement will be affected through an amendment to the Agreement. If the extension of the Agreement necessitates additional funding beyond that which was included in the original Agreement, the increase in the Institution’s maximum liability will also be affected through an amendment to the Agreement and shall be based upon rates provided for in the original Agreement.                             &lt; C.    PAYMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS: C.1. Maximum Liability. In no event shall the maximum liability of the Institution under this Agreement exceed $321,610 defined in Attachment B. The maximum liability represents available funds for payment to the Contractor and does not guarantee payment of any such funds to the Contractor under this Agreement unless the Contractor performs said work. C.2. Compensation Firm. The Maximum Liability of the Institution under this Agreement are firm for the duration of the Agreement and are not subject to escalation for any reason unless amended. C.3. Payment Methodology. The Contractor shall submit monthly invoices, in form and substance acceptable to the Institution prior to any payment. C.4. Travel Compensation. The Contractor shall not be compensated or reimbursed for travel, meals, or lodging. C.5. Payment of Invoice. The payment of the invoice by the Institution shall not prejudice the Institution's right to object to or question any invoice or matter in relation thereto. Such payment by the Institution shall neither be construed as acceptance of any part of the work or service provided nor as an approval of any of the amounts invoiced therein. C.6. Price Increases for Services. Prices of services may be increased only if the Contractor can provide proof of price increase for the item(s). It will be solely the Institution’s right to choose to accept the price increase, negotiate a mutually agreeable amount, or cancel the item from the Agreement. Volunteer State Community College requires sixty (60) day notice of anticipated price increases for services. C.7. Invoice Reductions. The Contractor's invoice shall be subject to reduction for amounts included in any invoice or payment theretofore made which are determined by the Institution, on the basis of audits conducted in accordance with the terms of this Agreement, not to constitute proper remuneration for compensable services. C.8. Deductions. The Institution reserves the right to deduct from amounts which are or shall become due and payable to the Contractor under this or any Agreement between the Contractor and the Institution any amounts which are or shall become due and payable to the Institution by the Contractor. D. STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS. D.1. Required Approvals. The Institution is not bound by this Agreement until it is approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee Institution laws and regulations. D.2. Modification and Amendment. This Agreement may be modified only by a written amendment executed by all parties hereto and approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee Institution laws and regulations. D.3. Termination for Convenience. The Institution may terminate this Agreement without cause for any reason. Said termination shall not be deemed a Breach of Agreement by the Institution. The Institution shall give the Contractor at least 30 days written notice before the effective termination date. The Contractor shall be entitled to receive compensation for satisfactory, authorized service completed as of the termination date, but in no event shall the Institution be liable to the Contractor for compensation for any service which has not been rendered. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to any actual general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. D.4. Termination for Cause. If the Contractor fails to properly perform its obligations under this Agreement in a timely or proper manner, or if the Contractor violates any terms of this Agreement, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate the Agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for completed services. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the Institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Agreement by the Contractor. D.5. Subcontracting. The Contractor shall not assign this Agreement or enter into a subcontract for any of the services performed under this Agreement without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution. If such subcontracts are approved by the Institution, they shall contain, at a minimum, sections of this Agreement pertaining to "Conflicts of Interest" and "Nondiscrimination" (sections D.6. and D.7.). Notwithstanding any use of approved subcontractors, the Contractor shall be the prime contractor and shall be responsible for all work performed. D.6. Nondiscrimination. The Contractor hereby agrees, warrants, and assures that no person shall be excluded from participation in, be denied benefits of, or be otherwise subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Agreement or in the employment practices of the Contractor on the grounds of disability, age, race, color, religion, sex, veteran status, national origin, or any other classification protected by Federal, or Tennessee constitutional or statutory law. The Contractor shall, upon request, show proof of such nondiscrimination and shall post in conspicuous places, available to all employees and applicants, notices of nondiscrimination. D.7. Strict Performance. Failure by any party to this Agreement to insist in any one or more cases upon the strict performance of any of the terms, covenants, conditions, or provisions of this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of any such term, covenant, condition, or provision. No term or condition of this Agreement shall be held to be waived, modified, or deleted except by a written amendment signed by the parties hereto. D.8. Institution Liability. The Institution shall have no liability except as specifically provided in this Agreement. D.9. Force Majeure. The obligations of the parties to this Agreement are subject to prevention by causes beyond the parties’ control that could not be avoided by the exercise of due care including, but not limited to, acts of God, riots, wars, epidemics or any other similar cause. D.10. Institution and Federal Compliance. The Contractor shall comply with all applicable State and Federal laws and regulations, including Institution policies and guidelines in the performance of this Agreement. D.11. Governing Law. This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee. The Contractor agrees that it will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Tennessee Claims Commission in actions that may arise under this Agreement. The Contractor acknowledges and agrees that any rights or claims against the Institution or its employees hereunder, and any remedies arising there from, shall be subject to and limited to those rights and remedies, if any, available under Tennessee Code Annotated, Sections 9-8-101 through 9-8-407. D.12. Completeness. This Agreement is complete and contains the entire understanding between the parties relating to the subject matter contained herein, including all the terms and conditions of the parties’ agreement. This Agreement supersedes any and all prior understandings, representations, negotiations, and agreements between the parties relating hereto, whether written or oral. D.13. Severability. If any terms and conditions of this Agreement are held to be invalid or unenforceable as a matter of law, the other terms and conditions hereof shall not be affected thereby and shall remain in full force and effect. To this end, the terms and conditions of this Agreement are declared severable. D.14. Headings. Section headings of this Agreement are for reference purposes only and shall not be construed as part of this Agreement. E. SPECIAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS: E.1. Communications and Contacts. All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications required by this Agreement shall be in writing addressed to the respective party as set forth below or to such other party as may be hereafter specified by written notice. The Institution: Volunteer State Community College Stephanie Coker Ramer 180 Gallatin, TN 37066 Phone: (615)230-3429 Fax: (615)230-3515 Stephanie.coker@volstate.edu The Contractor: University of Memphis Douglas E. Hurley 377 Administration Building Memphis, TN 38152 Phone: 901-678-8324 Fax: 901-678-5656 dhurley@memphis.edu All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications shall be sent in a manner that verifies proof of delivery. Any communication by facsimile transmission shall also be sent by United States mail on the same date of the facsimile transmission. All communications which relate to any changes to the Agreement shall not be considered effective until agreed to, in writing, by both parties. E.2. Subject to Funds Availability. The Agreement is subject to the appropriation and availability of Institution and/or Federal funds. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, the Institution reserves the right to terminate the Agreement upon written notice to the Contractor. Said termination shall not be deemed a breach of Agreement by the Institution. Upon receipt of the written notice, the Contractor shall cease all work associated with the Agreement. Should such an event occur, the Contractor shall be entitled to compensation for all satisfactory and authorized services completed as of the termination date. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to recover from the Institution any actual, general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. E.3. Breach. A party shall be deemed to have breached the Agreement if any of the following, including but not limited to, occurs: — failure to perform in accordance with any term or provision of the Agreement; — partial performance of any term or provision of the Agreement; — any act prohibited or restricted by the Agreement, or — violation of any warranty. E.4. Institution Ownership of Work Products. The Institution shall have all ownership right, title, and interest, including ownership of copyright, in all work products created, designed, developed, derived, documented, installed, or delivered to the Institution under this Agreement. The Institution shall have unlimited rights to use, disclose, reproduce, or publish, for any purpose whatsoever, all said work products. The Contractor shall furnish such information and data upon request of the Institution, in accordance with the Agreement and applicable Institution law. E.5. Printing Authorization. The Contractor agrees that no publication coming within the jurisdiction of Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 12-7-101, et. seq., shall be printed unless a printing authorization number has been obtained and affixed as required by Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 12-7-103 (d). E.6. Competitive Procurements. If this Agreement provides for reimbursement of the cost of goods, materials, supplies, equipment, or services. Such procurements shall be made on a competitive basis, where practical. E.7. Institution Furnished Property. The Contractor shall be responsible for the correct use, maintenance, and protection of all articles of nonexpendable, tangible, personal property furnished by the Institution for the Contractor’s temporary use under this Agreement. Upon termination of this Agreement, all property furnished shall be returned to the Institution in good order and condition as when received, reasonable use and wear thereof excepted. Should the property be destroyed, lost, or stolen, the Contractor shall be responsible to the Institution for the residual value of the property at the time of loss. E.8. Incorporation of Additional Documents. Included in this Agreement by reference are the following documents: a.     The Agreement document and its attachments b.      Technical Specifications provided to the Contractor c.      All Clarifications and addenda made to the Contractor’s Proposal d.      The Contractor’s Proposal In the event of a discrepancy or ambiguity regarding the Contractor’s duties, responsibilities, and performance under this Agreement, these documents shall govern in order of precedence detailed above. </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD1F3CD48-6ED8-4372-81D1-55E6E4D495DC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2158</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2166</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8F9AA27F-33C9-4F19-B003-8D8502AECC11"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7F72F48C-A132-41A9-A0ED-F4A8FD66972C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2158</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2159</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8F9AA27F-33C9-4F19-B003-8D8502AECC11"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode879564DF-30BF-4CB1-AECB-1DE49C59850A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2159</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2166</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8F9AA27F-33C9-4F19-B003-8D8502AECC11"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">321610</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>