<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370012" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode479CB6FB-6573-448A-9656-F9E88D72B641">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1767</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeCE6167C2-4D42-407A-A162-F33F82D3F2DD">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3333</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode7A9E9ED2-8E04-4C77-B323-601726C3ECB7">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">AGREEMENT BETWEEN THE SAGE GROUP, LLC AND NASHVILLE STATE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE This Agreement is entered into as of this 1st day of July, 2009, by and between The Sage Group, LLC, a limited liability company formed under the laws of the State of Tennessee and having its principal office at 5300 Maryland Way, Suite 103, Brentwood, Tennessee (hereinafter Sage), and Nashville State Technical Community College, a state college formed under the laws of the State of Tennessee and having its principal office at 120 White Bridge Rd., Nashville, Tennessee 37209 (hereinafter College). RECITALS A. Sage provides courses of instruction, manuals, systems and instruction in a variety of subject areas of higher education B.  College, an accredited institution of higher education, is willing to recognize credit toward its appropriate degrees for students enrolled at Nashville State Technical Community College upon successful completion of Sage courses that have been evaluated by the National Program on Non-Collegiate Sponsored Instruction and have received college-level credit recommendations. ARTICLE I: Term. This Agreement shall have a term of five years from the effective date set forth above. The maximum term of this agreement cannot exceed a total of sixty (60) months. Continuation of this agreement beyond June 30, 2009, is subject to the appropriation of state funds. ARTICLE II: Nashville State Technical Community College Obligations. 2.1. College agrees to award transfer credit to Sage students toward the appropriate Nashville State Technical Community College degree for student who have successfully completed the Sage courses, provided that any such course for which recognition of credit is sought has been evaluated by the National Program on Non-Collegiate Sponsored Instruction and has received a college-level credit recommendation. These courses are listed on the following web site: http://www.nationalponsi.org/ccr/Listinqs/saqe qroup.htm. Students must be admitted and enrolled at Nashville State Technical Community College in order to receive the transfer credit. 2.2. College shall remit to Sage for courses taught by Sage, all course fees paid to College, by Sage students. Such amounts shall be remitted to Sage within fifteen (15) days after the end of the calendar month in which such fees were received by College. 2.3. College agrees that Sage may advertise the existence of this Agreement, and the availability of Nashville State Technical Community College credit for the successful completion of the courses in question by Nashville State Technical Community College students, and may refer to Nashville State Technical Community College in such advertising. College will cooperate with Sage in developing marketing materials to be used in the promotion and advertising of the availability of Nashville State Technical Community College credit for successful completion of the courses in question by Nashville State Technical Community College. The use by Sage of any and all such material shall be subject to the prior written approval of College. 2.4. Nashville State Technical Community College faculty may conduct an annual review of all materials used by Sage in connection with the courses which are the subject of this Agreement, and Sage agrees to make any revision in such materials as may be required by College and approved by the National Program on Non-Collegiate Sponsored Instruction. 2.5. College will maintain on file, provided by Sage, the credentials and qualifications of all Sage faculty who are teaching the courses which are the subject of this Agreement. 2.6. College will provide Sage with quarterly reports of the number of Sage students who have been awarded College credit during the prior quarter. Sage will obtain written permission from Sage students allowing college to release the educational information to Sage. 2.7. Should this Agreement be terminated for any reason, any student enrolled in a Sage course which is the subject of this Agreement at the time of termination will be awarded appropriate credit by College for successful completion of the course. 2.8. College agrees to allow Sage to market courses offered by Nashville State Technical Community College. These courses may be delivered by Sage facilitators and must follow NSCC’s approval process for staffing and course delivery. The courses will be eligible for awarding of credit as sited in Article II, 2.1. The use of any such marketing material by Sage is subject to the prior written approval of College. 2.9. Sage courses recommended for credit by the National Program on Non- Collegiate Sponsored Instruction will give NSCC course numbers. Sage students that meet College admission requirement may enroll directly in these courses, taught by Sage. The students will receive college credit upon successful completion of the course and enrollment in NSCC. 2.10. Grade issuance to students of completed courses, when requested by third parties from Nashville State Technical Community College, will be done in accordance with the College’s standard procedures and federal law. Release of grades to third parties requires the written consent of the student. Obtaining the students consent will be the responsibility of Sage. 2.11. Claims Against the State of Tennessee. The State of Tennessee is selfinsured and does not carry or maintain commercial general liability insurance or medical, professional or hospital liability insurance. Any and all claims against the State of Tennessee, including the Institution or its employees, shall be heard and determined by the Tennessee Claims Commission in the manner prescribed by law. Damages recoverable against the Institution shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Claims Commission pursuant to T.C.A. Section 9-8-301 et seq. ARTICLE III: Sage Obligations. 3.1. Sage shall provide to College, and shall keep current monthly, a roster of the names and addresses of all Sage students who are enrolled in the courses which are the subject of this Agreement. College may use such roster for recruitment purposes. 3.2. All Sage faculty will possess the appropriate credentials and experience to ensure that the projected outcomes of each Sage course will be achieved. Sage will promptly provide to College the credentials and qualifications of all new Sage faculty who are teaching the courses which are the subject of this Agreement. 3.3. Sage will recommend Nashville State Technical Community College examinations to Sage students, and will encourage students to enroll in Nashville State Technical Community College. 3.4. Sage will not alter, add to or delete from the content of any course which is the subject of this Agreement without prior verification from the National Program on Non-Collegiate Sponsored Instruction that the proposed change would not adversely affect its credit recommendations. 3.5. Sage will not state, suggest or imply to any student or prospective student, or in any other manner or forum, that Sage is an accredited institution of higher education or that it has any relationship with College other than the relationship described in this Agreement. 3.6. For college course delivered by Sage, Sage instructors will assign student grades. The grading will be transmitted electronically to the College’s records office. 3.7. Sage students required to enroll directly with Nashville State Technical Community College will receive transcript waivers for the purposes of taking courses delivered by Sage. Transcripts will be required of Sage students if such student(s) desire to enroll in classes offered either on-line or on-site delivered by College instructors. 3.8. Sage will inform Nashville State Technical Community College whenever Sage courses are taught within the NSCC service region of Middle Tennessee. NSCC faculty will be given the opportunity to teach these courses. 3.9. Sage shall remit to the College $3,333.00 per month that shall be restricted to faculty development for on-line courses for the targeted telecom industry, business processing costs, and other items approved by the President for which the use of state funding would be inappropriate. Additionally, Sage shall remit to the College $1,767.00 a month for a restricted scholarship fund for adult students who are not eligible for lottery scholarship or federal financial aid. Sage payment to College is due within fifteen (15) days of the close of the month. 3.10. Insurance Clause. Sage, being an independent contractor and not an employee of this Institution, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, to pay all taxes incident hereunto, and otherwise protect and hold the College harmless from any and all liability not specifically provided for in this agreement. ARTICLE IV: Termination. 4.1. Either party may terminate this agreement at any time by written notice of not less than one hundred twenty (120) days to the other party, stating the date on which termination is to take place. 4.2. Effect of termination. 4.2.1. Accrued obligations. Termination of this Agreement for any reason shall not release either party hereto from any liability which, at the time of such termination, has already accrued to the other party or which is attributable to a period prior to such termination, not preclude either party from pursuing all rights and remedies it may have. 4.2.2. Confidential information. Except as required by law, all confidential information shall remain the property of the disclosing party. Nashville State Technical Community College is a state institution and must comply with the Tennessee Open Records Act. ARTICLE V: Trademarks and Service Marks. 5.1. Ownership. Each party acknowledges that the other party owns various registered and unregistered trademarks and service marks, listed respectively in Attachment 1 hereto. 5.2. Use. Each party hereby grants to the other party the non-exclusive, limited right and license to use the other party’s marks for the purposes of and during the term of this Agreement, but not thereafter, in connection with the using party’s functions and obligations under this Agreement. Neither party shall acquire, or shall represent to others that it has acquired, any ownership rights in the marks of the other party. Each party agrees to use the other party’s marks solely in the manner prescribed or consented to by the other party in writing. ARTICLE VI: Records and Inspections. 6.1. Records. Each party shall keep complete and accurate books of account and records for the purpose of determining the amounts of its financial obligations to the other party. The books, records and documentation of the contract insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this contract, shall be maintained in conformity with generally accepted accounting principles. All such books and records shall be kept at a place or places of business in the United States, for a period of not less than four (4) years after the close of the period to which they pertain. 6.2. Inspection. All such records will be open for inspection by the other party or its designated representative during such four-year period, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice, by the Institution or the State Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representative, or a licensed independent public accountant. Each such inspection shall be at the expense of the party making it, unless otherwise provided herein. ARTICLE VII: Representations. Each party represents to the other that it has the full right and authority to enter into this Agreement, and to grant the rights granted herein; and that there are no pending or threatened actions, suits or claims against it with respect to its right to enter into and to perform its obligations under this Agreement. ARTICLE VIII: Confidentiality. 8.1. Confidential information. To the extent allowable by Tennessee law, except as expressly provided herein, the parties agree that, for the term of this agreement and for seven (7) years thereafter, the receiving party shall not publish or otherwise disclose to any third party, and shall not use for any purpose, except for the purposes of this Agreement, any information furnished to it by the other party pursuant to this Agreement which if disclosed by the other party in tangible form is marked “Confidential” or with other similar designation to indicate its confidential or proprietary nature; or if disclosed orally is confirmed as confidential or proprietary by the party disclosing such information at the time of disclosure. Notwithstanding the foregoing, it is understood and agreed that confidential information shall not include information that, in each case as demonstrated by written documentation: was already known to the receiving party, other than under obligation of confidentiality, at the time of disclosure; was generally available to the public or part of the public domain at the time of disclosure; became generally available to the public or part of the public domain after its disclosure to the other party, and other than through any act or omission of the receiving party in breach of this Agreement; or was subsequently lawfully disclosed to the receiving party by a third party; or was developed by the receiving party without reference to any information or materials disclosed by the other party. 8.2. Permitted disclosures. Notwithstanding the provisions in Section 6.1 above, each party may disclose the other’s confidential information to the extent necessary to comply with applicable statutes or governmental regulations. Prior to such disclosure, and to the extent it may legally do so, the disclosing party will give reasonable advance written notice to the other party of such proposed disclosure. ARTICLE IX: Indemnification. Neither party shall be responsible for personal injury or property damage or other loss suffered by any person or entity except that resulting from its own negligence, and nothing in this Agreement shall be construed as creating an obligation to indemnify the other party against that party’s own negligence. Any and all claims against the State of Tennessee, including the Institution or its employees shall be heard and determined by the Tennessee Claims Commission in the manner prescribed by law. Damages recoverable against the Institution shall be limited expressly to claims paid by the Claims Commission toT.C.A., Section 9-8-301 et seq. ARTICLE X: Miscellaneous. 10.1. Independent contractors. Each party agrees that it will perform as an independent contractor under this Agreement, and not as an agent or employee of the other party. Nothing in this Agreement is intended or shall be deemed to create a partnership or joint venture of any kind. Neither party shall have the authority to or shall attempt to bind or commit the other party for any purpose except as expressly provided herein. 10.2. Voluntary Buyout Program. Sage acknowledges and understands that, for a period of two years beginning August 16, 2008, restrictions are imposed on former state employees who received a State of Tennessee Voluntary Buyout Program (VBP) severance payment with regard to contracts with state agencies that participated in the VBP. 10.2.1. The State will not contract with either a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or an entity in which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment or the spouse of such an individual holds a controlling financial interest. 10.2.2. The State may contract with an entity with which a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment is an employee or an independent contractor. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Sage understands and agrees that there may be unique business circumstances under which a return to work by a former state employee who received a VBP severance payment as an employee or an independent contractor of a State contractor would not be appropriate, and in such cases the State may refuse Sage personnel. Inasmuch, it shall be the responsibility of the State to review Sage personnel to identify any such issues. 10.2.3. With reference to either subsection a. or b. above, Sage may submit a written request for a waiver of the VBP restrictions regarding a former state employee and a contract with a state agency that participated in the VBP. Any such request must be submitted to the State in the form of the VBP Contracting Restriction Waiver Request format available from the State and the Internet at: www.state.tn.us/finance/rds/ocr/waiver.html. The determination on such a request shall be at the sole discretion of the head of the state agency that is a Party to this Contract, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration, and the Commissioner of Human Resources. 10.3. Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, requires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, 0620. 10.4. Waiver. No failure on the part of either party to exercise, no delay in exercising, and no course of dealing with respect to any right, power or privilege under this Agreement shall operate as a waiver thereof, nor shall any single or partial exercise of any such right, power or privilege preclude any other or further exercise thereof, or the exercise of any other right, power or privilege. 10.5. Survival Beyond Termination. Any and all obligations arising under ARTICLE VI, ARTICLE VIII and ARTICLE IX shall survive the termination or completion of this Agreement. 10.6. Severability. If any provision hereof shall be held invalid, illegal or unenforceable, all other provisions hereof shall remain in full force and effect, and shall be liberally construed in order to carry out the intentions of the parties as nearly as may be possible. 10.7. Third Party Beneficiaries. Nothing in this Agreement shall entitle any person to any rights as a third-party beneficiary under this Agreement. 10.8. Force Majeure. Neither party shall be liable for delay or failure of performance of any of its obligations under this Agreement when such delay or failure arises from events or circumstances beyond the reasonable control of such party, including, without limitation, acts of God, fire, flood, explosion, sabotage, terrorism, embargo, civil commotion, acts or omissions of any government entity, or labor disputes. 10.9. Assignment. Neither party may assign this Agreement, or any part thereof, or any right or obligation herein conferred, without the prior written approval of the other party, which approval shall not be unreasonably withheld. 10.10. Entire Agreement. This document constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof, and all previous agreements or discussions between the parties relating to the subject matter hereof are hereby superseded by this document. 10.11. Amendment. This Agreement, including all attachments hereto, may be modified only in writing signed by both parties. 10.12. Enforcement. This Agreement shall be deemed to have been made in the State of Tennessee, and shall be construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee without regard to conflict of laws principles. 10.13. Counterparts. This Agreement may be executed in counterparts, each of which shall be deemed an original, but all of which together shall constitute a single instrument. ARTICLE XI: Notices. Any notice or formal communication by one party to the other party required or permitted under this Agreement shall be in writing, and may be sent by facsimile transmission or electronic mail, provided that the original shall be delivered either in person or by United States Mail or a non-governmental carrier, and shall be received by the addressee no later than three (3) business days after delivery to the carrier. All such notices shall be directed and addressed as set forth below, or to such other notice addresses as the parties or either of them may subsequently designate in writing. ARTICLE XII: Nondiscrimination. The parties agree to comply with Titles VI and VII of the civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1972, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11,246, and the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, veteran status or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. IN WITNESS WHEREOF the parties have executed this agreement as of the date first above written. The Sage Group, LLC By: (Signature) Richard Q. Ford President &amp; CEO Nashville State Technical Community College By:                                    _______ (Signature) George Van Allen President 7 Approved By: Ten ssee Board isf Regents (Signature) By: Charles Manning Chancellor</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode956238F4-0947-43B9-B610-2DEABA048A57">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7951</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7960</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeCE6167C2-4D42-407A-A162-F33F82D3F2DD"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode76DB7E61-ADA7-4DC0-A1E3-4EA39531DAAC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7951</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7952</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeCE6167C2-4D42-407A-A162-F33F82D3F2DD"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB86AF89B-9202-4372-8FC6-05E9277FDC24">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7952</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">7960</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeCE6167C2-4D42-407A-A162-F33F82D3F2DD"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3333</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD29EF323-BA98-4749-B22B-4ECD57BB12A6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8248</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8257</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode479CB6FB-6573-448A-9656-F9E88D72B641"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC52064FC-BBAD-4A4F-A5DE-5F73576FBBAC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8248</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8249</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode479CB6FB-6573-448A-9656-F9E88D72B641"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode124D2A87-9471-4DB1-ACE6-71736966381E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8249</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">8257</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode479CB6FB-6573-448A-9656-F9E88D72B641"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1767</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>