<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370137" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode7354A798-357D-4247-A5B1-7ABFFA93AD29">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Sudanese Pounds</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeADE734EE-09D1-4E53-B9C5-73BE6D61F6AD">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Apparently the SAF did not seek the legally required prior approval of a civilian prosecutor before carrying out the arrest. Accused of having stolen a sub-machine gun from a SAF garrison, the boy was held for a total of 44 days without being handed over to the police, even after the responsible civilian authorities made an official transfer request. Conversely, the SPLA arrested and detained a 55-year-old veterinary assistant of the Hawazma tribe in White Lake/Jaw on 28 January 2008. The man had worked for six years in the White Lake region, which is an assembly area for SPLA troops moving out of Southern Kordofan. The man was reportedly questioned by SPLA military intelligence in connection with the arrest of another SAF soldier. He was allegedly given 25 lashes on the morning of 29 January, and again three days later after he was questioned. The victim reported that he had 2,000 Sudanese Pounds worth of medicine with him when he was arrested and alleges that the medicine was not given back to him when he was released on 12 February.  In addition, the presence of the formal judiciary in remote areas is so limited that local populations rely almost entirely on traditional, customary law-based administration of justice. While traditional systems of justice may work well in resolving many local disputes and minor criminal cases such as petty thefts or the destruction of property, their processes and decisions can contravene human rights norms. This remains a concern, even though customary laws are changing to reflect changing social attitudes. Decisions on family law and personal status in particular frequently discriminate against women and customary courts are also not appropriate forums to resolve penal cases of a serious nature, in particular cases of rape or other sexual offences. In some parts of the country, most notably in Southern Sudan, there have been efforts to integrate these often widely respected systems as an official part of the judicial system and, as part of this process, ensure their compliance with fundamental human rights norms</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC65F75E3-AB8E-45D0-8301-FCC465CAD39B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">889</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">910</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7354A798-357D-4247-A5B1-7ABFFA93AD29"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDC98FC47-D2FD-4A63-9D71-ECD36F227D51">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">889</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">894</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7354A798-357D-4247-A5B1-7ABFFA93AD29"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8C7432C0-57D4-49C1-9E6E-16A1A5142546">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">895</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">910</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7354A798-357D-4247-A5B1-7ABFFA93AD29"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Sudanese Pounds</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>