<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3370515" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4C5CF03A-B269-43E0-BEFC-E724EFB31533">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">RUR</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">130000000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeD1E201FF-ABA7-4A58-89B9-4B0F9FDB65AC">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">According to the program of RAO "LIES of Russia" the country will get more than 40 thousand MW of new capacities in the coming 4-5 years. 180 MW have already been added to the unified energy system in May 2006, when TGC-1 has commissioned the first unit of the Pravoberezhnaya CHPP in Saint-Petersburg, which is the first completed construction in the "List of to-be-commissioned priority power objects of the holding". And this is only the beginning - TGC-1 investment program, approved by the Board of Directors in the past year, provides for about twenty other generating assets of the Company to be reconstructed or newly commissioned in the coming decade, with the total estimated reconstruction and construction costs of more than RUR 130 billion. Financing is planned to be mainly provided through own and borrowed funds as well as funds raised with additional shares issue. In this respect, it is a major challenge for us to introduce and comply with the best international and Russian corporate governance practices and standards in order to provide the maximum transparency of the Company, achieve high performance of the management system and, as a result, increase the confidence of potential investors. The power sector of the North-West Region has good traditions and unique experience in addressing these tasks, including owing to the long-term interactions with foreign strategic investors. Since first days of its work TGC-1 has been strictly following the principles of transparency and publicity of its business, social responsibility, and corporate stability. It should be noted thatTQC-1 was one of the first territorial generating companies to receive a high corporate governance rating from Standard &amp; Poor's, as compared with the general level of ratings awarded to the Russian power generating companies - CGS-5</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE3331B3B-0D03-4871-A130-8276F871200E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">737</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">752</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4C5CF03A-B269-43E0-BEFC-E724EFB31533"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode53781C91-FDC2-4971-9BBF-0D74BAA6ACB9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">737</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">740</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4C5CF03A-B269-43E0-BEFC-E724EFB31533"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">RUR</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode2BA7BEB7-49D7-46D9-A461-633EB463D287">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">741</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">752</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4C5CF03A-B269-43E0-BEFC-E724EFB31533"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">130000000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>