<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3371734" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode467B92D1-04E2-4503-B16F-79BB8826BA6C">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Belize dollars</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">38000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeBE6737CE-C50B-4E9F-8A13-FD6CCB8EB56D">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">The new prime minister renounced the Accommodation Agreement, asserting that it was repugnant to the laws of Belize and therefore invalid. Belize then ceased to honor the contractual obligations as asserted by Telemedia. Telemedia repaired to the terms of the arbitration clause and submitted the dispute to arbitration before the LCIA in London. Belize refused to participate in the arbitration proceedings, contending, as it contends now, that the arbitration clause was invalid and that the arbitrators lacked jurisdiction. On March 18, 2009, the arbitral tribunal ruled that the Accommodation Agreement was valid and binding on Belize; that the tribunal had jurisdiction over Telemedia’s claims; and that Belize had breached the accommodation agreement. Belize Soc. Dev. Ltd., 668 F.3d at 728. The arbitral tribunal granted Telemedia declaratory relief, and awarded over 38 million Belize dollars in damages. Id. Two days later, Telemedia assigned the monetary portion of its award to BSDL. Id. In November 2009, BSDL brought suit in the District Court for the District of Columbia to confirm the arbitral award pursuant to section 207 of the Federal Arbitration Act (“FAA”), 9 U.S.C. § 207. Belize moved to stay confirmation of the award pending resolution of related litigation in Belize. The district court obliged; BSDL appealed. We reversed, noting that under the FAA, the stay order “was not in conformity with federal law and international commitments.” Belize Soc. Dev. Ltd., 668 F.3d at 733. We remanded and instructed the district court “to review and grant BSDL’s petition to confirm the Final Award absent a finding that an enumerated exception to enforcement . . . applie[s].” Id. On remand, Belize argued that the district court lacked subject matter jurisdiction over the dispute because it was entitled to sovereign immunity under the Foreign Sovereign Immunities Act (“FSIA”)</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode52CED64C-D09A-4860-BE43-64CA4CE6C3CF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">875</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">900</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode467B92D1-04E2-4503-B16F-79BB8826BA6C"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode532DF2DD-52F0-4F37-B1A0-8C78644FDEEF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">875</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">885</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode467B92D1-04E2-4503-B16F-79BB8826BA6C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">38000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5FDBA9E7-85C3-4552-9022-10850F92270F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">886</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">900</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode467B92D1-04E2-4503-B16F-79BB8826BA6C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Belize dollars</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>