<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3372105" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeA402EE64-BE60-48D4-AD00-BAF9BBF03F3E">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeA40516E2-F18C-49C8-99C9-78EC699AFCB0">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">This calls for what we know as a superheterodyne’ receiver or, as the hams call it more familiarly, a super-het’; a good second bet is a really good tuned radio frequency type, again abbreviated ham-wise to ‘TRF\ Building either of these is a pretty tricky procedure and after you have it all assembled and wired, it still must be ‘aligned’ which, to really' do right, calls for several special instruments. In the long run you’ll have a somewhat mediocre receiver which will cost you about as much as if you had bought a good, standard make, already built and operating. Then too, you can compromise and buy a ‘kit’ where all of the so-called ‘hard work’ has bc;en done for you. Holes are punched and drilled in chassis and panel, coils are wound and roughly aligned etc. It’s still quite a job to assemble, wire and complete the alignment. An experienced ham can do a good job with such a kit in a relatively short time but the beginner should be wary' of tackling it.” “Buying a good, factory-built receiver has several angles also. A really good new one by a reliable manufacturer is going to cost somewhere in the $lof&gt; to $250 price range. Even better ones go up in price from several hundred dollars to a few jobs selling at a thousand or more! Don’t let it scare you though; you are not about to equip ‘Gemini Control* but simply making a start in ham radio. You can do rather well with one of the more modest receivers and if it’s a fairly recent model ol reliable manufacture, it w'ill bring a good trade-in value if and when you want something better later; home-buill jobs arc rarely accepted as trade-ins.”</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEDAC1D7A-23CF-46EF-B27B-BA1175C5400F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1232</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1242</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA402EE64-BE60-48D4-AD00-BAF9BBF03F3E"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeAC7FD0C6-F35A-4AC4-97C5-1A17E498C363">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1232</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1242</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA402EE64-BE60-48D4-AD00-BAF9BBF03F3E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>