<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3372670" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode8C7F0EA4-4D4E-49EE-A024-7F3E2318613C">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Djiboutian Francs</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">400000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode991499B6-72A9-486D-9A30-963377E4DC68">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">At an information meeting organised by opposition parties but prohibited by the Ministry of Interior, numerous demonstrators came to express their discontent over the organisation and progress of the legislative elections, and to the mass arrest of opponents on Monday, 25 February, until late into the night despite the existence of a curfew. Security forces responded to the protest with bullets shooting at demonstrators. Witnesses report ten dead, including Youssouf Mahmoud Ahmed, member of the political party, Union for National Salvation (USN), and Kadir Mahmoud, a high school student. Those severely injured included Abdourahman Barkat God and Abdourahman Souleimane Bechir, both leaders of the MoDel party, and Khalid Mahmoud and Hussein Omar Abar, both high school students. The true figure of those killed or injured however remains unclear as arrests have prevented people from being brought to hospital. Hundreds have been arrested and are presumably being detained in Nagad administrative detention centre. Among them, there are 35 female MoDel militants. Police detaining these women have demanded 400,000 Djiboutian Francs for their release. One of the captives is Saada Abdi Ibrahim, wife of MoDel militant, Abdourahman Barkat God. Saada Abdi Ibrahim is diabetic and remains without medicine. The conditions of her detention therefore raise concern about her well being. Moreover, at least three MoDel followers, Abdourahman Barkat, Souleiman Béchir and Guirreh Medal, have already been remanded by Djiboutian courts and condemned to 3 months of imprisonment at Gabode’s prison for “incitement to insurrection”. These men have been refused the assistance of both a lawyer and a doctor. The main opposition leaders remain under house arrest, in detention or with outstanding proceedings against them. These measures show the absolute and radical nature of the repression of political opposition in Djibouti.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6D8DB178-2EB2-44DA-BAFD-961AF0C5CD6B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1115</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1140</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8C7F0EA4-4D4E-49EE-A024-7F3E2318613C"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode7DF5B3B9-C689-4F88-92C0-6336447F79E9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1115</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1122</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8C7F0EA4-4D4E-49EE-A024-7F3E2318613C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">400000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode817FC871-D056-48EF-A3CA-9EEEAE76AC1D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1123</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1140</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode8C7F0EA4-4D4E-49EE-A024-7F3E2318613C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Djiboutian Francs</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>