<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373169" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode20492B71-B4D4-4820-B5C3-2E97FB57B14E">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Finnish markka</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">35000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode6C106EF9-1544-4E4E-9916-BD4CC76B0BA6">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">During conversion there was a fire on board, but it was extinguished by the shipyard staff. Renamed Sally Albatross, the ship entered service for the new Sally Cruise brand in May 1986. She was mainly used for cruising around the Baltic Sea from Helsinki. In 1987 Rederi Ab Sally was sold to its rivals Effoa and Johnson Line. In January–February 1988 the Sally Albatross was comprehensively rebuilt at Schichau Seebeckwerft, Bremerhaven, Germany, where additional cabin were built on the former upper cardeck, the forward superstructure was built to a more streamlined appearance and smaller changes were made to the bow and other parts of the superstructure. At the same time the ships livery was altered, in addition to the light and dark blue stripes running along the hull black stripes were painted along the windows of the superstructure, giving the ship an even more streamlined appearance. The cost of the reconstruction was 35 million Finnish markka. Fire In January 1990, while docked at the Finnboda Shipyard in Nacka, Sweden, for reconstruction of the ship's restaurants, nightclub and conference facilities, practically the entire superstructure of the ship was damaged beyond repair by a fire which had started from drops of liquid metal sparkling on flammable material. The ships' sprinkler system was turned off for the duration of the docking, fire hydrants were dry and the temporary fire water supply was disconnected. In addition to this the fire watchman left for lunch during the hot work. Due to the danger of gas bottles (oxy-acetylene used in the reconstruction) exploding in the heat, the fire brigade withdrew from the interior of two decks under reconstruction, after having rescued the two crew members that were missing during the initial phase of the fire. Further fire fighting was conducted from the outside and from the decks above and below the reconstruction work</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB55BA1DF-7920-423B-BEA6-B704116EC454">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">934</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">959</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode20492B71-B4D4-4820-B5C3-2E97FB57B14E"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeAF41EB46-653B-43B1-A723-1C86890EA81B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">934</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">944</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode20492B71-B4D4-4820-B5C3-2E97FB57B14E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">35000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0B36AD55-4903-4281-826C-87DB5308C02F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">945</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">959</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode20492B71-B4D4-4820-B5C3-2E97FB57B14E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Finnish markka</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>