<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373612" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode1EF5E011-DC33-4DF0-99A8-4D0AC46E0534">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">drachmas</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeF483136E-980D-4A83-BBAE-A11B858BAF42">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">In the Ptolemaic era a small population of Greeks provided the main cadre of the army. These men provided manpower for the elite guards units and the phalanx that lay at its core. However, the distance of Egypt from Greece caused considerable difficulties as the population of Greeks in Egypt was and remained small. To remedy this problem, the Ptolemies set up military colonies and encouraged settlers to settle in them. In return for these plots of land, the kleruchoi, as they were known, would be obligated to provide military service. Mercenaries were also employed by the Ptolemies, who could afford it due to their wealth. For example, Ptolemy IV paid 1,000 drachmas a day for one distinguished Aetolian officer to serve in his armies. This system gave the Ptolemies more manpower, however they still suffered severe shortages. Despite this lack of manpower, they would not allow native Egyptians to fight in the army proper. The natives would only serve in the navy or as auxiliaries. This changed by the time of Raphia in 217 when the situation became especially dire for the Ptolemies. Their army was far too small to counter the far superior Seleucid force led by the formidable Antiochus III. To counter the larger Seleucid force, the general Sosibius assembled a large army which he trained for the fight to come, and in which he also enrolled 30,000 native Egyptians to serve in the phalanx. These 30,000 picked Egyptians, known as the Machimoi Epilektoi, fought well in the battle, but caused problems later on. The increased status of these Egyptian troops enabled and encouraged them to revolt, which led to a further crippling of the kingdom in the years following Raphia</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode93609E2A-409D-4B76-ACEB-5B13B4923C1E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">660</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">674</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode1EF5E011-DC33-4DF0-99A8-4D0AC46E0534"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5FA9F2CC-F300-4187-A7E3-FD6C2679CAFD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">660</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">665</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode1EF5E011-DC33-4DF0-99A8-4D0AC46E0534"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5632F5AC-4453-405E-BDA6-417C202145CF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">666</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">674</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode1EF5E011-DC33-4DF0-99A8-4D0AC46E0534"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">drachmas</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>