<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373627" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode9F656CB2-9861-45A3-B2A0-6A30ABBFB18C">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">hwan</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">7500000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode2996CFD3-5648-414B-AB04-FD2A23BA9216">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Park failed in winning over the army's Counter-Intelligence Command and the armored Ninth Division, but neither organization reported the plans to higher authorities, allowing the planning to proceed unimpeded. As 1960 drew to a close, moreover, Park began parallel talks outside of his core group, structuring a loose network of supporters for his plan; among those brought in by these talks was Major General Lee Chu-il, with whom Park agreed that once the coup had taken place, the new Army Chief of Staff Chang Do-yong would be placed as head of the Revolutionary Council in order to get the entire army's support. In March 1961, the core group met at the Chungmu-jang Restaurant in Seoul, and fixed the date April 19 for the coup, expecting significant disturbances on that day due to its being the anniversary of the revolution that had overthrown Rhee's regime. Park also secured the financial backing of prominent businessmen, amassing a total of 7.5 million hwan. Finally, on April 10, 1961, Park took the initiative in revealing the details of the plan to Chang himself. Chang's subsequent ambivalent response was decisive in allowing the coup to take place. While he turned down the leadership position offered to him, he neither informed the civilian government of the plan, nor ordered the arrest of the conspirators. This allowed Park to present Chang as an "invisible hand" guiding the organization of the coup. According to Han, this ambivalence was most likely because Chang had calculated that the coup organizers had by this time gathered too much momentum to stop, though this analysis assumes Chang's earlier non-involvement. The date of April 19 passed without the expected disturbances, however, and the planners rescheduled the coup for May 12.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE3AFA2BC-9ACE-44EF-A565-31632C46AF60">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">955</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">971</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9F656CB2-9861-45A3-B2A0-6A30ABBFB18C"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5FD2EE16-6141-4671-8A5F-8BF273D6FF01">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">955</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">966</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9F656CB2-9861-45A3-B2A0-6A30ABBFB18C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">7500000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode77AA47EE-7BE3-46D0-9DBB-8DB7C759BDF8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">967</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">971</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode9F656CB2-9861-45A3-B2A0-6A30ABBFB18C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">hwan</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>