<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373796" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeC8224382-B021-4ABB-9AED-02F38CC19D1E">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Ghana cedis</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">50</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode7B3D76B3-ECAC-48A0-ABEE-BA1F3A0A8B15">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Up to now the editors of Guinea Worm Wrap-Up have, with good reason, warned Ghana repeatedly about the perils of over-confidence or premature declarations of success. We have never before felt as assured about a national milestone of elimination before at least twelve consecutive months of indigenous cases have passed as we do now. And that this should occur in Ghana is especially wondrous, given that country's exceptionally tortuous and delayed arrival at this point in its campaign. The long hoped-for portents were there with the record-breaking 85% reduction in cases between 2007 (3,358 cases) and 2008 (501 cases), the 97% reduction in cases between 2009 (242 cases) and 2010 (8 cases), and the obsessive attention to detecting every case, containing every worm, and tracing every source that Ghana's Guinea Worm Eradication Program has manifest recently. A reward scheme is now operational in all recently endemic districts of Ghana that pays 50 Ghana cedis (~US$36) for reporting a case if the case is contained at a case containment center.  Over the years, Guinea worm disease has been entwined in Ghana's history, ethnology, geology, climatology, economy, traditional beliefs and modem politics. This disease once closed schools in Ghana by preventing so many young scholars from being able to walk. Soon after the program began, Ghana's “stunned” Secretary (minister) for Agriculture wrote the Secretary for Health to plead for help for the many farmers he had just seen suffering from Guinea worm disease during his visit up country to launch the annual maize-purchasing season. And a particularly outrageous outbreak struck hundreds of terrified preschoolers in 2007 less than five weeks before Ghana celebrated its 50th Anniversary of political independence. But after more than 500,000 cases since its inception; over four million cloth filters, more than one million pipe filters, 72,000 liters of ABATE®Larvicide; at least nine ministers of health and nine missed target dates, we are confident that Ghana's Guinea Worm Eradication Program has finally achieved the demise of the worm</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode57CEC71A-8902-4B3E-A200-946E3A9913C8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">954</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">968</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC8224382-B021-4ABB-9AED-02F38CC19D1E"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9FD17BED-5C1D-4B12-8B7F-5C016EDE5106">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">954</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">956</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC8224382-B021-4ABB-9AED-02F38CC19D1E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">50</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode16CED7E2-7FD6-4E6C-ABA7-3F29CF8292B7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">957</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">968</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeC8224382-B021-4ABB-9AED-02F38CC19D1E"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Ghana cedis</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>