<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373323" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode72CA5D63-4294-4372-BDA8-1E2036948B93">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">US dollars</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5100</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeD32FCBFB-A92C-45DF-A022-643A5D329C3C">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">The malu clan are in this case in a partnership, the woman and feminine goods such as pigs and clothes, while from the ai baqa, clan receive wives and give masculine goods. This used to include gold, silver and water buffalo, now replaced by money and cattle. On ceremonial occasions, such as funerals or of the clan house repair, goods between are again malu and ai baqa replaced. However, women rarely leave their clan. In the majority of the Bunak family, a matrilineal system prevails for the succession. The man traditionally moves into the clan of the bride (Matrilocality), where the later children also grow up. The husband has to provide as a mane pou ("new man") his children and wife, but is not considered a family member. He also has no claims or rights over his wife and children, even if he had to pay a high bride price. In 1991 this was about US dollars 5,100. If the wife dies first, the widower must leave the village and even his own children, and return to his old home village. This may also be necessary through certain ceremonies. He is not allowed to take any valuable property, therefore he is dependent on the help of his clan and his family. He also does not receive the support from his own children as a clan. When the woman moves into an ai baqa clan, one speaks of the clipping of the woman from her clan. She is admitted to her husband's clan, where the family forms a new line of lineage (dil), establishing a new malu - ai baqa relationship. The children also belong to the clan of the father. Clans can maintain as much as fifteen malu relationships but there can never be more than three to six dil. They maintain their status in the further course of the mother line</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA8F34D59-0207-434C-99BC-DE72BA7C15C3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">860</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">876</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode72CA5D63-4294-4372-BDA8-1E2036948B93"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode606808EE-02A8-4C73-88AA-3F9423BC6769">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">860</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">870</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode72CA5D63-4294-4372-BDA8-1E2036948B93"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">US dollars</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeBC920FAD-7B4E-4854-B105-70C10B68580D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">871</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">876</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode72CA5D63-4294-4372-BDA8-1E2036948B93"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5100</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>