<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373976" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode7062E71F-71EC-4C6F-8B4E-B42289731304">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">cruzados</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">200</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeBBB4D73F-F1D9-4822-A3C0-4C4DD45671EE">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">In 1604 the Lord President of Munster, Sir Henry Brouncker - at Limerick, ordered all Jesuits from the city and Province, and offered £7 to anyone willing to betray a Jesuit priest to the authorities, and £5 for a Seminarian. Jesuit houses and schools throughout the Province, in the years thereafter, were subject to periodic crackdown and the occasional destruction of schools, imprisonment of teachers and the levying of heavy money penalties on parents are recorded in publications of the time. In 1615-17 the Royal Visitation Books, written up by Thomas Jones, the Anglican Archbishop of Dublin, records the suppression of Jesuit schools at Waterford, Limerick and Galway.. Nevertheless, spite of this occasional persecution, the Jesuits were able to exert a degree of discreet influence within the Province and city. For instance in 1606, largely through their efforts, a Catholic named Christopher Holywood was elected Mayor of the city. . Four years earlier the resident Jesuit had raised a sum of '200 cruzados' for the purpose of founding a hospital in the city, though the project was disrupted by a severe outbreak of plague and repression by the Lord President The principal activities of the Order within the city at this time were devoted to preaching, administration of the sacraments and teaching. The School opened and closed intermittently in or around the area of Castle Lane, near Lahiffy's lane. During demolition work Stones marked I.H.S., 1642 and 1609 were, in the 19th century, found inserted in a wall behind a tan yard near St Mary's Chapel which, according to Lenihan, were thought to mark the site of an early Jesuit School and Oratory. This building, at other times, had also functioned as a dance house and candle factory.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeAE188839-5CCB-4DF6-847C-08CE4B7C8620">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1007</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1019</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7062E71F-71EC-4C6F-8B4E-B42289731304"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode40C17613-B049-457D-9315-BF10E0652504">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1007</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1010</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7062E71F-71EC-4C6F-8B4E-B42289731304"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">200</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC7AFDCFF-48BE-460B-ABDC-28ECA62AC7A8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1011</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1019</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode7062E71F-71EC-4C6F-8B4E-B42289731304"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">cruzados</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>