<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373190" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode6137198F-0AF2-4566-AF5D-60BAC8FA0FBF">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">NT$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode73737809-343B-49E4-9592-713303CE1333">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">In addition, bassist Doris Yeh has endorsed the Awakening Foundation, a women's rights organization in Taiwan. In February 2009, Lim and Yeh protested with human rights activists at the Taipei zoo panda exhibit, which symbolizes China's attempts to establish soft power relations with Taiwan. In August 2009, many aboriginal villages in Taiwan were heavily damaged by Typhoon Morakot, and Chthonic donated the proceeds from two concerts to an aboriginal organization. Lim personally carried supplies into the disaster areas. In March 2011, after the northeastern Japan earthquake, Chthonic raised and donated over one million NT$ for relief efforts. During Chthonic's 2011 North American tour, they received a threatening letter from unknown Chinese persons. The band is also banned in parts of China for their political views. The band's lyrics are often based on the defiant spirit of early Taiwanese colonizers, fictional wars between aboriginal gods and Han Chinese gods, Taiwanese folklore and mythology, historical events such as the Wushe Incident and the February 28 Incident, and the formation of the Takasago Volunteers. Prior to the album Seediq Bale most of the band's lyrics were written in Classical Chinese, which is rarely used in contemporary Chinese or Taiwanese music, and sung with Mandarin pronunciation. Starting with the album Mirror of Retribution the lyrics are written and sung in Taiwanese Hokkien. Some songs may also include verses in Japanese, Mandarin Chinese, or Formosan languages. Starting with Seediq Bale the band has released alternate versions of their albums for the international market, with some songs remixed with English lyrics</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode4E17BD64-DB61-43D2-9D36-FEDEFD3C5D53">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">614</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">629</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6137198F-0AF2-4566-AF5D-60BAC8FA0FBF"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3986A7D0-EDD9-471A-A770-9ECA8A21CB88">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">614</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">625</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6137198F-0AF2-4566-AF5D-60BAC8FA0FBF"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDC1927AB-81FF-4EE1-BA14-BF20B4E42870">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">626</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">629</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode6137198F-0AF2-4566-AF5D-60BAC8FA0FBF"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">NT$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>