<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373474" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode2D1F3916-4747-49C5-9F43-8CED800A7EC3">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">German gold marks</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2600000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeAC8089CF-BDEA-4D71-8F3A-7463AB10091E">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">An earlier opening was not possible due to the Brenz Railway clause of 21 February 1861, which pledged Württemberg not to build a rail link for twelve years between the Stuttgart-Nördlingen railway (Rems Railway/Ries Railway) and Ulm, otherwise the route from Nördlingen to Lake Constance would have been shorter via Württemberg than via the Ludwig South-North Railway through Bavaria. On 24 January 1877, the footbridge that crossed the station and connected it to the Zum Russischen Hof hotel was completed; its construction had started in July 1875. In August 1877, the Blaubeurer-Tor bridge was opened across the tracks to the north of the station, replacing the existing Karlstraße level crossing. The bridge was an iron truss bridge, 225.6 metres long and ten metres wide. In October 1986, it was demolished and replaced by the Ludwig Erhard bridge opened on 26 October 1989. In 1879, the post office located next to the station, was rebuilt and extended. Ulm Stuttgarter Tor station, north of the inner city, which today is called Ulm Ost (east), opened on the Brenz Railway on 20 September 1886. The second phase of expansion of the station began in 1888 and continued until 1891, involving the expenditure of 2.6 million German gold marks. The existing eastern storage sidings between Wilhelmstrasse and the Fils Valley Railway to the north-east of Ulm station, which still exist, were opened in 1888. On 26 March 1889, electric light was installed at the station, using electricity from the station’s own steam-powered, power plant on Schillerstraße. The station building was rebuilt again from 1889 to 1890. The cast-iron arches were replaced by a lobby that was 42 metres long and eight metres wide and was used for the ticket office. In 1891, the platform underpass was built, replacing the existing pedestrian level crossings. In the same year, at the end of the second construction phase, Ulm station had 22 tracks, four of which were used for passengers, five for freight and 13 for shunting.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode6183D29C-6568-476A-B60C-26ECD475B825">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1218</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1247</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2D1F3916-4747-49C5-9F43-8CED800A7EC3"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8D141F9B-3EF9-4A09-ABF6-5B1E8FA70F02">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1218</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1229</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2D1F3916-4747-49C5-9F43-8CED800A7EC3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2600000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0C27FF67-61AA-4CC9-9903-7528A9C4253C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1230</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1247</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode2D1F3916-4747-49C5-9F43-8CED800A7EC3"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">German gold marks</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>