<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373461" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeD72D79E0-18F4-479C-8B66-A756907BB525">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">£</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeA963450C-C7D9-43F0-BA0F-690A0292895F">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Ramsey moved to Arsenal in 2008 in a £5 million deal, where he quickly gained first-team experience. However, his career stalled significantly after he suffered a broken leg in a match against Stoke City in February 2010. After two loan spells away from Arsenal, he returned to full fitness and re-established himself as a regular starter during the 2011–12 season. Ramsey was a key player for Arsenal in the 2013–14 campaign, scoring 16 goals in all competitions, including the winner in the 2014 FA Cup Final against Hull City. He also played in the 2015 FA Cup Final, which Arsenal won, and scored a second FA Cup winning goal in 2017. On 1 July 2019, he joined Juventus after having signed a pre-contractual agreement, winning the league title during his first season. Ramsey made his full international debut for Wales in 2008 and was part of their UEFA Euro 2016 campaign, where he helped his nation to the semi-finals and was included in the Team of the Tournament. He also represented Great Britain at the 2012 Olympics. Early life As a child, Ramsey attended Ysgol Gyfun Cwm Rhymni (Rhymney Valley Comprehensive School) in Caerphilly County Borough. Ramsey's first introduction to football was at the age of nine, when he attended an Urdd training session at Caerphilly. Before turning to football, he was a keen rugby player and athlete. As a schoolboy he played as a winger for Caerphilly R.F.C.s youth development programme, where he was approached by scouts from rugby league side St. Helens after playing in a youth match against them but had already been signed by Cardiff City's youth academy. Ramsey was Welsh Schools' Athletic Association pentathlon champion in 2005 and was ranked 4th in Great Britain in the under 17 age group in 2006. He lived with his parents, Marlene and Kevin, and his brother, Josh, until moving to London where he was housemates with former Cardiff City teammate, Chris Gunter, who was then playing for Tottenham Hotspur</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCEDE0305-B760-46CD-A135-109B5801FCAA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">37</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">47</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD72D79E0-18F4-479C-8B66-A756907BB525"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode728EA7B9-D6F0-49A5-90D1-966C59E5AFC7">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">37</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">38</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD72D79E0-18F4-479C-8B66-A756907BB525"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">£</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode343B5BFC-7306-4345-8C05-4C1AFA0B6DE8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">38</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">47</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD72D79E0-18F4-479C-8B66-A756907BB525"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>