<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373214" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode5F210ADE-68F8-4ACA-A311-472F30F6EB62">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">drachmas</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">100000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode11E9D03D-3222-4C12-B835-5585E28F7B8D">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Cases of non-transparent public deals and corruption allegedly occurred at the time, given the lack of democratic checks and balances and the absence of a free press. One such event is associated with the regime's tourism minister, Ioannis Ladas. During his administration, several low-interest loans, amortized over a twenty-year period, were issued for tourist development. This fostered the erection of a multitude of hotels, sometimes in non-tourist areas, and with no underlying business rationale. Several such hotels were abandoned unfinished as soon as the loans were secured, and their remains still dot the Greek countryside. These questionable loans are referred to as Thalassodania (Θαλασσοδάνεια, 'loans of the sea'), to indicate the loose terms under which they were granted. Another contested policy of the regime was the writing-off of agricultural loans, up to a value of 100,000 drachmas, to farmers. This has been attributed to an attempt by Papadopoulos to gain public support for his regime. Italian connection At the time, the Italian far right was very impressed with the methods of Papadopoulos and his junta. In April 1968, Papadopoulos invited fifty members of the Italian far right on a Greek tour, to demonstrate the junta's methods. Invitees included Stefano Delle Chiaie and members of Ordine Nuovo, Avanguardia Nazionale, Europa Civiltà, and FUAN-La Caravella. (cf Frattini, Entity, 2004, p. 304) The Italians were impressed. Upon returning to their country, they escalated their political violence, embarking on a terror campaign of bombings and other violence which killed and injured hundreds. Afterwards, the right-wing instigators of this violence blamed the communists.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCD80E46F-BE6C-46DF-8601-0A0AAD9CF3B9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">889</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">905</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5F210ADE-68F8-4ACA-A311-472F30F6EB62"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode91898193-EE70-4AC8-8B7E-D052853FF6AC">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">889</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">896</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5F210ADE-68F8-4ACA-A311-472F30F6EB62"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">100000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE1FFA7D0-1E86-4F34-AD13-C7E8C77B43A4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">897</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">905</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5F210ADE-68F8-4ACA-A311-472F30F6EB62"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">drachmas</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>