<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3373381" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeA70A68FC-F35D-4B6B-A4C5-EEE8CB1A2953">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">NOK</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">52800000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode05780232-989E-465E-A2CE-CE7585C3881F">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Cross-country skiing was dominated by Norway; Marit Bjørgen won four gold and one silver, while Petter Northug won 3 gold and two silver. Canada, with Devon Kershaw and Alex Harvey took its first-ever victory with gold in the men's team sprint. Austria dominated the ski jumping, winning all five events: Thomas Morgenstern took three golds and one silver, Gregor Schlierenzauer won three golds, and Daniela Iraschko won the women's event. In the Nordic combined, Germany took four of the six individual medals, but lost both relays to Austria. Organization In 2002, the Association for the Promotion of Skiing and Oslo Municipality started the process of applying for the FIS Nordic World Ski Championships 2009. The city council decided to grant NOK 52.8 million to upgrade Holmenkollen, including Holmenkollbakken, for the 2009 World Championships. Oslo lost the vote in the International Ski Federation (FIS) against Liberec, Czech Republic, on 4 June 2004. The Norwegian Ski Federation subsequently stated that they would apply for the 2011 World Championships. The Association for the Promotion of Skiing stated that they wanted a new hill in Rødkleiva instead of expanding the existing ski flying hill in Vikersund, Vikersundbakken. Holmenkollbakken would then be used for the last time during as a large hill during the 2011 World Championships, and would then converted to a normal hill. In May 2005, the general assembly of the Norwegian Ski Federation voted to build a new ski flying and normal hill in Rødkleiva ahead of the 2011 World Championships. Following Vikersundbakken being awarded the FIS Ski-Flying World Championships 2012 in 2008, the general assembly of the Norwegian Ski Federation that year decided to terminate the plans for a ski flying hill in Rødkleiva</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE85357C9-18DF-42AC-9DDF-39C78B706B53">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">748</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">764</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA70A68FC-F35D-4B6B-A4C5-EEE8CB1A2953"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0E6A50F0-3842-452A-A56B-D7A98CAD6F1D">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">748</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">751</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA70A68FC-F35D-4B6B-A4C5-EEE8CB1A2953"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">NOK</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8F62777D-C62B-45C1-A19C-89B2142E6693">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">752</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">764</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeA70A68FC-F35D-4B6B-A4C5-EEE8CB1A2953"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">52800000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>