<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374563" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE7AA1C96-102C-4F11-8FFB-561413C1BD68">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Belgian Francs</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">218500</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEDF5DBF-1D37-4697-AE99-6C3D4D45D1FC">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">In the autumn of 1940, the Simexco firm was established by GRU officer Anatoly Gurevich. The firm was officially registered by March 1941, when it opened in two offices at 192 Rue Royale in Brussels. Simexco was established as a replacement cover organisation when the Brussels rain-ware export company known as the Foreign Excellent Raincoat Company was seized after the occupation of Brussels in 17 May 1940. Simexco was established as a genuine business with an absolutely firm legal status that was recognised as conservative in its approach by German service departments. On the recommendation of the administrative staff at the Abwehr IIIF. Ast. military command, it even been granted long distance, telegram communication, telephone and fax facilities by the German authorities that ensbled regular and privileged way to enable Trepper and Gurevich to communicate. Gurevich became a director of the business. According to the article of incorporation, the main investor was Nazarine Drailly, a Belgian communist and informer, who invested 218,500 Belgian Francs in the firm. Drailly was fully aware of the companies true purpose and actively took part in operations. Drailly's brother, Charles Drailly, a banker, became a commercial director of the firm in March 1941. He was almost certainly aware of the nature of the firm, but maintained his distance in his role as a director, never taking part in espionage operations. Margarete Barcza who lived with Gurevich, found additional shareholders amongst her bridge club. These shareholders were Florida nightclub owner, Robert Christen, travelling salesman Jean Passelecq, publisher Henri de Ryck and friend of Gurevich, Henri Seghers who owned a cigarette factory.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC27E4C44-A255-4748-B78A-68ED7A187869">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1046</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1068</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE7AA1C96-102C-4F11-8FFB-561413C1BD68"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeDD8EC5A1-FE13-499F-93EA-04132FADEAE1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1046</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1053</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE7AA1C96-102C-4F11-8FFB-561413C1BD68"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">218500</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode03044F38-B571-4308-B950-F98666D38944">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1054</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1068</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE7AA1C96-102C-4F11-8FFB-561413C1BD68"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Belgian Francs</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>