<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374676" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0E47D0B-0C87-4E8C-8F2E-D948938758D2">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">27600</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode03F92D02-0B52-4DAD-8708-262AC7CFDB73">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">2300</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode38FC8126-CEC6-4B83-8E8D-3B377B7E8405">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">This Instrument Prepared By: Middle Tennessee State University 1301 East Main St. Murfreesboro, Tn 37132 This Lease, entered into as of this___________day of December, 2007, made by and between College Heights Chapel, Inc. hereinafter called the Lessee, and the State University and Community College System of Tennessee hereinafter called the State. WITNESSETH: 1. LOCATION: The State hereby leases unto the Lessee those certain premises with the appurtenances situated in the 1601 E. Main St. and 1602 County of Rutherford_______ , City of Murfreesboro , located at Elrod St.________ 2. DESCRIPTION: The premises above are more particularly described as follows: Approximately 1.6 acres of land with improvements (a church building and house) located at 1601 East Main St. and 1602 Elrod St., Murfreesboro, Tn and further identified as Tax Map 0900, Parcels 6 and 7. 3. USE: The above described premises will be used by the Lessee for the purpose of a church facility and for no other purpose whatsoever. In using the premises, the Lessee shall comply with all federal, state, and local laws and rules and regulations, as well as the policies of the Tennessee Board of Regents. 4. TERM: The term of this lease shall Commence on cl°s'n8 date of the sale of the and shall Continue 15 months front premises described above to                         Date of Closing, the State hereinafter referred to as the “Date of Closing”.                           _________________________________ with such rights of termination as are hereinafter set forth. If the date of occupancy is other than the commencement date, then the rental period shall begin with the date of occupancy, provided that the rental period shall begin no later than thirty (30) days after the space is made available to the Lessee in accordance with the conditions of this lease. 5. RENTAL: The Lessee agrees to pay to the State as rent for said premises the sum of: Annual rent of $_____27,600_____, payable in installments of $    2,300 per month Rental shall be payable in advance as follows. Rental shall be paid to State at the address specified in Paragraph 8, or to such other address as the State may designate by a notice in writing. 6. TERMINATION:  A.  FOR CONVENIENCE: State may terminate this lease at any time effective on or after Date of Closing by giving written notice to the Lessee at least 120 days prior to the date when such termination becomes effective. Lessee may terminate this lease at any time effective on or after Date of Closing by giving written notice to the State at least 30 days prior to the date when such termination becomes effective. B.  FOR CAUSE: The State may in its sole discretion immediately terminate this lease and re-enter and take possession of premises at any time for any of the following causes: (a) Failure to disclose any conflict or potential conflict of interest existing at the date of this lease or hereafter created; and (b) Any other breach of the terms of this lease by Lessee which is not adequately remedied within twenty (20) days of the mailing of written notices thereof to Lessee. 7. ABANDONMENT: Lessee must notify the State in writing of any planned absence from the premises in excess of 30 consecutive days. If Lessee is absent from the premises in excess of 30 consecutive days without notifying the State, the State may treat the premises as abandoned and shall have the right to terminate the lease and re-enter and take the premises. In addition, the State shall have the right to take possession of any contents located in the premises at the time of termination. The State shall hold said contents for the benefit of the Lessee for an additional 30 days. If Lessee has not claimed said contents within 30 days of termination, the State may sell said contents and apply the proceeds of the sale to any amounts due and owing to the State by Lessee. 8. NOTICES: All Notices herein provided to be given, or which may be given, by either party to the other, shall be deemed to have been fully given when made in writing and deposited in the United States mail, certified and postage prepaid, and addressed as follows: To the Mr. Jack Weatherford Lessee at: 820 East Main St Murfreesboro, Tn 37130 To the   Middle Tennessee State State    University at:      1301 East Main St. Murfreesboro, TN 37132 Attn: Mike Gower 9. ASSIGNMENT AND SUBLETTING: The Lessee shall not assign or sublet all or any part of the leased premises without the written consent of the State. 10. INSPECTION: The State reserves the right to enter and inspect the leased premises, at reasonable times, and to render services and make any necessary repairs to the premises. 11. ALTERATIONS: The Lessee shall make no changes or alterations in the building located on said premises without the written consent of the State. In the event that alterations are made, except as otherwise agreed upon in writing, the Lessee will, at its own expense, upon the expiration of the term hereby created or extension thereof or upon termination of the lease for any reason, restore the building to the identical conditions as when entered upon the lease. 12. SURRENDER OF POSSESSION: Upon termination or expiration of this lease, the Lessee will peaceably surrender to the State the leased premises in as good order and condition as when received, reasonable use and wear thereof excepted. Upon termination, 9:55 AM 18-Dec-07 C0 8 ~ 0 6 1 1 the State may recover from Lessee an amount equal to the value of any damage to the premises beyond reasonable wear and tear. 13. QUIET POSSESSION: The State agrees that the Lessee shall at all times during the existence of this lease peaceably and quietly have, hold and enjoy the leased premises, without suit, trouble or hindrance from the Lessor, or any person claiming under the State, provided that Lessee is in compliance with its obligations and keeps and performs the covenants contained herein. 14. REPAIR AND MAINTENANCE: The State shall make all repairs and renewals necessary or advisable to keep said premises, both inside and outside, and all additions thereto, from deteriorating in value or condition. 15. DESTRUCTION: If the leased premises are totally destroyed by fire or other casualty, this lease shall terminate. If such casualty shall render ten (10) percent or less of the floor space of the leased premises unusable for the purpose intended, State shall effect restoration of the premises as quickly as is reasonably possible. In the event such casualty shall render more than ten (10) percent of such floor space unusable but not constitute total destruction, at its option, either party may terminate this lease. In the event of any such destruction other than total, where the lease has not been terminated as herein provided, the State shall diligently prosecute the repair of said premises. In the event the Lessee remains in possession of said premises though partially destroyed, the rental as herein provided shall be reduced by the same ratio as the net square feet the Lessee is precluded from occupying bears to the total net square feet in the leased premises. "Net square feet" shall mean actual inside dimensions. 16. LIABILITY: Lessee covenants and agrees to indemnify, protect, and save harmless the State against and from all claims, demands, damages, suits, or causes of action whatsoever asserted by any person, firm, or corporation arising out of or in any way connected with the use and occupancy of the leased premises by Lessee, and that Lessee will reimburse the State for all costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, which may be incurred by the State in connection with any such claims, demands, causes of action, or suits. Any claim alleging personal injury or property damage resulting from the negligence of the State, its employees or officials, shall be filed with the Claims Commission of the State of Tennessee for disposition in accordance with state law. Damages recoverable against the State shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Commission. 17. UTILITIES: The State shall be responsible for furnishing the following utilities: none Lessee shall be responsible for payment of all other utilities. 18. TIME OF ESSENCE: Time is of the essence of this lease, and the terms and provisions of this lease shall extend to and be binding upon and inure to the benefit of the heirs, executors, administrators, successors and assigns to the respective parties hereto. 19. HOLDING OVER: In the event the Lessee remains in possession of the premises after the expiration of the lease term, or any extension thereof, this lease shall be automatically 12:27 PM 20-Dec-07 C08-0S11 extended on a month to month basis, subject to thirty (30) days termination by either party, and otherwise on the terms and conditions herein specified, so far as applicable. 20. Prior to the execution of this lease, the special provisions which are described below and/or attached hereto and incorporated by reference were agreed upon. The Lessee shall be responsible for all utilities, custodial services and minor interior and exterior maintenance such as light bulb replacement, small plumbing repairs and lawn care. The Lessee fully understands that this lease is not binding except and until after the Date of Closing and all appropriate State officials’ signatures have been obtained, and the fully executed document returned to the Lessee. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, this lease has been executed by the parties hereto: Title: President STATE Middle Tennessee State University Name: ■ Jaeic O. Weatherford BY: fy.. .   77'/-,._________ Charles Manning, Chari cel for £^&lt;4 Tennessee Board of Regents Title: Secretary____________________________ BY: (N/R)__________ Commissioner of Finance and Administration Approved as to form and legality: (N/R)_______________________________ Attorney General BY: (N/R)____________________________ Governor 9:55 AM 18-Dec-07</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD404C06D-4814-4771-8891-7BCBF21497D5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1947</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1948</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0E47D0B-0C87-4E8C-8F2E-D948938758D2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3AC8EFC6-41E4-454E-ADBB-411B1F9914FA">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1947</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1959</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0E47D0B-0C87-4E8C-8F2E-D948938758D2"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeCDBBB355-6E3D-4BFC-8E8A-6A96050D686B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1953</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1959</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0E47D0B-0C87-4E8C-8F2E-D948938758D2"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">27600</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode72061203-1FC0-470C-8216-51FC6F0E6E44">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1993</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2003</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode03F92D02-0B52-4DAD-8708-262AC7CFDB73"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode14F8B492-5E6A-4BEE-A6FE-EA959E083AA8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1993</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1994</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode03F92D02-0B52-4DAD-8708-262AC7CFDB73"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode1F5324DD-F9CC-486A-B69E-658200A03B2E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1998</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2003</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode03F92D02-0B52-4DAD-8708-262AC7CFDB73"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">2300</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>