<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374349" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeB482A5C9-9993-4DF1-BCFC-27571863F799">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">Malayan dollars</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">177135</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode7BC42813-8DB6-43D8-951F-F2B7EEC38DFF">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">During its glory days, the hall was filled by the Chinese community that gathered for news, to participate in cultural programs or to watch stage performances. During World War II, it was a place where people sought refuge and aid, and later in the 1950s, after independence, members of the hall played significant roles in encouraging the Chinese community to apply for citizenship. In the early twentieth century, many Chinese retained a close attachment to mainland China and during World War II, they even collected money to fund China’s war against Japan. But after the war, the communities felt there was a need to change the perception of the Chinese community towards the then Malaya and to create sense of belonging. The hall played important role in this social movement. Construction of the building started in 1926 and it was completed only in 1935. The building has a touch of Asian architectural features with its dome and some of the detailing. The budget was 177,135 Malayan dollars. Police Co-operative Building Kuala Lumpur, 1959 A 200-metre walk away from the KLSCAH, the Police Co-operative Building, known today as Bangunan Koperasi Polis, is an experiment by the Federation of Malaya Police Co-operative Thrift &amp; Loan Society Ltd. of investment in real estate and took into consideration the high demand for good office space in the fast developing federal capital. The building stands on a site of 17,000 square feet, and is bounded on one side by Sultan Suleiman Road and on two sides by Kampung Attap Road. It is a thirteen storeys high and comprises a basement, ground floor, eleven typical upper floors and a double storeyed penthouse . Reinforced concrete was used throughout the structure. The width of the typical floor plan was kept to a desirable minimum in order to obtain natural lighting conditions from the windows which are all placed roughly due north or south. The height of the building is approximately 155 ft</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5CC44551-316C-4B41-AA86-91B7FBD5837E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">975</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">998</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeB482A5C9-9993-4DF1-BCFC-27571863F799"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB8A7C805-4999-48BC-BC8A-D7FEBAFF3C70">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">975</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">982</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeB482A5C9-9993-4DF1-BCFC-27571863F799"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">177135</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA0E69E2F-F1B2-49FA-BA25-1EEBBEF59F28">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">983</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">998</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeB482A5C9-9993-4DF1-BCFC-27571863F799"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">Malayan dollars</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>