<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374680" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode690F9A37-B1B5-4364-A92D-72A1E74E84D8">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">dollars</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1100000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode194C3A11-4CDC-4693-9AD5-48AEAEB58CD0">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">1100000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode09E25D13-DCED-4261-9F6B-ECEA27442083">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">20000001</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode958E0650-7414-42E1-B8BB-169F0F634A28">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">20000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeD54521D4-DACB-4358-8AB2-4D4D5ECB659C">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">15000001</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode5415A2FE-5E98-4D4E-AA18-167E84D4648D">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">15000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode871C47C0-BBA3-4DFB-A011-F3AEEBA46201">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">10000001</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode23A0F015-AFF8-431B-B599-500B1C92F287">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">10000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode38C83791-C99A-4D5D-A984-022A3226CAB4">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">6000001</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeB1D5A3FB-337D-4449-8179-39743A578795">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">RFP-1483 CONTRACT BETWEEN , VOLUNTEER STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND FIFTH THIRD BANK This Contract, by and between Volunteer State Community College, hereinafter referred to as the “Institution” and Fifth Third Bank, hereinafter referred to as the “Contractor,” is for the provision of Procurement Card Services, as further defined in the "SCOPE OF SERVICES." The Contractor is a for Profit Corporation. The Contractor’s address is: 424 Church Street Nashville, TN 37219 The Contractor’s place of incorporation or organization is Cincinnati, Ohio A. SCOPE OF SERVICES: A.1. Volunteer State Community College, a Tennessee Board of Regents Institution, shall obtain the services of a web-based procurement card program to process routine purchases and payment of goods. A.2. The Contractor shall provide procurement cards, which have been customized per the Institution’s requirements, including, but not limited to, artwork, logos and colors. A.3. All procurement cards will be requested and received by the Director of Purchasing and Contracts to be distributed to Institution employees. All procurement cards will be provided by a traceable signature delivery system. The procurement card monthly credit limit will not exceed the maximum balance as authorized by the Institution upon written, set up parameters. Both the Contractor and the Institution shall monitor the maximum balance. A.4. The Contractor shall adhere to a consistent billing and payment cycle with the Institution’s billing cut-offdate to be the 27th of each month. A.5. The Contractor shall provide a detailed summary statement including but not limited to the following reports: ■   Monthly Individual Procurement Cardholder Statement ■   Monthly Master Billing Statement ■  Vendor Analysis Report A.6.    Contractor shall provide a method to restrict the purchase of certain merchant category codes, such as gas stations, hotels, entertainment, liquor stores, etc. Additional merchant category codes may also be restricted during the term of this Contract, by Institution, upon written notice to the Contractor. A. 7.    In addition, Contractor shall provide all other items/services identified in Attachment 6.4 of Institution’s Request for Proposal and Section 3 of the Contractor’s Proposal response. B.    CONTRACT TERM: B.1. Contract Term. This Contract shall be effective for the period commencing on July 1, 2008 and ending on June 30, 2009. The Institution shall have no obligation for services rendered by the Contractor which are not performed within the specified period. B. 2.    Term Extension. The Institution reserves the right to extend this Contract for an additional period or periods of time representing increments of no more than one year and a total contract term of no more than five (5) years, provided that the Institution notifies the Contractor in writing of its intention to do so at least thirty (30) days prior to the contract expiration date. An extension of the term of this Contract will be effected through an amendment to the Contract. If the extension of the Contract necessitates additional funding beyond that which was included in the original Contract, the increase in the Institution’s maximum liability will also be effected through an amendment to the Contract and shall be based upon rates provided for in the original contract. C.    PAYMENT TERMS AND CONDITIONS: C.1. Maximum Liability. In no event shall the maximum liability of the Institution under this Contract exceed one million, one hundred thousand dollars ($1,100,000.00) annually. The maximum liability represents available funds for payment to the Contractor and does not guarantee payment of any such funds to the Contractor under this Contract. C.2. Compensation Firm. The Maximum Liability of the Institution under this Contract is firm for the duration of the Contract and is not subject to escalation for any reason unless amended. C.3. Payment Methodology. The Contractor shall submit monthly invoices, in form and substance acceptable to the Institution with all of the necessary supporting documentation, prior to any payment. Such invoices shall be submitted for transactions that are incurred on the procurement cards for the period represented on the invoice. Institution shall pay all charges in full thirty (30) days from the receipt of the invoice. C.4. Travel Compensation. The Contractor shall not be compensated or reimbursed for travel, meals, or lodging. C.5. Payment of Invoice. The payment of the invoice by the Institution shall not prejudice the Institution's right to object to or question any invoice or matter in relation thereto. C.6. Disputed Charges. Charges that are later determined to be fraudulent will be credited back to the Institution by the Contractor. C.7.    Potential Payments to Institution for its administrative services are as follows: SPEND LEVELS PAYMENT 30/25 TERMS 30/15 $1,000,000 - $3,000,000 0.45% 0.55% $3,000,000 - $6,000,000 0.55% 0.65% $6,000,001 -$10,000,000 0.65% 0.75% $10,000,001 -$15,000,000 0.75% 0.85% $15,000,001 -$20,000,000 0.85% 0.95% $20,000,001 - Greater 0.95% 1.05% Administrative payment is based on meeting a qualifying threshold of $1,000,000 in annual (calendar) net spend. D. STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS: D.1. Required Approvals. The Institution is not bound by this Contract until it is approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee laws and regulations. D.2. Modification and Amendment. This Contract may be modified only by a written amendment executed by all parties hereto and approved by the appropriate officials in accordance with applicable Tennessee laws and regulations. D.3. Ethnicity. This Contract shall not be executed until the Contractor has completed the Minority/Ethnicity Form. D.4. Termination for Convenience. The Institution may terminate this Contract without cause for any reason. Said termination shall not be deemed a Breach of Contract by the Institution. The Institution shall give the Contractor at least ninety (90) days written notice before the effective termination date. The Contractor shall be entitled to receive payment for charges incurred on procurement cards through the effective date of termination. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to any actual general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. D.5. Termination for Cause. If the Contractor fails to properly perform its obligations under this Contract in a timely or proper manner, or if the Contractor violates any terms of this Contract, the Institution shall have the right to immediately terminate the Contract and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for completed services. Notwithstanding the above, the Contractor shall not be relieved of liability to the Institution for damages sustained by virtue of any breach of this Contract by the Contractor. D.6. Subcontracting. The Contractor shall not assign this Contract or enter into a subcontract for any of the services performed under this Contract without obtaining the prior written approval of the Institution. If such subcontracts are approved by the Institution, they shall contain, at a minimum, sections of this Contract pertaining to "Conflicts of Interest" and "Nondiscrimination" Notwithstanding any use of approved subcontractors, the Contractor shall be the prime contractor and shall be responsible for all work performed. D.7. Conflicts of Interest. The Contractor warrants that no part of the total Contract Amount shall be paid directly or indirectly to an employee or official of the State of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as an officer, agent, employee, subcontractor, or consultant to the Contractor in connection with any work contemplated or performed relative to this Contract. D.8. Nondiscrimination. The Contractor hereby agrees, warrants, and assures that no person shall be excluded from participation in, be denied benefits of, or be otherwise subjected to discrimination in the performance of this Contract or in the employment practices of the Contractor on the grounds of disability, age, race, color, religion, sex, veteran status, national origin, or any other classification protected by Federal, or Tennessee constitutional or statutory law. The Contractor shall, upon request, show proof of such nondiscrimination and shall post in conspicuous places, available to all employees and applicants, notices of nondiscrimination. D.9. Records. The Contractor shall maintain documentation for all charges against the Institution under this Contract. The books, records, and documents of the Contractor, insofar as they relate to work performed or money received under this Contract, shall be maintained for a period of three (3) full years from the date of the final payment and shall be subject to audit at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice by the Institution, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. The financial statements shall be prepared in accordance with generally accepted accounting principles. D.10. Monitoring. The Contractor’s activities conducted and records maintained pursuant to this Contract shall be subject to monitoring and evaluation by the Institution, the Comptroller of the Treasury, or their duly appointed representatives. D.11. Progress Reports. The Contractor shall submit brief, periodic, progress reports to the Institution as requested. In addition, Contractor shall provide all other reports identified in Attachment 6.4 of Institution’s Request for Proposal and Attachment 5 of the Contractor’s Proposal response. D.12. Strict Performance. Failure bv anv partv to this Contract to insist in anv one or more cases upon the strict performance of any of the terms, covenants, conditions, or provisions of this Contract shall not be construed as a waiver or relinquishment of any such term, covenant, condition, or provision. No term or condition of this Contract shall be held to be waived, modified, or deleted except by a written amendment signed by the parties hereto. D.13. Independent Contractor. The parties hereto, in the performance of this Contract, shall not act as employees, partners, joint venturers, or associates of one another. It is expressly acknowledged by the  parties hereto that the parties are independent contracting entities and that nothing in this Contract shall be construed to create an employer/employee relationship or to allow either to exercise control or direction over the manner or method by which the other transacts its business affairs or provides its usual services. The employees or agents of one party shall not be deemed or construed to be the employees or agents of the other party for any purpose whatsoever. The Contractor, being an independent contractor and not an employee of the Institution, agrees to carry adequate public liability and other appropriate forms of insurance, on the Contractor’s employees, and to pay all applicable taxes incident to this Contract. D.14. Institution Liability. The Institution shall have no liability except as specifically provided in this Contract. D.15. Force Maieure. The obligations of the parties to this contract are subject to prevention by causes beyond the parties’ control that could not be avoided by the exercise of due care including, but not limited to, acts of God, riots, wars, epidemics or any other similar cause. D.16. Institution and Federal Compliance. The Contractor shall comolv with all aoblicable State and Federal laws and regulations, including Institution policies and guidelines in the performance of this Contract. D.17. Governing Law. This Contract shall be qoverned by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Tennessee. The Contractor agrees that it will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Tennessee Claims Commission in actions that may arise under this Contract. The Contractor acknowledges and agrees that any rights or claims against the Institution or its employees hereunder, and any remedies arising therefrom, shall be subject to and limited to those rights and remedies, if any, available under Tennessee Code Annotated, Sections 9-8-101 through 9-8-407. D.18. Completeness. This Contract is comolete and contains the entire understanding between the oarties relating to the subject matter contained herein, including all the terms and conditions of the parties’ agreement. This Contract supersedes any and all prior understandings, representations, negotiations, and agreements between the parties relating hereto, whether written or oral. D.19. Severability. If anv terms and conditions of this Contract are held to be invalid or unenforceable as a matter of law, the other terms and conditions hereof shall not be affected thereby and shall remain in full force and effect. To this end, the terms and conditions of this Contract are declared severable. D.20. Headings. Section headings of this Contract are for reference purposes only and shall not be construed as part of this Contract. E. SPECIAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS: E.1. Communications and Contacts. The Institution: Terry McGovern, Director of Purchasing and Contracts Volunteer State Community College 1480 Nashville Pike, Gallatin, TN 37066 615-230-3352 615-230-3515 The Contractor: Tom Miles, AVP Treasury Management Fifth Third Bank 424 Church Street, Nashville, TN 37219 615-687-3004 615-687-3090 All instructions, notices, consents, demands, or other communications shall be sent in a manner that verifies proof of delivery. Any communication by facsimile transmission shall also be sent by United States mail on the same date of the facsimile transmission. Changes to the Contract shall not be effective until agreed to, in writing, by both parties. E.2. Subject to Funds Availability. The Contract is subject to the appropriation and availability of Institution and/or Federal funds. In the event that the funds are not appropriated or are otherwise unavailable, the Institution reserves the right to terminate the Contract upon written notice to the Contractor. Said termination shall not be deemed a breach of Contract by the Institution. Upon receipt of the written notice, the Contractor shall cease all work associated with the Contract. Should such an event occur, the Contractor shall be entitled to payment for charges incurred on the procurement cards as of the termination date. Upon such termination, the Contractor shall have no right to recover from the Institution any actual, general, special, incidental, consequential, or any other damages whatsoever of any description or amount. E.3. Breach. A party shall be deemed to have breached the Contract if any of the following, including but not limited to, occurs: — failure to perform in accordance with any term or provision of the Contract; — partial performance of any term or provision of the Contract; — any act prohibited or restricted by the Contract, or — violation of any warranty. For purposes of this Contract, these items shall hereinafter be referred to as a “Breach." a.      Contractor Breach— Institution shall notify Contractor in writing of a Breach. In event of a Breach by Contractor, the Institution shall have available the remedy of Actual Damages and any other remedy available at law or in equity. b.      Institution Breach— In the event of a Breach of contract by the Institution, the Contractor shall notify the Institution in writing within 30 days of any Breach of contract by the Institution. The notice shall contain a description of the Breach. In the event of Breach by the Institution, the Contractor may avail itself of any remedy at law in the Claims Commission; provided, however, failure by the Contractor to give the Institution written notice and opportunity to cure as described herein operates as a waiver of the Institution’s Breach. Failure by the Contractor to file a claim before the appropriate forum in Tennessee with jurisdiction to hear such claim within one (1) year of the written notice of Breach shall operate as a waiver of said claim in its entirety. It is agreed by the parties this provision establishes a contractual period of limitations for any claim brought by the Contractor. E.4. Certificates/lnsurance Provisions. Certificates: The Contractor shall have in force and effect a “Bankers Blanket Bond” or “Financial Institute Bond”, including computer crimes as well as error and omission insurance as required by Federal and State regulatory authorities. Insurance: The contractor shall carry public liability insurance in at least the amount of $1,000,000 umbrella coverage for any and all liability, costs, damage or expense arising out of the terms of the agreement for Instutition, its agents or employees. Workers' Compensation insurance to limits as defined by Tennessee statute must also be maintained at all times during the term(s) of the Contract. E.5. Incorporation of Additional Documents. Included in this Contract by reference are the following documents: a.      This Contract document and its attachments b.      All Clarifications and addenda made to the Contractor’s Proposal c.     The Request for Proposal and its associated amendments d.      Technical Specifications provided to the Contractor e.      The Contractor’s Proposal In the event of a discrepancy or ambiguity regarding the Contractor's duties, responsibilities, and performance under this Contract, these documents shall govern in order of precedence detailed above. E.6. Lobbying. The Contractor certifies, to the best of its knowledge and belief, that: No federally appropriated funds have been paid or will be paid, by or on behalf of the Contractor, to any person for influencing or attempting to influence an officer or employee of any agency, a Member of Congress in connection with the awarding of any federal contract, the making of any federal grant, the making of any federal loan, and entering into any cooperative agreement, and the extension, continuation, renewal, amendment, or modification of any federal contract, grant, loan, or cooperative agreement. If any funds other than federally appropriated funds have been paid or will be paid to any person for influencing or attempting to influence an officer or employee of any agency, a Member of Congress, an officer or employee of Congress, or an employee of a Member of Congress in connection with this contract, grant, loan, or cooperative agreement, the Contractor shall complete and submit Standard Form-LLL, “Disclosure Form to Report Lobbying,” in accordance with its instructions. The Contractor shall require that the language of this certification be included in the award documents for all sub-awards at all tiers (including sub-grants, subcontracts, and contracts under grants, loans, and cooperative agreements) and that all sub-recipients of federally appropriated funds shall certify and disclose accordingly. E.7. Prohibited Advertising. The Contractor shall not refer to this Contract or the Contractor’s relationship with the Institution hereunder in commercial advertising in such a manner as to state or imply that the Contractor or the Contractor's services are endorsed. E.8. Copyrights and Patents. The Contractor agrees to indemnify and hold harmless the Institution as well as its officers, agents, and employees from and against any and all claims or suits which may be brought against the Institution for infringement of any laws regarding patents or copyrights which may arise from the Contractor's performance of this Contract. In any such action brought against the Institution, the Contractor shall satisfy and indemnify the Institution for the amount of any final judgment for infringement. The Contractor further agrees it shall be liable for the reasonable fees of attorneys for the Institution in the event such service is necessitated to enforce the terms of this Contract or otherwise enforce the obligations of the Contractor to the Institution. The Institution shall give the Contractor written notice of any such claim or suit and full right and opportunity to conduct the Contractor’s own defense thereof. E.9. Authorized Individuals. Each party hereto has provided the other party hereto with a list identifying the individuals from whom the other party is authorized to accept any notices, requests, demands, or other advice which may be given hereunder by the party providing such list. Said lists, which are attached hereto as Attachment RFP Section 1.7.1.1, shall be valid until revoked or amended by further written notice. The parties hereto shall only be entitled to rely on notices, requests, demands, or other advice given by such individuals. E.10. Hold Harmless. The Contractor agrees to indemnify and hold harmless the Institution as well as its officers, agents, and employees from and against any and all claims, liabilities, losses, and causes of action which may arise, accrue, or result to any person, firm, corporation, or other entity which may be injured or damaged as a result of acts, omissions, or negligence on the part of the Contractor, its employees, or any person acting for or on its or their behalf relating to this Contract. The Contractor further agrees it shall be liable for the reasonable cost of attorneys for the Institution in the event such service is necessitated to enforce the terms of this Contract or otherwise enforce the obligations of the Contractor to the Institution. In the event of any such suit or claim, the Contractor shall give the Institution immediate notice thereof and shall provide all assistance required by the Institution in the Institution's defense. The Institution shall give the Contractor written notice of any such claim or suit, and the Contractor shall have full right and obligation to conduct the Contractor’s own defense thereof. Nothing contained herein shall be deemed to accord to the Contractor, through its attorney(s), the right to represent the Institution in any legal matter, such rights being governed by Tennessee Code Annotated, Section 8-6-106. E.11. Debarment and Suspension. The Contractor certifies, to the best of its knowledge and belief, that it and its principals: a are not presently debarred, suspended, proposed for debarment, declared ineligible, or voluntarily excluded from covered transactions by any Federal or Institution department or agency; b.      have not within a three (3) year period preceding this Contract been convicted of, or had a civil judgment rendered against them from commission of fraud, or a criminal offence in connection with obtaining attempting to obtain, or performing a public (Federal, State, or Local) transaction or grant under a public transaction; violation of Federal or State antitrust statutes or commission of embezzlement, theft, forgery, bribery, falsification, or destruction of records, making false Statements, or receiving stolen property; c.      are not presently indicted for or otherwise criminally or civilly charged by a government entity (Federal, State, or Local) with commission of any of the offenses detailed in section b. of this certification; and d.      have not within a three (3) year period preceding this Contract had one or more public transactions (Federal, State, or Local) terminated for cause or default. E.12. Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA 12-4-124, reguires that Contactor attest in writing that Contractor will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated as Attachment A. If Contractor is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that the Contractor shall be prohibited from contracting or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. Contractor may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. IN WITNESS WHEREOF: FIFTH THIRD BANK VOLUNTEER STATE COMMUNITY COLLEGE: Elizabeth C. Cooksey, VP of Business and Finance Date Warren R. Nichols, President Date APPROVED: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS: Charles W. Manning, Chancellor Date</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode83644CBA-5DAB-4986-A838-F36E4BABCEC2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3490</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3531</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode690F9A37-B1B5-4364-A92D-72A1E74E84D8"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA770C475-E942-4005-86DE-FE81AA2DC910">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3490</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3523</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode690F9A37-B1B5-4364-A92D-72A1E74E84D8"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1100000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9DD95768-1A37-4367-A586-899661602FD4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3524</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3531</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode690F9A37-B1B5-4364-A92D-72A1E74E84D8"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">dollars</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA2AA1975-9101-44FD-B8C3-905CFFF718EB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3533</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3546</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode194C3A11-4CDC-4693-9AD5-48AEAEB58CD0"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode17C8A48C-5624-4145-AF14-7C511FB3DBC9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3533</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3534</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode194C3A11-4CDC-4693-9AD5-48AEAEB58CD0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeD8193E73-C279-4922-9AEC-204ABCF87EC8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3534</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">3546</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode194C3A11-4CDC-4693-9AD5-48AEAEB58CD0"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">1100000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode70184287-EE10-4080-98AF-B28D2CA3CEE4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4970</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4971</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode38C83791-C99A-4D5D-A984-022A3226CAB4"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeADFB6E5D-2CD8-429F-9113-7E32CD643376">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4970</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4980</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode38C83791-C99A-4D5D-A984-022A3226CAB4"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode91EF5716-1809-424F-A595-A7749325259E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4971</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4980</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode38C83791-C99A-4D5D-A984-022A3226CAB4"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">6000001</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode11ED176E-5659-410A-991F-BAF5403C5822">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4982</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4993</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode23A0F015-AFF8-431B-B599-500B1C92F287"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEF016E2-30B2-4B51-96E7-FA9C97314934">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4982</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4983</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode23A0F015-AFF8-431B-B599-500B1C92F287"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode280A6392-7468-4008-98CB-D4213FFDF876">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4983</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">4993</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode23A0F015-AFF8-431B-B599-500B1C92F287"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">10000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE7562C26-E467-462B-942A-60CF7B80CDE1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5006</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5007</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode871C47C0-BBA3-4DFB-A011-F3AEEBA46201"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode859D47EC-FC44-41E4-83D3-133C70CE3EC4">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5006</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5017</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode871C47C0-BBA3-4DFB-A011-F3AEEBA46201"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9A2F3AB4-FCF3-4059-92AF-81B2B34659BB">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5007</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5017</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode871C47C0-BBA3-4DFB-A011-F3AEEBA46201"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">10000001</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC192FACD-E924-404C-B982-AE8059823E9E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5019</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5020</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5415A2FE-5E98-4D4E-AA18-167E84D4648D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode778874BE-561C-4F1D-B5E3-445D6793DBAF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5019</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5030</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5415A2FE-5E98-4D4E-AA18-167E84D4648D"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode64FDBC1F-0174-498E-A0E5-0A44A5F74C92">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5020</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5030</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode5415A2FE-5E98-4D4E-AA18-167E84D4648D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">15000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode14FA5546-C348-4E78-B9BD-FCDD666C1FC5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5043</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5044</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD54521D4-DACB-4358-8AB2-4D4D5ECB659C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0F756BC-B341-43A3-B95D-5868983990AD">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5043</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5054</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD54521D4-DACB-4358-8AB2-4D4D5ECB659C"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode8B7BBD93-E116-405B-A6D0-AE1598C692A3">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5044</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5054</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeD54521D4-DACB-4358-8AB2-4D4D5ECB659C"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">15000001</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode48886943-3BF3-4F84-AF1F-527522369BF2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5056</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5057</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode958E0650-7414-42E1-B8BB-169F0F634A28"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode368902E0-FA33-4960-9CA0-C70475FBB8B1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5056</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5067</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode958E0650-7414-42E1-B8BB-169F0F634A28"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC22962B9-B4B8-4863-BAEC-AB176709D188">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5057</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5067</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode958E0650-7414-42E1-B8BB-169F0F634A28"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">20000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode978CDA87-CE2E-43DA-86BC-CCC8EA617176">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5080</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5081</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode09E25D13-DCED-4261-9F6B-ECEA27442083"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode66E091E2-3226-44EC-8C09-6BD695A48BB0">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5080</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5091</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode09E25D13-DCED-4261-9F6B-ECEA27442083"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0C466151-ED72-4FD0-9572-2D61D46614A2">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5081</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">5091</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode09E25D13-DCED-4261-9F6B-ECEA27442083"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">20000001</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>