<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374689" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode60BBD6AD-AC96-4A37-B93E-A6223A47DC25">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">DOLLARS</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">270000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode79F9048D-7186-4E6E-A125-52B954E9AB44">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">270000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode475607E9-D183-42B0-A188-158777AD6A03">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">270000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeBA481492-79DE-452F-B8D9-DE3E2C7C52C1">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">332.77-09.620 AGREEMENT THIS AGREEMENT, made and entered into this i U-^day of      -   2009, by and between SUMMITT MANAGEMENT CORPORATION (hereinafter, "SMC") and TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY, a Tennessee Board of Regents institution, (hereinafter, "TSU" WITNESSETH: WHEREAS, SMC seeks to sponsor an annual cultural, entertainment and sporting event to be known as the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC, to take place in Memphis, Shelby County, Tennessee. WHEREAS, TSU has agreed to participate in said SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC by way of its varsity football team and by the performance ofTSU's marching band during the pre-game, half-time and in a parade prior to the game. NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration of the mutual covenants and agreements herein contained, it is hereby agreed as follows: SECTION I.        Services to be Performed. 1.1    The varsity football team representing TSU shall play in a football game at the Liberty Bowl Memorial Stadium in Memphis, Tennessee on the following dates: September 11,2010 September 10, 2011 September 8, 2012 September 14, 2013 September 13, 2014 Failure of the varsity football team to play in the football game shall be considered a significant breach of this Agreement. 1.2    The marching band of TSU shall agree to the following: (a) perform at a parade at approximately 8:00 A.M. on the day of the game, (b) pre-game performance, and (c) perform during half-time. Failure of the marching band to perform at any event specified herein shall be considered a significant breach of this Agreement. 2.1    During the Term of this Agreement, SMC agrees to guarantee the sum of TWO HUNDRED SEVENTY THOUSAND ($270,000) annually to the TSU football team for participation in said SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC, as set forth herein. The guarantee shall be secured with a letter of credit, performance bond or insurance sixty (60) days prior to the date of the event. In addition, SMC agrees to contribute THIRTY THOUSAND DOLLARS ($30,000) annually to the TSU marching band. Except as specifically provided above and herein below, no other compensation or remuneration shall be payable by SMC to TSU pursuant to this Agreement. 2.2    TSU will retain its advance ticket sales proceeds, with any difference between this amount and the TWO HUNDRED SEVENTY THOUSAND DOLLARS ($270,000) annual guaranteed installment as stated in Section 2.1 to be settled as soon as possible after the close of the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC, but no later than thirty (30) days thereafter. 2.3    SMC shall be responsible for the following: (a)    Rental of Liberty Bowl Memorial Stadium. (b)    Provide all supporting personnel (scoreboard operator, ticket sellers, ushers, gatemen, first aid attendants, ambulance service and attendants). (c)    All advertising and promotion costs. (d)    All catering for President's box and working media. (e)     Printing of tickets. 2.4     SMC shall obtain public liability insurance in appropriate amounts insuring the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC and TSU from liabilities arising from the sporting event controlled by SMC. Upon request, a certificate of insurance will be issued to TSU. 2.5    Any and all claims against the Institution (TSU) for personal and/or property damage resulting from the negligence of the Institution (TSU) in performing any responsibility specifically required under the terms of this Agreement shall be submitted to the Board of Claims or the Claims Commission for the State of Tennessee. Damages recoverable against the Institution (TSU) shall be expressly limited to claims paid by the Board or Claims Commission pursuant to T.C.A. Section 9-8-301, et seq. 2.6    TSU shall be responsible for travel, meals and lodging expenses incurred in connection with its football team, marching band and staff. 2.7    A business settlement and payment of the guaranteed annual installment amount due TSU hereunder shall be made as soon as possible after the close of the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC, but no later than thirty (30) days thereafter. Business settlement is to be made by certified check, bank money order or some other acceptable negotiable financial instrument (no personal checks), including a summary event reconciliation statement, and made payable and mailed to: Tennessee State University 3500 John A. Merritt Boulevard Campus Box 9626 Nashville, TN 37209-1561 Attn: Business Office  2.8    Use of the Stadium Club shall be at the sole discretion of SMC. If used, TSU will receive seventy-five (75) passes for its use. All costs for catering to be paid by SMC. 2.9    SMC to provide one complimentary hotel bedroom suite for the President during weekend of the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC. 2.10  SMC agrees to pay any and all other expenses related to the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC that are not provided specifically herein, but in no event shall the amount paid to TSU exceed the amounts specified in the various provisions of the Agreement. SECTION 3.       Game Rules. 3.1   The SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC football game shall be conducted under the rules of the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA). 3.2    Game officials shall be appointed by the participating schools. The costs and expenses of the game officials and chain crew shall be paid by SMC. Total amount payable by SMC not to exceed FIVE THOUSAND DOLLARS ($5,000). Any excess amount shall be paid by the home team. SECTION 4.       Tickets. 4.1    TSU shall be provided with Four Hundred (400) complimentary tickets for its use and benefit. 4.2    SMC shall designate 2,000 tickets to be sold from the TSU box office as student tickets with the proceeds included in the business settlement at Section 2.2. SMC reserves the right to set the student ticket price at its discretion. 5.1    SMC shall own and have the sole and exclusive right to negotiate and contract for the sale and licensing of any radio and/or television broadcasting rights of the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC, and any audio or video recordings of same. Any fees or compensation payable for such rights and/or recordings shall be paid to SMC. TSU shall have the right to broadcast, via radio, to its respective home market without remuneration to SMC. SECTION 6.       Game Program. 6.1    SMC shall be responsible for producing and disbursing game programs and other literature and shall receive all revenue from the sale of same. TSU agrees to cooperate with and assist SMC in the preparation of the same by providing such information, photographs and written materials as SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC reasonably requests, no later than Sixty (60) days prior to the game. SECTION 7.       Copyrights and Royalties. 7.1    TSU warrants that all copyrighted material to be performed by its respective marching band has been duly licensed or authorized by the copyright owners or their representatives. Further, TSU shall assume all responsibility for any payment of royalty fees in connection therewith. 7.2    TSU agrees to allow SMC and its sponsors to use the school name and logo in any advertisements and promotions of and/or related to the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC through print media, broadcast media, concession sales and other souvenir sales and incentives for the period of participation. Any other use of copyrighted logos and emblems owned by TSU shall be only underwritten authority granted by TSU. SECTION 8.       Term of Agreement. 8.1    The term of this Agreement shall be for an initial term of five (5) years, 2010 through 2014 (hereinafter the “Term”). 8.2    This contract may be terminated annually by either party giving written notice to the other by October 15th. SECTION 9.       Promotions. 9.1 TSU agrees to notify alumni of the SOUTHERN HERITAGE CLASSIC via its alumni newsletter or a special alumni mailing. It is further agreed that the above will be performed no later than July 10 prior to each game. 10.1     This Agreement shall be binding on, and inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and assigns. 10.2    If any provision or part of this Agreement is declared or for any reason determined invalid or unenforceable, it shall be deemed severable and the validity of the remainder or the application of such provision to other circumstances shall not be affected thereby. 10.3    The failure of any party to seek redress for violation of, or to insist upon the strict performance of any provision or condition of this Agreement shall now constitute a waiver or in any way prevent subsequent enforcement of any such provisions or conditions. 10.4   The undersigned person executing this Agreement on behalf of each party hereby represents and warrants that all action necessary to authorize the execution and delivery of this Agreement has been taken by the party for whom he is signing and that the undersigned has been duly authorized and directed by such party to execute and deliver this Agreement. 10.5    SMC warrants that no part of the total contract amount provided herein shall be paid, directly or indirectly, to any officer or employee of the State of Tennessee as wages, compensation, or gifts in exchange for acting as officer, agent, employee, sub-contractor, or to SMC as an individual. SMC warrants that within the past six (6) months, it has not been, and during the term of the contract will not become an employee of the State of Tennessee. 10.6    SMC warrants that it is an independent contractor and not an employee of TSU. 10.7   SMC shall maintain documentation of all transactions related to this agreement. The books, records and documents of SMC, insofar as they relate to the terms of this agreement, shall be maintained for a period of three (3) full years from the date of the final payment, and shall be subject to audit, at any reasonable time and upon reasonable notice, by the TSU or the State Comptroller of the Treasury or their duly authorized representatives. 10.8   The parties agree to comply with Title VI and VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, Title IX of the Education Amendments of 1973, Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, Executive Order 11, 246 and the related regulations to each. Each party assures that it will not discriminate against any individual including, but not limited to, employees or applicants for employment and/or students because of race, religion, creed, color, sex, age, handicap, veteran status or national origin. The parties also agree to take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during their employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, or national origin. Such action shall include, but is not limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion or transfer, recruitment or recruitment advertising, layoff or termination, rates of pay or other forms of compensation, and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. 10.9  This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of Tennessee and federal law. 10.10 Prohibition on Hiring Illegal Immigrants. Tennessee Public Chapter No. 878 of 2006, TCA §12-4-124, requires that SMC attest in writing that SMC will not knowingly utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract and will not knowingly utilize the services of any subcontractor, if permitted under this Contract, who will utilize the services of illegal immigrants in the performance of this Contract. The attestation shall be made on the form, Attestation re Personnel Used in Contract Performance (“the Attestation”), which is attached and hereby incorporated by this reference. If SMC is discovered to have breached the Attestation, the Commissioner of Finance and Administration shall declare that SMC shall be prohibited from contracting with or submitting a bid to any Tennessee Board of Regents institution or any other state entity for a period of one (1) year from the date of discovery of the breach. SMC may appeal the one (1) year by utilizing an appeals process in the Rules of Finance and Administration, Chapter 0620. 10.11  It is hereby agreed that this Agreement constitutes and expresses the entire agreement between the parties. The provisions of this Agreement are not subject to amendment or modification, except by written instrument signed by both parties. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, the parties have by their duly authorized representatives set forth their signatures. TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY 3500 John Merritt Blvd. Nashville, TN 37209-1561 Athletic Director SUMMITT MANAGEMENT CORPORATION 4466 Elvis Presley Blvd. Suite 248 Memphis, TN 38116 BY. Fred Jones, Jr. President TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS APPROVED: by: Charles W. Manning Chancellor </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeA72CFFB3-1988-45F2-9D79-1F36809E3E4F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1620</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1648</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode79F9048D-7186-4E6E-A125-52B954E9AB44"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode133FA679-4BC4-4AEC-9C21-9A9967512646">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1620</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1648</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode79F9048D-7186-4E6E-A125-52B954E9AB44"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">270000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeADBB142F-0021-492D-B7F1-DCB2F7796C78">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1650</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1658</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode475607E9-D183-42B0-A188-158777AD6A03"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB5AD161B-CD05-43CD-B040-ACEE8FAEBC15">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1650</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1651</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode475607E9-D183-42B0-A188-158777AD6A03"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode656141C1-609A-4888-B564-584F088AF62B">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1651</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1658</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode475607E9-D183-42B0-A188-158777AD6A03"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">270000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode21979AE3-1BE5-4212-BADF-4D6D212F0D26">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2268</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2304</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode60BBD6AD-AC96-4A37-B93E-A6223A47DC25"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode04C1B4BB-CB60-49DD-B194-A66E2250C3A1">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2268</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2296</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode60BBD6AD-AC96-4A37-B93E-A6223A47DC25"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">270000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5F8EE78E-1889-4A05-B302-7E4D824E5647">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2297</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">2304</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode60BBD6AD-AC96-4A37-B93E-A6223A47DC25"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">DOLLARS</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>