<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374693" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4A81FA61-0B94-4220-9626-FD7E64755112">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">252130</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeE0450FDB-1817-4170-9FA3-4B9BE3FE1CFA">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">KNOXVILLE-KNOX COUNTY COMMUNITY ACTION COMMITTEE And TENNESSEE TECHNOLOGY CENTER AT KNOXVILLE LICENSED PRACTICAL NURSING PROGRAM This Agreement is made and executed in Knoxville, Tennessee, on the 4th day of September 2009; by and between: The Knoxville-Knox County Community Action Committee (CAC), 2247 Western Avenue, P. 0. Box 51650, Knoxville, Tennessee 37950-1650, a public agency with full designated legal authority to administer employment and training programs on behalf of the Chief Elected Official of Knox County, and Tennessee Technology Center at Knoxville, 1100 Liberty Street, Knoxville, Tennessee 37919, a public entity with full legal authority to do business in the State of Tennessee, and hereinafter referred to as the "Subcontractor". Witnesseth: Whereas, this is a subcontract under CAC administered contract(s) with the State of Tennessee to provide employment and training services under the Workforce Investment Act (WIA), And Whereas, the purpose of this agreement is to conduct a program of employment and training services for residents of Local Workforce Investment 3; Now therefore, the parties do mutually agree as follows: 1.  Period. The Subcontractor will begin performance of this agreement on or after the eighth day of July, 2009 and will complete performance no later that the 31st day of July, 2010. 2. Compensation. The total amount paid by the CAC to the Subcontractor under this agreement shall not exceed $252,130.00 all of which shall be classified as training costs. 3.  Performance Objectives. A. The Subcontractor will: 1. Provide 84 hours of pre-skills instruction for 42 participants selected for the program. 2.  Provide training In Licensed Practical Nursing resulting in the issuance of the appropriate Licensed Practical Nursing license to 42 students selected and approved by the CAC. 3.  Provide books, fees, training supplies, instructional staff and other training related services necessary for the conduct of the program. Specific books and supplies to be provided as listed on Attachment C. 4.  Provide students with information regarding health &amp; accident insurance and liability insurance programs available through subcontractors. B. The CAC will: 1.  Certify and refer eligible participants to the Subcontractor 2.  Provide participant support such as tools, uniforms, certain fees, and other items not included in Attachment C necessary to support the participant and enable the participant to complete the training and become employed. 3.  Reimburse the Subcontractor for costs associated with the conduct of the training program up to the total compensation amount. 4. Method of Payment. Payments will be made by the CAC to the Subcontractor according to the following provisions: The Subcontractor may invoice quarterly attaching copies of the Trainee Progress/Attendance Report, signed by both the instructor and student. Invoices submitted for the first three quarters may be prorated portions of the total compensation amount. The final invoice must be accompanied by a Year-To-Date Expenditure Report documenting actual expenses in accordance with the approved allocation plan and budget. The total compensation invoiced to the CAC will not exceed the Subcontractor's actual cumulative operating expenses, including budgeted allocated student fees, for these activities or the $252,130.00 whichever is less. 5. Program Implementation A. The Subcontractor agrees to implement this Agreement in accordance with the specifications outlined in the Licensed Practical Nurse Training Curriculum. B. The Subcontractor agrees to accept for enrollment into this training program only those individuals who have been WIA registered and referred to the Subcontractor. C. The Subcontractor agrees to assist the CAC in verifying the employment of participants successfully completing the training program. D. The Subcontractor agrees that the full expenditure of the status of invoices submitted for payment shall never be a basis for withholding any services to any participant relating to their training or employment. 6. Incorporation. This agreement is subject to and Incorporates, as if each document were written in full within this provision, the following attachments: A. "Standard Provisions and Assurances for Agreements under the Workforce Investment Act" dated July 1, 2005. B. The Subcontractor's proposal and budgets. C. Specific list of Books and Supplies. The authorized parties agree to the provisions outlined above. Knoxville-Knox County Community Action Committee Tennessee Technology Center at Knoxville Tennessee State Board of Regents </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode0E79D406-2C19-456A-B014-61A1B7B0DBA6">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1450</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1461</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4A81FA61-0B94-4220-9626-FD7E64755112"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode270CE99C-4D89-4A32-88C2-A53B146EBA00">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1450</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1451</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4A81FA61-0B94-4220-9626-FD7E64755112"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeE23FD80B-A770-4236-91C6-C4BAC69D2DD5">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1451</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1461</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4A81FA61-0B94-4220-9626-FD7E64755112"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">252130</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>