<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374694" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeF2DF6F14-983A-4AE3-9031-558A554D218B">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">5392.3</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode225F7A83-2392-494D-8A23-5AE0E8DEC0F8">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT FOR EMPLOYEE SERVICES Middle Tennessee State University          Tennessee Board of Regents VENDOR PARTY                 PROCURING PARTY This memorandum signifies agreement of the above parties concerning the provision of employee services. The agreement is as follows: 1. Vendor agrees to furnish the services of its employee, Karen Ward, who will be 50% at TBR for the month of September 2009 and perform the following services for procuring party: Serve as the Regents Online Campus Collaborative (ROCC) Director of Nursing Education and Allied Health. 2. Compensation to vendor party (includes cost of any applicable staff benefits to vendor's employee for service under this agreement) $5,392.30 per month for the month of September 09.* Maximum liability of procuring party $5,392.30** * Extra compensation in the amount of $9,166.67 per month plus 568.34 FICA @ 6.2%, $132.92 FICA Med @ 1.45%; and $916.67 Retirement @10% ORP. **Maximum amount may be adjusted subject to across-the-board/pay plan increases, insurance premium changes. 3. Payment will be made by procuring party after completion of service and after receipt of invoice from vendor party, mailed to the following address: Deanna Hall Director of Fiscal Services Tennessee Board of Regents 1415 Murfreesboro Road, Suite 350 Nashville, TN 37217 4. Contract term: September 1, 2009 through September 30, 2009. 5. Either party may terminate this agreement by giving written notice to the other at least 30 days before the effective date of termination. In that event, vendor shall be entitled to receive just and equitable compensation for any satisfactory work completed as of the termination date. In addition, procuring party shall have the right to immediately terminate this agreement and withhold payments in excess of fair compensation for work completed in the event that the employee fails to perform in a timely and proper manner or breaches any material term of this agreement. 6. This agreement cannot be assigned or subcontracted without the written consent of all parties. 7. During the performance of this contract both parties warrant that they will not discriminate against any employee or applicant for employment because of race, age, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, veteran status or national origin. The parties will take affirmative action to ensure that applicants are employed and that employees are treated during employment without regard to their race, religion, creed, color, sex, disability, or national origin. Such action shall include, but not be limited to, the following: employment, upgrading, demotion, transfer; recruitment or recruitment advertising; layoff or termination; rates of pay or other forms of compensation; and selection available to employees and applicants for employment. Dated this 17th day of August, 2009. TITL^ John W. Cothern Vice President DATE:__\ \ \OCj BY: TENNESSEE BOARD OF REGENTS DATE: </Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3A137509-91CC-40F1-B7E8-5FAA36815A8A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">715</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">724</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF2DF6F14-983A-4AE3-9031-558A554D218B"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeB754156A-D53F-40AF-A6EF-4334405C1E7E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">715</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">716</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF2DF6F14-983A-4AE3-9031-558A554D218B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode5F1BCD66-E1B4-49FF-BEC2-23A8614EA05E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">716</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">724</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeF2DF6F14-983A-4AE3-9031-558A554D218B"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">5392.3</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>