<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374203" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnodeED8AD040-370D-45A2-A164-D1AE666AEB87">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">bolivianos</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">400</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeFCEE3061-BA5A-4D07-8CF9-D39B5F520CAF">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">The tricameral congress comprised the Senate and the Chamber of Tribunes, whose members had fixed terms, as well as a Chamber of Censors, whose members served for life. Theoretically, the Senate was responsible for codifying laws and reorienting church and court officials, the Chamber of Tribunes possessed general legislative powers, and the Chamber of Censors had oversight powers that included impeachment of members of the executive. In reality, the legislature's key functions were to name the president and to approve a list of successors submitted by the president. One of the long-lasting effects of the Bolivarian constitution was the establishment of an executive-based system. The Bolivarian constitution reflected the Spanish tradition of bureaucratic patrimonialism in which power rested in the executive branch. In many ways, the Bolivarian constitution reflected Bolívar's desire to prevent rule by the masses. As a result, the franchise was extended only to those literate in Spanish who either possessed property then worth 400 bolivianos or engaged in an art, in a science, or in some other remunerative position. Domestic and personal servants were also denied the franchise. In short, voting rights were limited to a very small and privileged elite. Voting qualifications and restrictions remained until universal suffrage was adopted during the 1952 Revolution. Bolívar also feared that rival elite factions would wage battle against each other for control over the new nation and became convinced that the best way to prevent instability and chaos was to institutionalize a strong, centralized, and lifetime presidency.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC127D60A-82D9-41E8-BF36-BA362F181CB9">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1042</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1056</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeED8AD040-370D-45A2-A164-D1AE666AEB87"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeEEB3E6E3-B514-4AF6-BE3A-BC18EA5AF754">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1042</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1045</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeED8AD040-370D-45A2-A164-D1AE666AEB87"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">400</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeC6DE4331-542D-4349-8B04-4076F60D4ABF">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1046</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1056</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnodeED8AD040-370D-45A2-A164-D1AE666AEB87"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">bolivianos</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>