<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3374703" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode4F7E69E3-D0C0-4AF1-ABFE-810036D559B7">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">$</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">3850</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode21F42B63-A457-4D73-8C46-83BD0A25A142">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">NASH Natk«ai Association cf Sys&gt; tw Hems May 16, 2011 The Education Trust is a national nonprofit organization committed to the high academic achievement of all students, pre-k through college, and to closing the achievement gaps that separate students of color and those from low-income families from other young people. The Education Trust is partnering with the National Association of System Heads (NASH) in the Access to Success Initiative, and serves as managing partner for the Initiative. The Access to Success Initiative (A2S) is an ambitious effort undertaken by a number of NASH members—state higher education systems—to improve overall student success and to close by at least half the gaps in both college-going and college completion that separate low-income and minority students from others by 2015. A2S is supported by the Bill &amp; Melinda Gates and Lumina Foundations. A crucial aspect of A2S is the collection, analysis, and public reporting of data to document annually each system's progress towards the Initiative goals. These metrics measure progress in ways that improve on traditional measures, which requires systems to make an extra effort to collect new data and to analyze it in nontraditional ways. In order to support this extra effort, and to ensure the full and timely delivery of the required data, the following agreement is put in effect. AGREEMENT The Education Trust agrees to provide $3,850 to each participating system, in this case The Tennessee Board of Regents, to support the data collection effort of the Access to Success Initiative. The funds will be paid upon receipt of this signed agreement. The amount of funds provided this year have been reduced due to funding limitations but we hope that the investments made in the data collection process and platform will compensate by requiring less time to submit the data. The Tennessee Board of Regents agrees to submit the data requested to The Education Trust by June 30, 201$ and to participate in conference calls and/or webinars pertaining to the data collection and analyses as needed. The A2S data site will open in mid-May at which time systems can download the updated templates for the 2011 collection. Systems will receive an email with their login information from our data vendor the week of May 16, 2011 with further instructions. Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs The Tennessee Board of Regents contact Jennifer Engle, Dir^ptor of Higher Education Research and Policy, at jengle@edtrust.org or Ericka Miller Vice President for Operations &amp; Strategic Leadership The Education Trust -(s -    'I/ Date Date Attachment CC:      John Morgan GregShutz</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnodeF7AEA2C3-8D2E-4A96-86F1-B942B343E549">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1421</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1427</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4F7E69E3-D0C0-4AF1-ABFE-810036D559B7"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode50CFCD81-8692-4DD2-ABFB-36C6EB9D0C16">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1421</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1422</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4F7E69E3-D0C0-4AF1-ABFE-810036D559B7"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">$</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode48D01E86-E3C7-4B6E-B4DB-9B74755EA16A">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1422</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">1427</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode4F7E69E3-D0C0-4AF1-ABFE-810036D559B7"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">3850</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>