<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3375925" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode191E6CA0-BFCC-4D70-BBCF-82223E7E358D">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">HRK</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">54000000000</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnodeB67DF347-B243-418A-B165-5858E9AB21A1">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">Until now, INA has been involved in exploration and production operations in Croatia (Pannonian basin, Adriatic offshore) and 20 foreign countries. Today INA operates its exploration and production activities in Croatia, Egypt and Angola. In exploration and production, as the primary initiator of company’s development, in the future INA plans to follow development strategy based on research, development of existing projects and the potential action of non-organic steps. The Company is focused on 100% reserves replacement and maintenance of production level of approximately 70,000 boe per day. Downstream INA has two fuel refineries, located in Rijeka (Urinj) and Sisak. The refinery in Rijeka is located on shore, allowing access to the port for deep-drawing ships and the pipeline system of JANAF. More than HRK 54 billion is invested in the refinery system development in the last few years. In Rijeka refinery three facilities within Hydrocracking complex were built – Mild hydrocracking, Hydrogen unit and Desulphurization plant (Claus) as well as numerous supporting facilities and installations. The facilities are in commercial work from May 2011. In February 2014 a contract on basic design for the Delayed Coking Unit for Rijeka Refinery was signed with the company Bechtel Hydrocarbon Technical Solutions (BHTS). In Sisak refinery three plants have been completed: desulphurization plant, the so-called Claus the hydrodesulphurization of FCC gasoline plant and Isomerization plant. Furthermore, from mid-2013 Sisak Refinery has the possibility of production of diesel fuels with bio component and in the same year in September a system of additional wastewater treatment KROFTA was put into operation, while in April 2014 the installation of new coke chambers was carried out at the Coking plant.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode84B8D2F0-0492-41D2-8F58-01EDDF61EA9E">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">816</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">830</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode191E6CA0-BFCC-4D70-BBCF-82223E7E358D"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode3C85707B-9638-43FA-B90E-2E5516A62526">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">816</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">819</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode191E6CA0-BFCC-4D70-BBCF-82223E7E358D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">HRK</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode72EC06F3-A0AC-48EC-8597-C3BDBD164588">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">820</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">830</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode191E6CA0-BFCC-4D70-BBCF-82223E7E358D"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">54000000000</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>