<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?OntoDPSData docID="3376233" markupID="2092790" OntoTechnologyVersion="3.59.92.0"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:BasicEntity="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:Aux="http://www.abbyy.com/ns/Aux#">
	<BasicEntity:MoneySimplified rdf:nodeID="bnode87C138EE-AB5B-4D6C-AF54-DE7BC6EADD3F">
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_currency xml:lang="en-US">reichsmarks</BasicEntity:ms_major_currency>
		<BasicEntity:ms_major_amount xml:lang="en-US">10</BasicEntity:ms_major_amount>
	</BasicEntity:MoneySimplified>
	<Aux:TextAnnotations rdf:nodeID="bnode5A7836F7-79DA-4FF3-83CD-FBFBEE8FB9A2">
		<Aux:document_text xml:lang="en-US">First underground Polish teams there were created in late 1939 and early 1940, among youth of districts of Widzew, Karolew, Ruda Pabianicka and Retkinia, also in towns of Zgierz and Pabianice. It has been established that in 1942, the final match between Cytadela and Wólka, was ended 10 minutes before time. Several Polish teams were active in the city during the occupation. According to the webpage of Łódź Office of Polish Football Association, these were: Wólka, Wola, Wicher (which was made of players of ŁKS Łódź), Cytadela, Widzew, Zdrowie, Ruda, Chojny, Retkinia, Harcerze, Klapitka, Pabianice and Zgierz. Most active football team of wartime Łódź was Widzew, which played several games in that period, but the best team of wartime Łódź was Wólka. On October 24, 1943, the game between Wólka and Wicher was interrupted by German police. Many players and fans were arrested, and taken to a police station, but all were released after paying the ticket in the amount of 10 reichsmarks. in Piotrków Trybunalski, there were five teams: Huta (now Concordia), Bugaj - Zryw, Pekin - Ruch, Arba (former Zakład Skórzany). Since 1940, they played regular games, with lookouts scanning the area, as Germans tried to catch players. in Rzeszów, games of Resovia Rzeszów were organized since 1942 in neighboring town of Strzyzów, regarded as a safer location. Like in other places of the occupied country, players risked arrest, but their love of the game was more important. Among those who took part in those games were Edmund Białas of Lech Poznań, who lived in Rzeszów during the war, and Tadeusz Hogendorf, legendary player of Resovia and Warszawianka Warszawa. Hogendorf recalled later that Germans asked Poles to play against them. Matches took place somewhere near Dębica, and Germans provided transportation for Polish players.</Aux:document_text>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:InstanceAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode445118BD-590A-46DC-B4C8-1C7887F9E84F">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">977</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">991</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode87C138EE-AB5B-4D6C-AF54-DE7BC6EADD3F"/>
			</Aux:InstanceAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode9826B23D-932E-4947-ABC2-B7121FC4DB5C">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">977</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">979</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode87C138EE-AB5B-4D6C-AF54-DE7BC6EADD3F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_amount</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">10</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
		<Aux:annotation>
			<Aux:PropertyAnnotation rdf:nodeID="bnode14A70237-11BD-420C-991E-B38B612BE6D8">
				<Aux:annotation_start rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">980</Aux:annotation_start>
				<Aux:annotation_end rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#integer">991</Aux:annotation_end>
				<Aux:instance rdf:nodeID="bnode87C138EE-AB5B-4D6C-AF54-DE7BC6EADD3F"/>
				<Aux:property_name xml:lang="en-US">http://www.abbyy.com/ns/BasicEntity#ms_major_currency</Aux:property_name>
				<Aux:property_value xml:lang="en-US">reichsmarks</Aux:property_value>
			</Aux:PropertyAnnotation>
		</Aux:annotation>
	</Aux:TextAnnotations>
</rdf:RDF>